Eigth
Pam! Pamela! Pamela-ma-ding-dong! Making copies!
I'm not making any copies.
Let's go! Messages, stat, lotsa do, lotsa do. Information superhighway.
Nothing new.
Lay them on moi. What?
There's nothing new.
That's not what you said earlier.
Oh, do you want me to repeat the messages that I gave you before for the...
The most sacred thing I do is care and provide for my workers, my family.
I give them money. I give them food. Not directly, but through the money.
I heal them. Today I am in charge of picking a great new health care plan.
Right? That's what this is all about.
Does that make me their doctor?
Um... yes. In a way. Yeah, like a specialist.
So, which health plan have you decided on?
I am going to go with the best, Jan. I am going to go with the one with the acupuncture, therapeutic massage, you know, the works.
Wait, acupuncture?
Mm-hmm.
None of the plans have acupuncture. Have you looked at them closely, Michael?
Oh, I think it was you who didn't look closely enough at the gold plan.
The gold plan?
Yeah.
I'm not even on that plan.
Well, I'd recommend it.
Michael.
It's very good.
You gotta crack these things open.
You know, the whole reason that we're doing this is to save money.
So, you just need to pick a provider and then choose the cheapest plan.
Well, that is kind of a tough assignment. It's not going to be a popular decision around the old orifice.
So...
Well, it's a suicide mission, you know?
Michael.
I don't...
Maybe, I mean...
They're...
You know, sometimes a manager, like yourself, has to deliver the bad news to the employees. I do it all the time.
Oh, yeah, one of you ever done that.
So, I'm doing it right now. To you.
Last night on Trading Spouses, there's... Have you seen it?
No, I have a life.
Interesting. What's that like?
You should try it sometime.
Wow. But then who would watch my TV?
Sort of like...
That would be a problem.
There's a decision that needs to be made and I'm having an unbelievably busy day.
So, I am going to let you pick a healthcare plan for our office and then explain it to your coworker.