All right, Jim, your quarterlies look very good.
How are things going at the library?
Oh, I told you, I couldn't close it, so...
So you've come to the master for guidance?
Is this what you're saying, Grasshopper?
Uh, actually, you called me in here, but, yeah.
All right, well, let me show you how it's done.
Yes, I'd like to speak to your office manager, please.
Yes, hello, this is Michael Scott.
I am the regional manager of Dunder Mifflin Paper Products.
I just wanted to talk to you manager-a-manager.
All right, done deal.
Thank you very much, sir.
You're a gentleman and a scholar.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Okay, I'm sorry. My mistake.
That was a woman I was talking to.
So she had a very low voice.
Probably a smoker.
So...
So that's the way it's done.
I've been at Dunder Mifflin for 12 years,
the last four as regional manager.
Uh, if you want to come through here...
Ah, see, we have the entire floor.
So this is my kingdom, far as the eye can see.
Ah, this is our receptionist, Pam.
Pam! Pam, Pam!
Pam Beasley.
Pam has been with us, um, for forever.
Right, Pam?
Well, I don't know.
If you think she's cute now,
you should have seen her a couple of years ago.
What?
Uh, any messages?
Um, yeah, just a fax.
Oh.
Pam, this is from corporate.
I know.
How many times have I told you
that there's a special filing cabinet
for things from corporate?
You haven't told me.
It's called the Waste Paper Basket.
Ha ha ha!
Look at that!
Oh, look at that face!
People say I am the best boss.
They go,
God, we've never worked in a place like this before.
You're hilarious.
And you get the best out of us.
Um...
I think that pretty much sums it up.
I found it at Spencer Gifts.
I found my play for you
Ba-dum-dum-dum-dum...
Da-da-dum dums, da-da-dum...
I want no gifts for you
Ba-dum-dum-dum precis-da-da-dum-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da...
My name is Jim Halpert,
and I am a sales rep,
which is a very important job.
dozens, literally dozens of small businesses would go paperless.
They'd have to write on their hands or bed sheets or who knows, you know?
Total chaos. Total chaos.
I mean, or they could get their paper somewhere else.
Stables, maybe. I don't know.
People respond to the human touch.
And that's what I give them.
I can look at a client and I can say,
hello, how are you?
How's business been going?
And we can go back and forth for some time,
and then I'll say how many reams do you want?
And they'll order it, and then I'll take care of all the sales.
I'll make sure that they get that paper.
And they appreciate that.
What's up?
I still love that after seven years.
Oh, wow.
What?
Nothing.
Okay, all right. See you later.
All right.
Take care.
Back to work.
My job is to speak to clients on the phone
about quantities and type of copy or paper.
You know, whether we can supply it to them,
whether they can...