build these levels of
Hey, yeah. Can I help you out in here?
Oh, I'm all set. Thanks.
Gotcha.
Good. I'd go with the rose.
That's a good idea.
Today is diversity day, and someone's gonna come in and talk to us about diversity.
It's something that I've been pushing, that I've been wanting to push for a long time, and corporate mandated it.
And I never actually talked to corporate about it. They kind of beat me to the punch.
Ah, no, bastards.
But, uh, but I was going to, and I think it's very important that we have this.
I'm very, very excited.
That's the thing. It's very sturdy paper, and on the back it says 100% post-consumer content.
What?
Hello? Uh-huh.
Wait, what?
I'm sorry, Mr. Deckard, I think I'm losing you.
Hello? Hello? Yeah.
Hold on one sec. I don't know. Hold on one second.
Do you really have to do that right now?
Yes, I do. I should have done this weeks ago, actually.
Mr. Deckard, I'm sorry about that.
Can you hold on one second? Yeah, just one second. Thanks.
Hello? Oh, that's it. Perfect.
So what I was saying... Hello?
Thanks, Dwight. Retaliation. Dit for tit.
That is not the expression.
Well, it should be.
This is my biggest sale of the year. They love me over there for some reason. I'm not really sure why.
But, uh, you know, I make one call over there every year just to renew their account.
And that one call ends up being, uh, 25% of my commission.
For the whole year. So, you know, I buy many bottles of champagne, celebrate a little.
And this year I'm pushing recycled paper on them for 1% more.
I know, I'm getting cocky, right?
Solitaire? Yeah, free sell.
Or 6-on-7. I know, I saw that.
So then why didn't you do it? I'm saving that, because I like it when the cards go...
Who doesn't love that?
Dude, free sell.
Solitaire is a one-player game. You can't have two players.
Well, I mean... What's your win rate?
76%. What's yours?
You're not allowed to play two-player. You need to start over.
You're doing fine.
Hey, Oscar! How you doing, man?
All right. So you have a good weekend going there?
Oh, yeah, I bet it was fun.
Oh, hey, this is Oscar.
Martinez. Right. See? I don't even know. First-name basis.
Great. We're all set.
Oh, hey, well, diversity, everybody. Let's do it.
Oscar works in here. Jim, could you wrap it up, please?
Yeah, Mr. Decker, please.
It's diversity day, Jim. I wish every day was diversity day.
Oh, I'm sorry.
You know what? I'm actually gonna have to call you back.
Thank you. Sorry about that.
Thank you. Thank you. One people, please come in.
Get in the cars! Get in the cars!
Thank you. Thank you very much.
Okay, thanks for filling these out. I promise this will be quick.
We only have about an hour.
Yeah, I would like to see us erase 100 years of racism in an hour.
Does this company have 100 years to erase this one?
No.