armor here She wants the
one support construction we
Are you listening to me, Michael?
Affirmative.
What did I just say?
You just said, let me check my notes.
You just said...
Alan and I have created an incentive program...
Hey, hey, how is Alan?
Tell Alan that the Mets suck.
Okay?
From me, big time.
Go Pirates!
Not gonna do that, Michael.
Okay.
We've created an incentive program to increase sales.
At the end of the month, you can reward your top seller with a prize worth up to $1,000.
Woo, howdy-ho.
Wow, 1,000 big ones.
That's cool.
Do I get to pick the prize?
Yes, yes, you can.
Question, does top salesmen include people who were at one time such outstanding salesmen
that they've been promoted to...
No, Michael.
No, you can't win this prize.
I didn't mean me.
Well, first what we have to do is find out what motivates people more than anything else.
Sex.
It's illegal, can't do that.
Next best thing.
Torture.
Come on, Dwight, just help me out here.
It's just stupid.
Michael?
Pam!
Hey, there's a...
Burger with cheese!
There's a person here...
And fries!
And Jake, what?
Go ahead.
There's a person here who wants to sell handbags?
No, no, no, no vendors in the office.
That is a distraction.
Okay, I told her you'd talk to her at least.
Pam, Pam, come on, I'm busy.
So just tell her to go away.
Okay.
Alright, I'll talk to her.
This one is hand-in-hand.
Alright, girls, break it up, you're being infiltrated.
Cock in the hen house.
Cock's in the hen house.
Don't say cocks.
Oh, what is your name, affair lass?
Katie.
Ah, Katie.
Wow, look at you.
You are, uh, you're like the new and improved Pam.
Pam 6.0.
Oh, look.
Oh, hey, no catfights, you two.
I'm against violence in the workplace.
So am I.
And nobody cares what you think.
Doesn't matter.
So, uh, you know what?
I usually don't allow solicitors in the office.
But today, I am going to break some rules.
And you can have the conference room.
It's yours, all day.
Wow, thanks.
There's an HR meeting in there at 11.30.
Well, let's put him in the hallway.
Give him some chairs.
Right?
Decisiveness.
One of the keys to success, according to Small Business Man.
I do.
I read Small Business Man.
I also, uh, subscribe to USA Today and American Way, um, magazine.
That's the In-Flight magazine.
Some great articles in that.
They did this great profile last month of Doris Roberts.
And where she likes to eat when she's in Phoenix.
Illuminating.
This is my conference room.
So please, uh, make yourself at home.
Whatever you need.
I'm right on the other side of this wall.
Used to be a window here.
There's not anymore.
So that's where I will be.
So, if you need anything else, something to make you more comfortable,
just don't hesitate to ask.
I'm right here.
I guess a cup of coffee would be great.
Wait a second.
Ugh, I should have spotted another addict.
Ugh, gotta love the bucks.
What?
It's like a slang for Starbucks.
They're all over the place.
Oh, man.
That place is like the promised land to me.
What a business model, too.
Oh, too bad we don't have the good stuff here.
A regular coffee is fine.
No, it's not.
It's...
No, really, it is.
No, here's the thing.
You know, I do my best to be my own man
and go by the beat of a different drummer.