beste
Hey, you ready?
Alright, alright, secret sign.
Hey, Ryan.
Very good.
Excellent, excellent.
Michael!
Today, at lunchtime, we are going to be playing the warehouse staff in a friendly little game
of basketball.
My idea.
The last time I was down there, I noticed they put up a couple of hoops.
And I play basketball every weekend, so I thought, this might be kind of fun.
And so I start messing around.
And I'm sinking a few, you know, swish, swish, swish.
Nothing but net.
And their jaws just drop to the floor.
African Americans.
So, you know, it's really just a good friendly game.
Reason for everybody to get together.
Pam, Pam, thank you, ma'am.
Messages, please.
There you go.
New pants?
Uh, yes.
Thank you for noticing.
Abercrombie and Fitch?
Uh, they look that good.
Wow.
Oh, Pam, please behave.
Mike Myers, genius.
No, actually, I got them at a fancier place.
Tarjay.
Michael, can I talk to you for a second, please?
Uh.
In your office?
I think I should be on the team.
No.
And that's not me being mean, Dwight.
That is based on your past behavior.
Oh, please.
When I let him come to my pickup game.
I apologize for that.
I vouch for you.
Michael, I-
I vouch for you in front of Todd Packer, Dwight.
I don't know what you're talking about.
I'm sorry.
All right, here's what I'm going to do.
The hand strikes and gives a flower.
You are not going to play basketball.
No.
But I need somebody to come in and take over the holiday and weekend work calendar.
I can handle that.
Good.
Excellent.
It'll be fun.
Yeah.
Because corporate wants somebody to be here on Saturday, and so we're going to have to
I have a couple people come in on the weekends and I know nobody's going to want to do it
and everybody's going to complain and bitch and I don't want to have to deal with it.
That's why you have an assistant regional manager.
Yes.
Assistant to the regional manager.
Yeah, it's the same thing.
No, it's not.
It's lower.
It's close.
What was that?
What?