And this is my little
Dunder Mifflin, this is Pam.
Hold please.
Well I see you're going for the whole board supermodel thing.
Dunder Mifflin, this is Pam. May I help you?
Smoke smoke smoke smoke.
I wasn't really going for anything.
A child is born. Beautiful sunset. Now I'll catch the next one.
Unicorn walks into the office.
Do you have an appointment?
Look, Pam, this is not meant as a criticism, but let me tell you what you're doing wrong.
You're the voice of this company, right?
And when clients call and you're not smiling, they can hear that in your voice.
It is a real turn off.
Are you being serious?
Yes, I am, absolutely.
Okay, so the next call we get, I'd like you to smile. I'd like to see a big smile.
Okay.
No one's calling.
I know. Somebody will. And we'll wait.
Sometimes there's a lot of time between the calls.
I knew, I knew. We will wait.
Okay.
We will wait for the call. And you will smile.
Let me try something. Just while we're waiting.
Okay.
Tell me if I'm smiling or not.
Hi Pam, how are you?
Was I smiling?
Yes.
Okay. Let me try this one.
Hi Pam, how are you?
No.
I mean you can tell.
Yeah, I could tell.
No, I wasn't smiling that time. And they can tell too.
That was a good example.
Thank you.
Alright. When we get a call, I'll come back and you'll do the smile.
Okay.
Dunder Mifflin, this is Pam. One moment, I'll transfer you.
Michael!
Oh God!
Dwight, come on!
I wanted to talk to you about the downsizing.
There's no downsizing.
But if there were, I'd be protected as assistant regional manager.
Assistant to the regional manager, Dwight.
Yeah, so I don't have to worry.
Look, look, look. I talked to corporate about protecting the sales staff.
And they said they couldn't guarantee it if there's downsizing. Okay?
But there's no downsizing. So just don't...
Bottom line. Do I need to be worried?
Maybe.
It looks like there's going to be downsizing.
And it's part of my job, but...
Blah!
I hate it.
I think the main difference between me and Donald Trump is that
I get no pleasure out of saying the words, you're fired.
You're fired.