I'm an early bird and I'm a night owl, so I'm wise and I have worms.
Oh.
Oh!
Breakfast.
I got your sausage, egg and cheese biscuit.
Yummy yummy.
Thank you.
Ryan.
What was the thing you needed me to come in early for?
Um, the sausage, egg and cheese biscuit.
But thank you and why don't you just take a couple hours, office is yours.
Home alone, risky business.
Take your pants off, run around.
Whatever you ought to do.
I'm just going to take a nap in my car until work starts.
Okay.
Healthier.
I'm watching those climbs.
Music.
Hey.
Morning.
Oh, Pam.
Can I see you in here for a second?
It's important, so.
Okay.
What?
What is this?
I found Dwight's wallet in the parking lot.
Oh my god, what are we going to do?
I don't know, I don't know.
I don't know what the best play is.
Do we tear everything up or do we buy a horse on the internet?
I mean, I don't know what to do.
What do you think?
I know, I know what to do.
Okay, what?
Okay, put everything back exactly how you found it.
Okay.
Hey Dwight, Jim and I found your wallet in the parking lot.
What did you do to it?
Nothing.
I'm serious.
What did you do to it?
Dwight, I swear we didn't do anything.
Nice try.
Cancel card.
I mean, you've got stuff here.
You rented Mermaids.
You can't, it's a movie, you can't do that.
You know that.
It's not an office expense.
Yes, thank you.
Next year.