Let's think this through. If we ask corporate for that, then...
They are either gonna say yes or no.
Could go either way. We don't know what they are going to say.
Think it through!
We have to think it through! Because if they say no...
Can we not?
No, yes we have to. You know why?
Because I don't like to be cooped up in that office, in that box, all day long.
Heisman! Because I need to think.
Okay, Jim? Oh, Kevin!
Nice catch.
Oscar!
Intercepted! Right here.
Give it to me.
Phil, give me the ball. Okay.
Give me the ball. You guys, the creed.
Give me the ball right now. Give it to me.
Fumble!
Alright, hey!
You alright, Ryan?
Ryan?
Yeah.
Pam!
My future is so bright, Jim.
Jim, do you know how bright my future is?
It's so bright that...
What?
Do you know?
Is there something I gotta wear?
Huh?
Goggles?
Oh, they're having a sale on TiVo.
Maybe I should get a TiVo.
Ooh, DVD burner. Maybe I should get one of those.
You are so lucky, Jim. You are so lucky.
I'm so lucky.
You are so lucky, Jim. You are so lucky you don't have this problem.
What was the ninth place prize again?
A loaf of bread?
Pagino's Pizza.
Oh, great. Tasty, terrific pizza.
Question. Do their pizzas play DVDs?
Dwight was the top salesman of the year at our company.
He wins a little prize money and gets honored at some convention.
It is literally the highest possible honor that a Northeastern Pennsylvania-based
mid-sized paper company regional salesman can attain.
What did I do to deserve this?
Are you sad that Dwight beat you?
No.
Are you gonna cry, Jim? Do you need a tissue?
Hey, I heard you got a wedding dress. Do you have pictures?
Oh, yeah. I'll show them to you later.
Oh, I should get back.
Talk to you guys later.
Okay, cool.
I have a ton of stuff to do for the wedding, and I have to do it in the office.
And that can be kind of awkward, just because people can get all weird about wedding stuff,
and I just, I don't want to offend Angela or someone.
That's what she said.
Ha! I don't get it.
Grapes? Seductive?
So, you ready for the big speech this afternoon?
Well, that's not really a big speech. You're still coming, right?
Oh, absou-fruitly. Fruit, grapes, nailed the joke. Matter of time.
And yes, it is a big speech. Biggest of your life.
Speaker at the sales convention. Been there, done that. Went there again, did it again.
Two years in a row. Consecutive.
I just, I miss the feeling of knowing that you did a good job because somebody gives you proof of it.
Sir, you're awesome. Here's a plaque.
What, a whole year has gone by and you need more proof? Here's a certificate.
They saw making plaques that year.
What if I give a really long, extended thank you, for instance.
Thank you, Mr. Blank. Thank you, very, very-
That would look terrible.
These are mostly salesmen, and salesmen expect to be entertained, and you are the main act.
When I was in the sixth grade, I was a finalist in our school's spelling bee.