Oh, I don't know Pam. I paid $400 for this phone because I like the ring.
You did?
Now I realize that you can program or download any ring you want, so I'm a little overwhelmed.
Yeah.
There's a lot of choices. You gotta help me here.
Okay.
Which one of these is coolest? What do you think?
How about that one?
No, no.
Oh, that one was good.
Are you kidding me? No. That one says I am so lame.
Know which one I want? There's one that sounds like a jackhammer.
Just really grabs your attention. It's like...
You know what I'm talking about?
Do you mean vibrate?
So, I'm happy to be here. It's very nice to see all of you. You're all looking well.
Today's a women in the workplace thing.
Jan's coming in from corporate to talk to all the women about...
I don't really know what, but Michael's not allowed in. She said that about five times.
Women today, though we have the same background, are not allowed in.
She said that about five times.
Women today, though we have the same options as men, we often face a very different set of obstacles in getting there.
Hey, what's going on?
Michael, I thought we agreed that you were...
I thought about it. I just have a few things I want to say.
What are you doing?
Just hear me out. What is more important than quality? Equality.
Now, studies show that today's woman, the Ally McBeal woman, as I call her, is at a crossroads.
Michael...
And just... You have come a long way, baby. But I just...
I just want to keep it within reason. They did this up in Albany...
You are not allowed in this session.
And they ended up turning the break room into a lactation room, which is disgusting.
Now you're really not allowed in this session.
Well, I'm their boss, so I feel like...
I'm your boss.
Anybody want any coffee or anything?
We're fine, Michael. We just need you to leave, please.
Ladies, I am so, so sorry.
Can we start again?