The Lord of the Rings trilogy, if you see it back to back, it's good.
Dunder Mifflin, this is Pam.
Pam, it's Michael. Help me. I need help right now.
Michael, what's wrong?
I'm hurt. I have hurt myself. Oh my God.
Okay, wait, wait, wait.
This is not looking good, Pam.
Michael, do you need me to call an ambulance?
No, I want you to pick me up.
Okay, wait a second. I thought you said that you were hurt.
I am hurt. I hurt my foot.
I want to come to work, but I need you to come and pick me up.
Oh God!
Hey, whoa, Michael.
It's okay. It's Jim. Just say again really loudly what happened.
Okay, I burned my foot very badly on my Foreman Grill,
and I now need someone to come and bring me into work.
You burned your foot on a Foreman Grill.
I enjoy having breakfast in bed.
I like waking up to the smell of bacon, sue me.
And since I don't have a butler, I have to do it myself.
So most nights before I go to bed,
I will lay six strips of bacon out on my George Foreman Grill.
Then I go to sleep.
When I wake up, I plug in the grill.
I go back to sleep again.
Then I wake up to the smell of crackling bacon.
It is delicious. It's good for me.
It's the perfect way to start the day.
Today I got up, I stepped onto the grill,
and it clamped down on my foot. That's it.
I don't see what's so hard to believe about that.
Can you come get me?
I have to stay here and answer the phone.
Okay, could someone come and get me, please, Ryan?
Michael, you should stay home and rest.
There's no toilet paper here. Could Ryan tell Ryan to bring toilet paper?
Could you tell him that?
Can you hop?
I tried hopping, Kevin, and I bumped my elbow against the wall,
and now my elbow has a protuberance.
No one wants to pick me up?
What is going on?
Michael is sick, and he wants one of us to rescue him.
I'm coming, Michael! I'm going to save you!
Michael is in trouble! Okay?
Hold on, Michael! I am coming! Wait there!
I got it, Dwight!
Michael, why don't you call your girlfriend?
I don't have a girlfriend.
But you said you went out this weekend.
It was all made up. Just someone come, okay?
Anyone, anyone but Dwight.
What was that?
Oh! He hit the pole!
It's broken, right? He can't...
Oh, Dwight.
Dwight.
Oh!
Oh my gosh!
Is he okay?
He's still driving.
Dwight!
You forgot your bumper!
Hello?
Please don't send Dwight.
Morning, everyone.
Don't freak out.
I forbid anybody to freak out.
Clearly, I have had a very serious accident,
but I will recover, God willing.
I just want to be treated normally today.
Normal would actually be good,
considering the trauma that I've been through.
You missed two big conference calls today, one with corporate.
Oh, did you explain why?
No, I didn't mention that you cooked your foot.
Burned my foot, Pam.
Please stop popping my cast.
Thank you.
So where are you shipping your foot?
Ha, ha, ha. So where are you shipping...
Your foot?
You should put butter on it.
Uh, that's what she said.
See, I haven't lost my sense of humor.
No, no need. It was a nonstick grill.
I've had a Foreman grill for about six years.
I've done about 85% of my cooking on it.
But I've never burnt myself.
Probably because I don't use it as a pillow.
I always keep a stash of bubble wrap in my house.
Some days, hectic, tiring days,
I just like to go home and zone out,
click on the tube, and pop a few.
Very soothing.
Want to try?
You know, that's probably not going to last too long.
You should go to a hospital and get a real cast.
Right, like I'm going to spend the day in the hospital.
Bureaucracy and germs.
And doctors.
Yes, so two days.
What?
Constructing a homemade cast?
Genius.
Filled with foresight.
Like in the pioneer times,
if you lost a leg,
they would then use the bone of the leg for a cane.
They wasted nothing.
Wow, I don't want to hear you talk.
Pam, can I have a word with you in my office?
Okay.
Oh.
All right.
Thank you.
Pam, messages please.
You didn't have any.
Really?
Well, it seemed very important to you earlier
that you needed to stay and...
Do my job?
No.
Your job is being my friend, Pam.
Ow! God!
It slipped.
Sorry.
It's just that before you said you didn't want any special treatment.
I don't want any special treatment, Pam.
I just want you to treat me like you would
a family member who's undergone
some sort of serious physical trauma.
I don't think that's too much to ask.
Do you want some aspirin because you seem a little fussy?
No, I don't want some aspirin. Yeah, I am fussy.
Aspirin's not going to do a damn thing.
I'm sitting here with a bloody stump of a foot.
Pam, I am Assistant Regional Manager
and I can take care of him.
Part of my duties are to...
What? Part of your duties are to what?
What?
You just said that part of your duties are to something.
I didn't. Yes, you did.
What is wrong with you? What is wrong with you?
Oh, who made popcorn?
Well, you know,
frankly, a lot of us have been saying
something like this for a long time.
Yeah, I've been saying that.
Yeah, and I think that
the very fact that we're including it in our agenda,
frankly, is a big step forward.
Did you know I used to be an HR?
I'm sorry? I used to be an HR.
I was a head of HR.
I used to be an HR. I was a hellraiser.
Okay.
Right.
Great. Why don't we move on?
All right. Moving on.
Great, because I think that, you know, the very fact that...
Fine. Thank God. You're here.
What you got? What you got?
All right. Panic Room, Maverick,
now Summer's BBQs.
Where's little man Kate? Hey, we're out.
In three different places. Oh, man.
It's not a Jodie Foster afternoon without little man Kate, buddy.
Okay.