Everybody hello, can I have your attention please since it's Valentine's Day. There's something that I wanted to say I
Love the women of this office Pam. I love you
Michael's got a few tricks for Valentine's Day. He found a place where you can get 12 plastic roses for $10 and
He's got a great line
Me so thorny. I love you Angela
Yes, even you I
Love you Kelly I
Love you Meredith. This is all platonically of course I
Love ladies always have
And you know what I think is the most attractive part of a woman's body
The brains because I don't think a woman is beautiful unless she is smart
And also the brains are where ladies get their best nasty ideas for bedroom stuff
I
Really like Valentine's Day in this office. It's kind of like grade school everybody gives out little presents and stuff
Like last year Jim gave me this card with Dwight's head on it. It was
horrifying and funny and
Phyllis
Just sign here
Roy and I are saving for the wedding so I made him promise not to get me anything too big
Happy Valentine's Day darling love Bob Vance Vance refrigeration
Wow, all right Dwight as you know I'm heading to New York today doing a
Presentation on the branch to the new CFO and you want me to come with you
No, the opposite of that I will stay here and run things on this end good
Question will you be seeing Jan when you're in New York? I probably will what do you ask? Well, it's Valentine's Day you guys
You know
Screwed what is your problem?
This is a business trip
I would have to be a raving lunatic to try to talk to Jan about what happened between us her words not mine
She sent me an email this morning
But it is Valentine's Day
It's New York City of love
Hey Pam you heart NY right you want me to pick you up anything that's okay
The best present would be you do a good job in front of the new CFO
Dude, I'm gonna nail it me in New York. Oh, I own that city but good about it
See ya
Well, here we go on our way to New York New York New York the city so nice they named it twice
Manhattan is the other name
So I broke up with Katie and haven't been dating anybody else. So this year I don't have to worry about Valentine's Day
It's gonna be good. I invite a couple friends over we're gonna play some cards and I'll end up winning a lot of money
Because they're idiots
It's gonna be great
What's this what is this I
Don't know what's on your desk
You but who put it here and for what purpose?
There when I sat down
Happy Valentine's Day
I
It's me I'm the bobblehead
Yes
The meeting is until 3
But I always like to come to New York a little bit early and hit some of my favorite haunts like right here
My favorite New York pizza joint
And I'm gonna go get me a New York slice
Hey Kelly, what's up?
Nothing. Oh
Except oh my god Jim last night Ryan and I totally finally hooked up. It was awesome. That's great
I'm really happy I know it was so funny because we were at this bar with his friends and I was sitting next to him the
Whole night and it wasn't making a move. So in my head I was like Ryan
Taking you so long and then he kissed me and I didn't know what to say so I said
Ryan what took you so long? I mean he just said to him. Can you believe that Wow? Oh my god, Jim. Is that embarrassing?
No, don't be no. Thank God. I was nervous Jim. You will not believe I was so nervous
But now now I have a boyfriend
I hooked up with her on February 13th
Here it is part of New York City Times Square
Named for the good times you have when you're in it
Most people when they come to New York, they go straight to the Empire State Building
That's pretty touristy. I come here great places to eat. We have bubblegum shrimp red lobster down there. You know
This is this is the heart of civilization right here
This place used to be full of hookers and porn shops and it's not that way anymore
There's an old building that one hasn't been torn down yet, but they will they'll get to it. We've got tj