GT- geographically besides the
Tonight is the Dundee's, the annual employee awards night here at Dunder Mifflin, and this
is everybody's favorite day.
Everybody looks forward to it because, you know, a lot of the people here don't get trophies
very often, like Meredith or Kevin.
I mean, who's going to give Kevin an award?
Dunkin' Donuts.
Plus, bonus, it's really, really funny.
So, you know, an employee will go home and he'll tell his neighbor, hey, did you get
Kevin an award?
And the neighbor will say, no, man, I mean, I slave all day, nobody notices me.
Next thing you know, employees smell something terrible coming from the neighbor's house.
Neighbors hanged himself due to lack of recognition.
So you ready for the Dundee's?
You know what they say about a car wreck where it's so awful you can't look away?
The Dundee's are like a car wreck that you want to look away, but you have to stare at
it because your boss is making you.
It's Fat Halpert.
What?
Fat Halpert.
Jim Halpert.
So why don't I take you on a tour of past Dundee winners?
We got Fat Jim Halpert here.
Jim, why don't you show off your Dundee's to the camera?
Oh, I can't because I keep them hidden.
I don't want to look at them and get cocky.
Oh, that's a good idea.
Minor at home in a display case above my bed.
TMI.
TMI, my friends.
TMI, too much information.
I used to say don't go there, but that is so lame now.
Or you go, girl, or...
When did Where's the Beef?
That was like a long, long time ago.
It's funny how the shelf life of these things, like how long they last.
Like too much information probably came on the scene.
I mean, I didn't hear it until like this month, so it's pretty recently.
But you know, they're generally good for like no more than five or six years.
And here we have Stanley the Manly.
Now Stanley is a Dundee all-star, aren't you saying?
Why don't you show them some of your bling?
I don't know where they are.
I think I threw them out.
Oh, no, you didn't.
I think I did.
Why did...
Say, we gotta order some more appetizers this time.
We ran out last year, remember?
Yes, we should.
You know what?
I wanted one of those skillets of cheese, but when I got off stage, someone had eaten
all of them.
Two Oscar Martinez.
It's the Show Me the Money Award.
Michael has taped every Dundee's Awards.
And now he's making me look through hours of footage to find highlights.
I think I'm gonna play for the ladies.
Hit it, Dwight.
A little bit of Pam all night long.
A little bit of Angela on the thing.
A little bit of...
This is the part where Kevin sat in front of the camcorder all night.
It's great.
A little bit of Roy eating chicken crispers.
A little bit of Tim and with some ribs.
A little bit of...
Well, what should I do, guys?
Seriously, do you want me to just cancel the Dundees?
No, we were just hoping you wouldn't do those characters like last time.
Ping?
Everybody loves Ping.
He's my most popular character.
I think many people find that character slightly racist.
Really?