Yeah, that looks good, but you want to initial one of those.
Where is my desk?
That is weird.
This is not funny. This is totally unprofessional.
Okay, well, you're the one who lost the desk.
I didn't lose my desk.
Okay, calm down. Where was the last place you saw it?
Okay, who moved my desk?
I think you should retrace your steps.
Okay, I am going to tell Michael,
and this entire office will be punished.
Colder.
Warmer.
A little warmer.
There you go. Ooh, warmer.
Warmer.
Warmer, warmer, warmer.
Cold, cold, cold. Back up.
Ooh. Ooh, warmer.
Hot. Red hot. Hot.
Very hot.
Phone ringing
Dwight Schrute.
Hi, Dwight.
What sort of discounts are we giving on the 20-pound white box?
Jim, I've given you this information like 20 times.
Right now.
It's by the ream.
Yeah, ream.
It is now $9.78.
Sorry.
It's a discount of 7%.
Okay, thank you.
Gotta get back to work.
Wash your hands, Kevin.
Right.
Oh, let me just check the pricing list.
Hold on one second.
Sensei.
Hello, it's Senpai.
Dwight.
You know what?
Let me give you a call right back.
I'm going to find it, and then I'll call you back.
Thanks.
Yes, I just had a question.
What is it?
I'm sorry.
Yes, I just had a question.
Yes, Sensei.
Arigato gozaimashita.
Hai.
Is that your mom?
No, that was my sensei.
Oh, I thought it was your mom.
I am now Senpai, which is assistant sensei.
Assistant to the sensei?
That's pretty cool.
Assistant sensei.
Okay.
I am a practitioner of Goju-Ru karate here in Scranton.
Hai.
Two.
Wait, snap your kick back.
Three.
Hai.
My sensei, Aira, recently promoted me to purple belt
and gave me the duties of a senpai.
Not that a lot of people here in America know what a senpai is,
but it's equally as respected as a sensei.
Great.
Excellent.
That's okay.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Hold on, hold on.
Sorry, just one second.
Dwight, you can't use your patron here.
I told you.
Okay, it's a sales call.
Ten push-ups.
Ten push-ups!
I can...
Yes, sensei.
Do I feel bad that I haven't bonded with the other students?
No, I'm not there to make friends.
I'm there to attack people.