Hey, there.
I'm afraid you are.
Good morning, Pam.
Good morning, Michael.
What's going on?
Nothing.
You look nice today.
Um, I don't get what you mean.
You just, um, you look good.
Your shirt. It looks...
You look real good.
Uh, well, you said I look thin, so what is...
Does that mean I'm, like, thin weird or thin handsome or...
Thin handsome, Michael.
Ah. Yes, well, of course. Of course.
Ha ha ha.
Wait, Jim. No. Don't drink directly from the can.
Okay, I'm serious. It's all over the Internet.
They use the same shipping company as rat poison, and it gets on the can.
Well, you're an idiot.
What can I say, Dwight? I live a very dangerous life.
Ow!
Hey, what's up?
Hey.
Any emails today?
Um, I don't think so.
No? Um, check your spam folder.
Oh. There it is.
What?
Um, 50 signs your priest might be Michael Jackson.
Well done. Topical.
I am king of forwards.
It's how I like to do business.
Everybody joking around.
We're like friends.
I am Chandler and Joey,
and, uh, Pam is Rachel,
and Dwight is Kramer.
So the monkey does the sex thing right here.
Ha ha ha!
That's funny. That's funny.
Not offensive, because it's nature, educational.
Do you want the link? Because then you could forward it around.
Um, I...
Can't sit around.
Maybe, maybe. Well, we'll see.
Because I don't know if it's a...
Come on!
What has two thumbs and likes to bone your mom?
This guy!
Oh, you are so bad.
Yeah!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, this guy is out of control.
He is a madman. Better get the bleep button ready for him.
Bleep, bleep!
What's up, Halpert?
Still queer?
Uh-oh! Oh!
Todd Packer and I are total BFF.
Best friends forever.
He and I came up together as salesmen.
One time we were out, and we met this set of twins,
and Packer told them that we were brothers.
And so, you know, one thing led to another,
and we brought them back to the motel.
And then Packer did both of them.
It was awesome. It was so...
Whoa, whoa, whoa! Oh, okay.
Great aggoso for you right now.
Randall, CFO, resigned. Nobody knows why.
Are you kidding? Everyone knows why.
You don't know? Oh, okay. Check this out.
So here's the story.
So Randall is nailing his secretary, right?
And she's totally incompetent.
Really? Here we go. Buckle up and go to be a bumpy one.
We're talking blonde incompetent, right?
Like ten words a minute, talking.
Well, to be fair, blondes brunettes, you know,
there are a lot of dumb people out there.
They are women, right?
Oh, wow! I didn't say it! I didn't say it!
I said it.
And then, suddenly, for no reason,
this bimbo blows the whistle on the whole thing just to be a bitch.
Oh, wow! What did I tell you about the blink button?
Hey, what has two thumbs and hates Todd Packer?
This guy.
I meant to ask you, do you think you'd get someone
to drive me around because of the DUI situation?
Oh, bad boy.
Um, Ryan.
Come on, kid. Let's go.
Oh. Man, Todd Packer can do anything.
Except pass the breathalyzer.
Yeah.
You a big William Hung fan?
Why does everybody ask me that? Who the hell is that?
Did you see that?
I saw it.
You can see her.
It's fake.
She's a senator.
I'm really excited to meet your mom.
You are?
My mom is coming in to visit.
And she lives, like, two hours away,
and she doesn't have a cell phone,
which is cool because it's kind of adding some suspense to my day.
I keep looking over at the door, hoping she'll walk in.
I'm excited to show her around.
She really wants to meet everybody.
Oh, yeah? Good. Because I have a lot of questions.