Did she get one of these?
No, thank you.
Do you even know what this is?
It is a fitness orb and it has completely changed my life.
Forget everything you thought you knew about ab workouts.
Done.
This ab workout is specifically designed to strengthen your core.
Numerous health benefits.
Strengthens your back.
Better performance in sports.
More enjoyable sex.
You're not having sex.
Plus improves your reflexes.
See how I would have caught that.
Okay, you know what?
How much is that?
It's only 25 bucks.
Wow.
Okay.
Fuck.
Oscar, I'm ready for you.
Today is performance review day company wide.
And I'm a little concerned about my review.
I exceeded my sick days and my personal days because I just couldn't take it.
And I don't have a good answer for him when he asks me.
So.
Michael, I don't know what to say.
Um, you're in accounting.
Yes, I'm in accounting and I'm sorry about all the extra days.
I know I'm past my limit.
So good, good, good.
Something to work toward.
Being here more.
I'm a big believer in people being here more.
Yes.
You know what this is?
No you don't.
Don't mind the question.
This is a visual aid for my performance review.
The budget is tight and if anyone is getting a raise it is going to be a fight to the death.
And I intend on winning that fight.
Dwight.
Determined.
Worker.
Intense.
Good worker.
Hard worker.
Terrific.
Dwight.
I want two.
Jim.
Uh, Jim.
Is Jim.
My name is Jim.
It's a total waste of your M.
Really?
Yeah.
You have a better idea?
Yeah, magnificent worker.
I like this worker.
More money for this worker.
Man, I like this worker.
Mighty worker.
That's good.
Oof.
I'll do that.
Pam, can I see you in my office?
Last year my performance review started with Michael asking me what my hopes and dreams
And it ended with him telling me he could bench press 190 pounds.
So I don't really know what to expect.
Pam, you're trustworthy.
Thank you.
And a woman.
Oh no.
And I want you to listen to a voicemail from my boss.
Michael, it's Jim.
I guess I missed you.
I'll be there this afternoon for performance reviews.
I hope it's understood that that will be our only topic of discussion.
See you soon.
Person.