What?
Oh, nothing.
Pam's on vacation and she gets back tomorrow, so it'll be nice to see her.
It'll be nice. And she set a date for the wedding with Roy.
June. Summer. So that'll be nice.
And that's that.
What?
Oh, nothing.
Jim's been looking at me kind of a lot all week.
I would be creeped out by it, but it's nothing compared to the way Michael looks at me.
MUSIC
Spamster.
Pam plus Spam plus...
Hamster.
Right.
Welcome back. How was your vacation?
It was great.
Yeah?
Mm-hmm.
Did you get lucky?
Boink.
Roy and I just got back from the Poconos.
I get ten vacation days a year, and I try to hold off taking them for as long as possible.
And this year I got to the third week in January.
I am Pam.
Spicoli guy.
Oh, God.
Need some helpers. Okay.
Whoa! God! Yuck! Yuck! Yuck! Yuck!
What?
Wow! What happened in there?
I don't know.
There was stink in there. My God.
What is that?
Oh, I don't know.
Is that a bird?
I don't think it's a bird.
Oh, God. How could that happen? How could...
Right in the middle of the carpet.
What's going on?
Somebody vomited right in the middle of the carpet in my office.
I don't think that's vomit.
Check it out.
Me?
It would be a wuss just getting out and not pulling your coffee.
Tell me what it is.
Oh, that's rude.
What is it?
Michael.
What is it? No! Just tell me what it is.
Michael, I got to get out of here. I can't hold my breath that long.
Open the door up.
It smelled terrible.
Oh, no.
I cannot believe a pipe burst and left that there.
There's no burst pipe.
How do you know that? What is it, then?
Hey, guys.
Somebody making soup?
Here she comes. All clean?
Great.
Still stinky.
It's worse.
She probably scrubbed it in the toilet.
Gosh, she probably scrubbed it into the fibers of the carpet.
Total permeation.
I am a big Fear Factor fan.
I'm a big fan of anything Joe Rogan does, actually.
So this is sort of like my audition tape.
I can't stand it.
I can't stay in here another second.
Hey. Welcome back.
Thanks.
So, how was the resort? Did you ski a lot?
A little.
Good.
What's going on here?
What?
I did not do that.
That sounds disgusting.
It wasn't me.
It was not me.
Oh.
Wow.
Hey.
Hey, Jim. I thought that we would be desk buddies while they change my carpet.
That might be a little difficult with the one computer.
Oh.
There's definitely a desk open in the back.
Yeah.
Which I guess I'll be taking.
No, no, no. Seriously, I don't mind sharing.
No, no, no. Seriously. I'll be in the back.
Hey, Kelly.
Are you moving back here?