It is Friday morning and it is another beautiful day in Scranton, Pennsylvania.
Oh my god.
Pick up, pick up, pick up, pick up.
We have a serious problem here.
Alright everybody, lock the doors, turn off the lights, pretend you're not here.
Are we in danger?
There's no time to think about if this is real.
Just...shh. Everybody...
Michael, should I call the...what?
The IT tech guy and me did not get off to a great start.
Yeah, I tried to install it myself, but you guys have these things so password protected.
That just means you have to enter your password.
What's your password, Michael?
Um...
Oh, that's...
One, two, three, four.
Yes.
Do you have a question or something?
About my turban maybe?
Nope.
No, I actually wear a turban sometimes.
I don't know.
I actually wear a turban sometimes.
You want to see it?
Got it.
Yaw.
Why do you have that?
Comedy.
It's funny.
It's Johnny Carson.
Karnak.
So...
Did you have Johnny Carson in your land?
In Pittsburgh?
Yeah, but
I never really watched him.
Oh, you are forbidden.
No.
I'm much younger than you.
I watched Conan.
All right.
I'm gonna...
I'm gonna get a cup of coffee.
Coffee or some tea or hummus or something?
No, thank you.
Oh, God!
Please don't do that.
Sorry. What is going on in there?
Why is he here?
What are you doing?
I can't tell you.
I don't have to tell you anything.
Look, Michael, I know you don't want to have to think about this,
but if something were to happen to you,
if you were to be forbidden, then I would need to know in order to take over.
Dwight, nothing is gonna happen to me, okay?
I'm in the best shape of my life.
Look at this.
Yeah, but that doesn't matter. You could get a brain aneurysm.
Or hit by a car. Or a bus. Or a train.
Or get poisoned. Fall down a well.
Step on a mine. Choke.
Oh, okay. If I step on a mine in Scranton, Pennsylvania and die,
you can have my job, okay?
Why don't you just go away?
There are certain things a boss does not share with his employees.
His salary.
That would depress them.
His bed.
And I am not going to tell them that I'll be reading their emails.
So how do you search by keyword phrase?
Try profits.
No, try Michael Scott.
Michael, boss, and funny.
Oh my god.
Wow.
I got an email from Stanley.
Stanley. Terribly nice guy.
Sorry I didn't write back sooner.
I can't go to the game tonight because my boss, Michael, is an ass
and making me stay late.
Well, Stanley's an ass.
Not one of our harder workers.