Happy Halloween, everyone.
No, that's great.
Hey. Happy Halloween.
Jan called.
Oh, okay.
I know why she is calling.
It's the end of the month,
and I was supposed to let somebody go
by the end of the month.
And I'm not gonna let you.
I'm not gonna let you.
And somehow I'm supposed to put on a costume and smile.
Okay.
Jan Levinson's office.
Hey, Sherry. Michael Scott returning.
Oh, she's in a meeting.
She just wanted the name of the employee you let go.
Well, I'm gonna wait till the end of the day,
because the book said it's best to wait until the end of the day.
I just need the name of who you're planning to let go.
I don't know yet.
I will have to call her back.
I know she wanted the name.
Okay. Sherry?
Yeah?
If you were getting fired,
how would you want to be told
so that you could still be friends with the person firing you?
Jan wants the name as soon as possible, Michael.
Thanks.
I'll call her back.
I wish I could fire Sherry.
Hey, I'm still here.
Okay. I'm sorry. Yeah.
Bye.
Hey, you.
Big Jim.
And Phyllis.
Working hard, Phyllis?
Of course. You're always working hard.
Keep it up.
I'm gonna go get some water.
Okay.
Hey, you.
Working hard.
Keep it up.
And there's Stanley.
No costume?
Well, no. Not trying to fit in.
I wish I had your confidence. I really do.
Something wrong, Michael?
No. No. What could possibly be wrong?
Everything's great.
Just keep living your lives.
Everything's gonna be fine.
Oh.
You are all such...
wonderful, innocent people.
I mean, you hear about layoffs in the news,
but when you actually have to do it yourself,
it is heavy stuff.
It's...
I mean, these are people's lives you're talking about.
You want me?
Yes.
Paper mache?
Yes. Yesh.
Um...
Pam, I have to let somebody go today.
This is, uh,
the hardest thing I've ever had to do.
Why did you put it off until Halloween?
Because it's very scary stuff.
I think it's gonna put a damper on the party a little.
You're worried about the party?
There's a man's life at stake here.
So it's a man?
No. Poor woman.
A human life.
If you had to guess who it would be
based on their job performance
and who you think deserves to be fired,
who would that be?
I just answer the phone.
And sometimes you just let it go to voicemail.
Your costume is fantastic.
I know.
I set away for it in July from a catalog.
Oh, no, don't, don't, don't, don't.
Ah!
Okay.
Oh, man.
Okay, I have to fire somebody.
What is that? What are you supposed to be?
I'm a three-hole punch version of Jim.
Because he can have me either way.
Plain white Jim or three-hole punch.
That's great.
Yeah.
Yeah, well, look, what about me?
Hold on.
What are you?
A monk?
I'm a Sith Lord.
Big deal.
Three round pieces of paper
taped to his shirt.
This cost me $129.