Kevin Malone, you're next. Spit that out.
Spit... Okay, come on. Let's go.
Phone ringing
You look cute today, Dwight.
Thanks, girl.
So, yesterday, Dwight found half a joint in the parking lot.
Which is unfortunate because, as it turns out, Dwight finding drugs
is more dangerous than most people using drugs.
Let's go over some of the symptoms of marijuana use, shall we?
You tell me who this sounds like.
Slow moving.
Inattentive.
Dull.
Constantly snacking.
Shows a lack of motivation.
Hey...
I like the people I work with, generally.
With four exceptions.
Someone committed a crime.
And I did not become a Lackawanna County volunteer sheriff's deputy to make friends.
And by the way, I haven't.
I enjoy the tangy zip of Miracle Whip.
Ah!
Jim does the best impressions.
Sometimes he'll look up at me from his desk and he'll just be someone else.
Like, he'll go, um...
I'm sorry.
That's supposed to be Phyllis.
I can't do it as good as he can.
Nice.
Kevin.
Do someone else.
Um...
Angela.
Whoa.
The eyebrow.
Yeah.
Oh, sure. I can definitely help you with that.
Okay? Please hold.
Kelly Kapoor!
Say your prayers.
Let's go.
Conference room, pronto.
Come on, step it up.
And the guys are saying, chug, chug, chug.
But I'm so small and all I'd eat in that day was one of those anti-m pretzels from the food court.
So I said, is it okay if I sip it?
And they said no, but Ryan seemed cool either way.
Stop!
This is not Kelly Kapoor's story hour.
Illegal drugs were consumed on company property.
Okay? Your ass is on the line, mister!
My ass is on the line!
Now I'm gonna ask you again.
What time did you go home last night?
Six.
I didn't know that you were at a party on Saturday night.
I go to a lot of parties.
Okay, I'm gonna need to search your car. Give me your keys.
I am not giving you my keys.
You make me do this the hard way.
What's the hard way?
I go down to the police station on my lunch break.
I tell a police officer, I know several, what I suspect you may have in your car.
He requests a hearing from a judge and obtains a search warrant.
Once he has said warrant, he will drive over here and make you give him the keys to your car.
And you will have to obey him.
Yeah, let's do it that way.
Ryan, is he bugging you?
Dwight, dude, you gotta take a chill pill, man.
It was one joint in the parking lot.
You know, you're totally harshing the office mellow.
I can't stop this investigation. It is my job.
Whoa, you are a volunteer.
I volunteered for this job.
And that's not the same.
It is my duty.
Volunteer duty.
To investigate the crime scene.
I have six more interviews to go and then I will reveal what I know.
Narc!
If you're attempting to compliment me, then you have done a very good job.
I wasn't attempting to compliment you.
Because being a narc is one of the hardest jobs that you can have.
Okay.
And I am very proud of being a narc.
Why don't you just cool it, cool it? Dwight, please? God.
Dude, where's my office?
I totally lost it.
Because I was half-baked.
Smoking doobies.
Dooby brothers. I was smoking doobies with my brothers.
Peace out.
Seacrest.
Well, your office is behind you.
Thanks.
Munchies.
Who wants some munchies?
I don't think Michael's ever done drugs.
I don't know if anyone's ever offered him any.
Michael's behavior is erratic and unpredictable.
But I don't think he's doing drugs.
Maybe he should.
Pick the edge off.
Uh, not at work, of course.
Oscar visited Mexico when he was five to attend his great-grandmother's funeral.
What does that mean to a United States law enforcement officer?
He's a potential drug mule.
Have you ever taken any illegal drugs?
No, I have not.
Do you think it's possible that maybe you could have had some drugs in your system without you knowing about it?
What are you implying?
Have you ever...
pooped...
a balloon?
Okay.
I'm done with this.
He sure left in a hurry.
I don't want to blow this.
This is what all good law enforcement officers dream of.
The chance to solve an actual crime.
Do you know what this is?
Yes, it's marijuana.
How do you know that?
It's labeled.
Dammit.
He asked if you've been acting.