Nothing much. What's up with you?
I cannot believe I fell for that.
Oh my gosh.
Haha. What?
What? Where's the funny?
Give it to me.
Um...
Is it me or does it smell like Up Dog in here?
What's Up Dog?
Nothing much. What's up with you?
Oh wow.
I walked right into that.
Oh, that's brilliant.
Hey Stanley, is that jacket made of Up Dog?
I'm on the phone.
Mmm.
What flavor coffee is that? Up Dog?
What's that?
I don't know. Nothing. What's up with you?
Huh?
What does that mean?
What does what mean?
The thing you just said.
Dwight!
Hey, is it me or does this place smell like Up Dog?
What's Up Dog?
Gotcha!
Oh god.
Crap.
Nothing.
How are you doing?
Good. How are you doing?
Mmm.
Damn it.
Hello.
Buy me one of Cracker?
Cracker? Cracker?
No thanks. You got a package.
Ooh, Pam with the dirty talk.
And he's lining it up.
Seems pretty straight forward from here.
If Michael Scott sings it,
he'll win a Buick signed by Tiger Woods.
Oh!
Oh, he totally misses!
No, he meant to put it right next to the hole.
That's much harder to do.
Interception!
He shoots, he scores!
Michael, try it like this.
This would be much harder.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. I don't want to chip my mug.
Please get that off the floor.
Alright.
Jack Nicholson for bidet.
Jack Nicholson.
It's a celebrity tournament.
I got it.
No problem.
Oh man, it's really bad there.
Yeah.
Do you feel it?
God damn it, Dwight!
That's great.
Should I clean out my desk?
That won't be necessary.
Today is spring cleaning day here at Dunder Mifflin.
And yes, I know it's January.
I am not an idiot.
But if you do spring cleaning in January,
guess what you don't have to do in the spring?
Anything.
They say a cluttered desk means a cluttered mind.
Well, I say an empty desk means an empty mind.
No, that's not what I was going to say.
Don't be fooled by the phrase, dust bunnies.
They are vicious little bitches.
And if they get inside your disk drive,
God help you, they will bring your computer to its knees.
They sit in corners of the room,
and they're not going to get out of the room.
They're going to get out of the room.
They sit in corners,
hatching, defecating, laying eggs.
And their sole purpose in life is to eat dead skin,
which humans in this office shed by the boatload.
especially Creed.
Look at them all out there.
My little worker bees buzzing away.
If they're the worker bees, you're the queen bee.
No, I am the king bee.
Queen's higher?
No, king is higher than ace.
I am the ace bee.
I am the queen bee.
Meredith, men's room.
Make sure you replace the urinal cakes.
They're worn down.
Kevin, file drawers.
Angela, kitchen.
Oscar, dusting.
Where is Oscar?
He's out sick.
That is unacceptable.
I agree, it's unacceptable.
What are you guys doing?
People magazine crossword puzzle.
Keep or toss?
Keep. I will finish out later.
It's from 99?
Yeah, I know what it's from Ryan.
18 across.
Mary, Kate, and Ashley blank.
Michael wrote?
Judd?
Michael wrote.
Michael wrote?
Judd?
Michael. Yes.
Oscar is out sick.
On a Friday?
Can I do some of the talking?
I will do the talking.
What difference does it make whether you're here?
Hello? Hi, Oscar, it's Michael.
And Dwight.
Yeah, um, heard you were under the weather.
Yeah, I think I came down with the flu.
Really? Oh, that is a shame.
You know, it's cleaning day here today.