Hey, are they left for the big meeting yet?
I got Michael's lucky tie.
No, they're in the conference room.
Okay.
Wait, are those Michael's Levi's?
Yeah, who dry cleans jeans?
Michael and his jeans.
He gets in them and I'm not exactly sure what happens,
but I can tell you he loves the way he looks in those jeans.
I know that's why he started Casual Fridays.
I'll take those.
Thanks.
MUSIC
Have you ever heard of Dr. David Friendly?
Dr. David Friendly's egg yolk diet.
It's kind of unique.
My diet the last couple of months has consisted mostly of egg yolks and cottage cheese.
Well, you don't just have the egg yolks, it's not like a rocky thing.
You do hard-boiled eggs.
I got one of those melon ballers.
It's like a little ice cream scoop.
I just scoop out the middle of the egg and just pop it in my mouth.
I don't even use a plate anymore.
The first couple weeks I did.
But you know what?
Boom, I keep a melon baller at my desk.
So if I have a hard-boiled egg...
I know, but you know what?
It's perfect.
I know it sounds ridiculous.
It sounds ridiculous, but you know what?
Dr. David Friendly.
He came up with this thing.
The guy, he was like, I think he was like 400 pounds when he started.
And he started with this.
The melon baller was my idea.
Most of that is good.
Not today, Kevin.
I cannot be around cars today.
You know what one loaf of bread would do to my abs?
I'm almost there, so we should have plenty of time to go over the presentation.
And excuse me, I've also confirmed the meeting this afternoon at 4 p.m.
Conflict.
What?
I have a conflict with that.
What do you mean?
I have a pajama party at the Playboy Mansion with the bunnies.
Michael, I need you to take this seriously.
I can't get out of it.
Michael, are you hearing me?
I'm hearing you.
Meeting confirmed.
This is a very important meeting.
Would you like your confirmation number?
Please grab a pen, because I will only be repeating this once.
I'll see you in ten minutes.
42897.
Okay.
What is a closer?
A closer is a sales term for someone who always gets the job done.
And that is me.
A, B, C. Always B, closing.
Glen Gary, Glen Ross.
Hey, give me the Glen Ross leads.
No way.
They're just for closers.
Do you know who you're talking to?
I'm Michael Scott.
Really?
Well, take any lead you want.
No, thanks.
I don't need them.
Because I have a client list right here on my computer.
So, suck on that.
Hey.
Hi.
What are you doing?
I don't know.
I think I was just staring at my desk.
Really?
Do you want to get back to that?
I could go.
I should go.
Yeah.
Do you mind leaving?
Not at all.
It's very important.
Mm-hmm.
Thank you.
Sure.
This is a projection of the county's needs.
Wow.
Looks like USA Today.
13 schools, 2 hospitals.
So, this possible client they're talking about, actually a big deal.
It's Lackawanna County, our whole county.
And if we get this, they might not have to downsize our branch.
I mean, a branch doesn't necessarily mean a whole state.
It's a whole state.
The whole state of Lackawanna County.
I think it's a pretty big, it's a whole state.
If they get this, they might not have to downsize our branch.
And I could work here for years.
Years.
So when we get to the Radisson, I'd like to...
Oh, I changed it to Chili's.
Excuse me?
Radisson just gives out this vibe.
It's like, oh, I'm doing business at the Radisson.
It's kind of snooty.
You had no right to do that, Michael.
Here's the thing.
Chili's is the new golf course.
It's where business happens.
Small businessman magazine.
It said that.
It will. I sent it in.
Let it to the editor.
All right.
But you will let me run this meeting.
Mm-hmm. Power trip.
What?
She had done a background check on me.
She had it printed out.
No. Yeah.