What is this? What happened here?
I don't know.
Oh, this does not look good.
Did anyone see what happened around my desk area this morning?
Dwight, I really think someone's probably just playing a prank on you, so just go right through it.
A prank, huh?
This is official police line tape, okay?
It's not a prank.
Probably is.
Damn it, people! Someone must have seen something!
Oh, you people are useless. Jesus.
Thunder Mifflin, this is Pam.
Hold, please.
Dwight, it's the sheriff.
He said that it's really important it's regarding your desk.
I'll transfer.
Oh, no, no, don't!
I can't...
Just cut through it, man. It's no big deal.
This is why I am a volunteer sheriff's deputy and you are not.
Not what?
Wow, man, he really wants to get in touch with you. Maybe it's a murder.
No, there's no blood.
Maybe poison? Possibly. My God!
No, Jim, no!
Sheriff!
This is volunteer sheriff's deputy Dwight Schrute.
Press the pound key!
Have you found a band yet for your wedding?
No.
Because I'm in a band.
We really rock.
Yeah, I mean, it's inevitable. I definitely overhear some wedding preparation, but I'm fine with it.
She hears me arranging my social life
and we both have to hear Dwight order deer urine over the internet.
So it evens out.
Oh, I got the save-the-date. Yeah? Yeah, pretty stationery. Oh, thanks.
I didn't get mine yet.
There are a few people I decided not to invite.
And that might make things kind of awkward, but
it's my wedding.
And I don't want anyone there who has called me a hussy.
Nothing much is happening today.
We are having photo IDs taken. Whoop-de-doo.
Can't always be like the apprentice.
I know. I'm a big brother.
Something important happens every day.
But real life is not like that.
Okay, here we go. One, two...
He sometimes wears glasses. Write that down.
Also, that may not be his real hair.
No, wait.
Yeah.
On or off?
Off.
Okay.
Oh. What is on your face?
Is that a disguise?
Excuse me.
Clown paint.
I'm the one who petitioned the office park to have these ID badges taken.
So there were no death threats?
Let me see your ID.
ID badges are long overdue.
Security in this office park is a joke.
Last year I came to work with my spud gun in a duffel bag.
I sat at my desk all day with a rifle that shoots potatoes at 60 pounds per square inch.
Can you imagine if I was deranged?
That's not bad.
Hey, do you do weddings?
Would you seriously want your wedding photos to look like that?
Not bad.
I gave her a higher clearance than you.
What does level red mean?
I'd tell you, but I'd have to kill you.
Ha ha ha ha!
That's a nice tie.
Thank you.
That is... who makes that?
I don't know.
Do you mind if I wear that for the photo?
Let's keep our clothes.
It's like child abuse.
I say if Jesus saw that, he'd freak out.
He'd freak out, Toby.
I mean, in so many levels.
And I'm supposed to work there.
What's the dealio?
Just sledding Oscar Venn a little.
We would use the break room.
The photographer's back there.
What's the problem?
Angela.
There's just a little dispute over a poster in their workspace.
Since Christmas.
So what, you're having a little spat?
I forget, are you guys dating?
No.
Michael, can I talk to you for a second, please?
Here's how I usually handle this.
All I do is listen.
These things just have a way of working themselves out.
It's like if you write someone a letter when you're really angry
and they say to keep it in your drawer for a couple of days,
and then you just never end up sending it.
What do you know about conflict resolution?
Your answer to everything is to get divorced.
So...
Okay, okay, well...
That was the right decision for me, my man.
Well, that's not gonna fly here, because in this office,
it is still death through its part.
Assuming that we don't get downsized.
Pam?
Would you get Angela and meet us in the conference room, please?
A mediator's tool chest.
Okay, well, before we get started,
you should know that there are five different styles of conflict.
My Shaolin Temple style defeats your monkey style.
Can we go? I have a lot of work to do.
Nope, this is important.
Okay, the first style is lose-lose.
What's the next one?
Just hold on, please.
Okay, if we do lose-lose, neither of you gets what you want.
Do you understand?
You...
You would both lose.
Now, I need to ask you,
do you want to pursue a lose-lose negotiation?
Can we just skip to whatever number five is, win-win or whatever?
Win-win is number four, and number five is win-win-win.
The important difference here is, with win-win-win, we all win.
Me, too.
I win for having successfully mediated a conflict at work.
Okay, so this is the disputed poster.
Now, one at a time, I want you to express your feelings
using I emotion language and no judging or you statements.
I got this poster for Christmas, and I feel I want to see it every day.
It makes me feel like the babies are the true artists,
and God has a really cute sense of humor.
Come on, seriously, that?
I don't like looking at it.
It's creepy and in bad taste, and it's just offensive to me.
It makes me think of the horrible frigid stage mothers
who forced the babies into it.
It's kitsch, it's the opposite of art.
It destroys art, it destroys souls.
This is so much more offensive to me than hardcore porn.
Okay, okay, okay, stop, stop, stop.
Let's see if we can't just brainstorm
and find some creative alternatives that are win-win.
Win.
Yes, thank you, Pam.
How about Angela makes the poster into a T-shirt?