Everybody in the conference room now, please. Thank you.
Time is money.
Do you need anything?
No.
Should I get water or donuts?
Come on, let's go. Take a seat.
What's going on, Michael?
I want somebody to give me the name of one of our biggest competitors.
Office Depot.
Good. Yes, that will work.
Alright, now I need a plural noun.
Apparently Michael has come up with a Dunder Mifflin madlib, and he's making us play it with him.
We are so happy.
No, I'd like to choose a different adjective.
How about a location?
The planet Capricum.
Where the hell is that?
It's from Battle Circle, Capricum.
Okay, alright.
I am going back to my desk now.
No, no, no, not until you give me an adjective.
Annoying.
We already have that, so...
Frustrating.
No, Toby, damn it, come on. We already have that. I need something fun.
Something like fat or smelly or pukey.
Pukey.
Pukey's good.
Okay.
Pukey.
Now I need a noun.
Ass.
Good.
Thank you, Phyllis. That wasn't so hard.
Alright, here we go.
Office Depot is an annoying store.
One day, Creed went there to buy paper.
And he ran into irritating silos.
Yeah, get him, Creed.
One of them was named Michael Scott.
And he was an...
Oh, damn it. Okay.
Okay, okay, we're... Okay, we're starting over.
Tonight, the Scranton Business Park is having casino night.
And we are converting our warehouse into a full-blown gambling hall.
And I know that the only way to get there is to buy paper.
But, I think, if you're going to get paper, you need to have a good
casino night.
And we are converting our warehouse into a full-blown gambling hall.
And I know it's illegal in Pennsylvania, but it's for charity.
And I consider myself a great philanderer.
It's just, it's nice to know, at the end of the day, I can look in the mirror and say,
Michael, because of you, some little kid in the Congo has a belly full of rice this evening.
Just... makes you feel good.
Excuse me, how long is it that you wait for a table for two?
I would never, ever serve you. Not in a million billion years.
It's a nice tux.
I know. It belonged to my grandfather.
He was buried in it, so... family heirloom.
So what's the deal? We gotta pay for our own drinks? That's lame.
Come on, it'll be fun. And besides, I'm a roulette expert.
Impossible. Roulette is not a game of skill, it is a game of chance.
I could always kind of win at roulette.
Oh, really? How would you do that?
Mind control.
You can't be serious.
Are you serious?
Ever since I was a little kid, like eight or nine, I could sort of control things with my mind.
I don't believe you. Continue.
It was just little things, you know? Like I could make something shake, or I could make a marble fall off the counter.
You know, just little things.
That's ridiculous.
You know what? Uh, why don't you move that coat rack?
Excuse me, everyone. Attention in the office, please.
Jim is about to prove his telekinetic powers, and he needs absolute silence.
Go ahead.
Okay, I'll try.
Oh my god.
I try not to think of it as lagging behind. It's more of a David and Goliath thing.
Well, the fact of the matter is that your branch is currently number four of the five branches that I oversee.
Top 80 percent.
Michael?
Yep?
You know that I'm very serious here.
Jan, listen, I promise I will kick it up a notch. Bam!
What?
Emeril. Oh, actually, while I have you, not that I have you or have ever had you, but we're having our casino night tonight, and I think everyone would love to see their fearless leader here.
I thought that you were their fearless leader.
I am, but you are the Eva Perone to my Cesar Chavez.
Oh, come on. Come on. It'd be fun. I can hear it in your voice. You need a break.
Goodbye, Michael.
Jan and I understand each other. The romancing is sort of on hold for the time being, but we remain good friends. Good friends with privileges. Not now, someday.
I don't believe that Jim moved that coat rack.
But if he did, he has an obligation to use his gift wisely. With great power comes great responsibility. They could do a cross-section of his brain to find out more, but I don't think it's true, though.
Okay, everybody. Tonight's event is to benefit the Boy Scouts of America.
Again. We do that every year.
Well, they need our money. They don't have cookies like the Girl Scouts.
It'd be nice to do something for people who are actually suffering.
Well, Oscar, if you don't like it, then you should concentrate on winning, because the person at the end of the evening with the highest chip can't even get a good shot.