Go! With the door!
Push! Push!
No, no, no! Turn around!
You break it, shove it through!
You shove it! Shove it back!
Here we go!
Don't break the branches, Dwight.
Ah! I got a splinter!
Well, suck it up. We all have problems.
Hey everybody! Look what we have!
Ha ha ha! Nice, huh?
I've got it leveraged. Push! Straight up!
One, two, three!
Merry Christmas!
Did it work?
Well, sort of.
Why did you get it so big?
Eh, that's what she said.
I'm not sure.
A, that's what she said.
And B, I wanted it to be impressive.
Biggest day of the year, deserves the biggest tree of the year.
But what are we going to do with this hacked off part?
Well, that is a perfectly good mini tree, Kevin.
And we are going to sell that to charity.
That's what Christmas is all about.
So this year, for the first time ever,
I got Pam in Secret Santa.
And I got her this teapot.
Which I know she really wants.
So she can make tea at her desk.
But I'm also going to stuff it with some inside jokes.
Like, this is my high school yearbook photo.
She saw it at the party.
And it really makes her laugh.
Not sure why.
What else?
This is a hot sauce packet.
She put this on a hot dog a couple years ago.
Because she thought it was ketchup.
And it was really funny.
So I kept the other two.
This would take a little too long to explain.
So I won't.
And this is a card.
Because Christmas is the time to tell people how you feel.
Is there anything we're missing?
Phyllis, you got the lights?
Yes, I got those cute little ones.
Do you think I should have gotten the big ones?
We'll see.
Angela drafted me into the party planning committee.
Her memo said that we need to prepare for every possible disaster.
Which to me seems excessive.
Merry Christmas!
Ho, ho, ho! Pimp!
I'm kidding!
What do we got? What do we got?
How many plates are we getting?
Fifteen. Double it. Double everything.
Double ice cream, double napkins. Double it.
It was a tough year.
I had to fire somebody this year.
This party has to really rock.
Check it out.
Christmas bonus. 3000 Gs.
I got this for helping save the company money.
So I guess I'm good came out of firing Devin after all.
Maybe I should call him.
Tell him that.
I want people to cut loose.
I want people making out in closets.
I want people hanging from the ceilings.
I want it to be a playboy mansion party.
And also I want you to know and spread the word that I will have my digital camera.
And I'll be taking pictures all along the way.
And the best and craziest thing that happens will be on the cover of the newsletter.
Incentive.
You do realize that we can't serve liquor at the party.
Yeah, I know. Damn it.
Stupid corporate wet blankets.
Like booze ever killed anybody.
One, two, three.
You guys should use a hand truck.
Do we have one?
No.
Will you help me?
Towards me.
That's good. Towards me.
Towards me. Okay, I'm good.
I'm good.
Creed.