Hey.
Hello.
Jim?
What's up, buddy?
This is not funny.
Why is my stuff in here?
Wow, that's weird.
Ooh, a dollar for a stapler.
That's pretty good.
Yeah, well, I'm not paying for my own stuff.
Okay, I know you did this because you're friends with the vending machine guy.
Who, Steve?
Yeah, Steve.
What do I want?
Ooh, pencil cup.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no.
That's my pencil cup.
Um, I don't think so.
I just thought you were going to say something about a pencil cup.
I don't know.
I'm just going to say that I'm going to say that I'm going to say that I'm going to say
Ooh, pencil cup.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no.
That's my pencil cup.
Um, I don't think so.
I just bought it.
Uh, I think so, and you're going to hand it over to me.
I love these.
Okay, fine.
My wallet.
Oh, there it is.
J1.
Here, you know what?
I don't have any.
Give me that.
Some nickels.
Five, ten, fifteen, twenty, twenty-five.
Hello, everyone.
Morning, Michael.
Where are we going this afternoon?
Nah.
Last week, Michael sent out this mysterious memo.
It's time for our first quarter camaraderie event.
So pack a swimsuit, a toothbrush, rubber-soled shoes, and a ski mask.
A ski mask and a swimsuit.
So that he can have us rob a bank and then escape through the sewers.
And brush our teeth.
Are you all packed?
Yes, I brought my tuffel bag and a sleeping bag just in case.
Where do you guys think we're going?
Definitely someplace we can swim.
Right?
Yeah, Florida.
Did you hear something?
Yeah?
Michael.
Stanley, Bo Manley.
I need to know.
Banana fan or faux fanley?
What we're doing.
Me and my mom, manley.
You said bring a toothbrush.
Stanley.
Is this an overnight?
Maybe.
The suspense is just so exciting, isn't it?
Should my wife tell her boss she's not coming in tomorrow?
Maybe.
I don't know.
Not maybe.
Yes or no?
Well, no.
Don't spoil it for everybody, all right?
But we are going on a booze cruise on Lake Walla Popac.
In January.
It's cheaper.
This is not just another party.
This is a leadership training exercise.
Right?
I'm going to combine elements of fun and motivation and education into a single,
mind-blowing experience.
Yeah?
Hello, Michael.
Hello.
Can we come in?
Of course.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Thank you very much.
Have a seat.
Oh, every man's dream.
Oh, really?
A surprise visit from his boss?
Two ladies at once.
What?
Why are you looking at me like that?
Okay.
You heard something.
Yeah, it's a booze cruise, but there's more to the story than that.
A booze cruise?
What do you mean?
Leadership off-site.
Booze cruise is just a rhyme.
Michael, we discussed the IRS has regulations.
Yeah, I don't even know why I said booze cruise.
This event has to have legitimate business content to be tax-deductible.
Of course.
We discussed that.
Yes, yes.
Look, I have a whole program planned.
Jan, this program is going to change people's lives.
I am going to be dropping serious knowledge all over the boat.
Good.
This is Brenda Matlow from Corporate Training.
Hello.
I thought that she could attend tonight, and if your event is appropriate,
you could give it to other branches.
Oh, cool.
Cool.
And maybe you could attend tonight, and then you could stay over at my house for the night.
Awkward.
That's... you know what, Brenda?
Could Jan and I have a moment alone?
Jan said if you asked me that, I was supposed to say no.
Really?
You seriously said that?
Okay, Brenda, could Jan and I have a moment alone?
Sure.
Brenda.
Thanks.
I mean, no.
Okay, you know, I'm going to go now, and...
Okay.
Good luck, Brenda.
See you later.
Okay.
Try to...
I'll call you later.
...be professional.
No, it's all right.
You call me if you need anything, Brenda.
I'll call you too.
So, you are probably going to get carted.
So, I can make you a fake ID.
We have a laminating machine.
It is now time to unveil the destination of this year's retreat.
We are going on a harbor cruise of Lake Wallem-Palpac.
It's a booze cruise.
All right.
I have a test for business school tomorrow night.
Is it okay if I skip the cruise and study for that?
No.
This is mandatory.
But don't worry.
You know what?
You're going to learn plenty.
This is going to turn your life around, Ryan.
I'm already in business school.
Well...
Wait, Michael.
Yeah?
Why did you tell us to bring a bathing suit?
To throw you off the scent.
Yeah, but I bought a bathing suit.
Well, just keep the tags on and you can return it.
I took the tags off already.
Well, that's not my fault, okay?
Just, we're not going to pay for a bathing suit.
Okay, I know what you're all thinking.
I'm going to go.
Who is this smart little cookie?
Her name is Brenda something and she is from corporate.
And she is here like you to learn from what I have to say.