So, Phil recruited me to sell these cards,
and now I am recruiting you.
Who is this guy again?
Don't worry about Phil. He drives a Corvette.
He is doing just fine.
Okay.
Calling cards are the wave of the future.
These things sell themselves.
Who uses calling cards anyway?
You know what? That's a nice attitude, Ryan.
I'm just helping you invest in your future, my friend.
It sounds like a get-rich-quick scheme.
Yes! Thank you.
You will get rich quick. We all will.
Didn't you lose a lot of money on that other investment,
the one from the email?
You know what, Toby?
When the son of the deposed king of Nigeria emails you directly
asking for help, you help.
His father ran the freaking country. Okay?
Alright, so raise your hand if you want to get rich.
Alright.
No. How is this not a pyramid scheme?
Alright. Let me explain again.
Phil has recruited me and another guy.
Now, we are getting three people each.
The more people that get involved, the more people who are investing,
the more money we're all going to make.
It's not a pyramid scheme.
It is a... It's not even a scheme, per se. It's...
I have to go make a call.
I'm sorry.
Happy birthday, Michael.
Oh, what?
I said happy birthday.
Thank you. That's really nice.
Today is my B day and people around here just go crazy for it.
I don't know why.
Oh, fun fact. I share my birthday with Eva Longoria.
So, I'm a perfect icebreaker if I ever meet Terry Hatcher.
Excited?
Mm-hmm.
Everybody freaking out?
Cool. Gonna be fun. You're late.
Thank you.
But I forgive you because Dothat is my birthday.
What's up?
Hey.
Oh, happy birthday.
Ah, thank you, sir.
Michael's birthday. It's pretty fun to watch, actually.
He gets very excited and then he eats a lot of cake.
And then he runs around the office,
then he has a sugar crash in the afternoon,
and then he falls asleep.
And that's when we get our work done.
Mm-hmm.
Did you hear anything yet?
No. I'm still waiting.
Yes.
There he is, the birthday boy.
Oh, God.
Birthday hug.
No, no, no, no. New suit, please.
That suit is amazing.
Thank you very much. It is from Italy.
Actually, no. Bulgaria.
Maybe I should get one.
Good luck. One of a kind.
eBay.
Question.
May I be in charge of the party planning festivities?
Not necessary.
The party planning committee is all over.
They've been working 24-7 all day yesterday.
Excellent. On my part, I did manage to reserve the...
Don't. No.
Please don't want to spoil it for anybody.
I'll spoil the surprise.
Let's get the party started.
Let's get the party started. Not the way I taught you.
Michael's birthday is hard for me
because he gets very excited,
but he's also under a lot of pressure,
which builds up until he's ready to explode.
As his right-hand man, it's my job to release that pressure
so that he can enjoy himself, if only for a moment.
My hump, my hump, my lovely lady lump.
Check it out.
When should we bring out the cake? One or 1.30?
One's good.
1.30.
I'm sorry. Are we boring you?
Party planning committee, listen up.
Michael would like trick candles for his birthday cake,
so make that a priority.
Where do we get those?
Not my problem.
Here's a list of things that Michael would like to be surprised by.
Michael wants a stripper gram?
Yes, but he doesn't want to know when or whom.
No. This is a closed-door meeting.
Good. You know, Ryan, you don't have to get me a present.
I won't.
Good. Great.
Okay, good.
I think I'm gonna go.
Ah, no, I think you're gonna stay.
I'm sorry.
Yeah?
Michael, I have Jan on the line.
Oh, great. Put her through.
Hello, Michael.
Hey, you.
I'm returning your call. You said it was urgent.
It is urgent. I just wanted to call and wish you a happy birthday.
Well, today's not my birthday, so...
Really?
Because I thought we had the same birthday.
Happy birthday, Michael.
Thanks.
Am I on camera?
Nope.
Totally private.
And say whatever is in your heart.
You can take a five if you want.
Somebody brought in donuts for my birthday.
Happy birthday.
Thanks.
Here's the thing about bosses and employees.
A good boss will say, hey, it's my birthday. Celebrate me.
A great boss will say, hey, it's my birthday. Celebrate yourselves.
Because you are the ones who made me great.
And I am the boss.
And you are the ones who made me great.
And I will acknowledge your contributions...
...with donuts.
Man, I'm so sorry.
When did you find out?
They said the same thing.