I am actually looking forward to take your daughter to work day.
I am not great with kids, but I want to get better, because I'm getting married.
So I put out a bunch of extra candy on my desk so the kids will come talk to me.
Like the witch in Hansel and Gretel.
Bribery. Nice.
Oh, I have more.
Hey, Miss Beasley of your nasty.
Oh, Michael, you can't be nasty today.
Oh, God, is that today?
I reminded you last night.
Listen, I like kids, but this is not a kid's environment.
This is like HBO. No limits.
Who knows what I'm going to say?
Crazy stuff. And it is R rated. It is not rated G.
I am like Eddie Murphy in Raw, and they are trying to make me into Eddie Murphy and Daddy Daycare.
Both great movies, but still.
Well, I'll be in my office.
Don't you think you should say something?
They're cool.
Michael, I think that as the boss you should be...
Fine, fine, fine, fine, fine.
Hi, children. I'm Michael Scott, and I am in charge of this place.
How do I make you understand?
I'm like Superman, and the people who work here are like citizens of Gotham City.
That's Batman.
Okay, I'm Aquaman. Where does he live, guys?
The ocean.
I work with a bunch of nerds.
I think five plain and one veggie should be fine.
How about pepperoni?
No.
I like extra cheese.
Absolutely not.
I like extra cheese, too.
Fine. The first lesson we'll teach the children will be about obesity.
Thank you.
I'm pretty excited about today. I babysit Toby's daughter, Sasha, sometimes. So, she's the coolest kid.
She has seen me play with dolls, though. So, don't know how cool she thinks I am.
Put that away and learn.
Learn what?
Learn why Daddy's so cranky when he comes home from work.
I brought my daughter Melissa in. That girl is very spoiled.
That child has no idea what I have to deal with so she can have a little cell phone and spend all my money at that steam-towed mall.
Hello, tiny one.
Come on.
You are the future.
This is my file cabinet.
This is the partition between my desk and Angela's.
Abby's my fiancee Stacey's daughter. I think she'll have a good time. I just hope she doesn't look on my computer.
Actually, I'd better go check.
I'm sorry.
Michael, you remember my daughter Melissa?
Oh, yes. Hello. How are you? Good to see you. Wow, you've really grown up.
You know what? Don't mind me saying so. She has turned into a stone cold fox. Better keep the frat boys away from her.
I'm in eighth grade.
She's in middle school.
Yeah, middle school is amazing. It is extraordinary. An extraordinary time.
It's not that children make me uncomfortable. It's just that why be a dad when you can be a fun uncle?
I've never heard of anyone rebelling against their fun uncle.
I'm going to go read my book now.
Angela, is it okay if I'm the head accountant today?
I'm the head accountant.
Yeah, but can I say that I'm it just for today?
I can't set that kind of precedent.
She's a bright girl. She'd see right through that.
They want how many spiral pads?
Well, 50. I over ordered because they had a back order.
I got permission to bring Jakey into work, which is great because he got suspended this week and now I don't have to pay for a sitter.
Can you pull that down?
Yeah.
Okay, tell them what you wanted to say.
Do you need any help?
No, thanks. We'd have to explain everything. It's probably just easier if we do it ourselves.
Alright, I wasn't expecting that. Let's go draw.
Oh my god, she is so cute. I want to die. Don't you just love kids, Angela?
I guess I wouldn't mind a pair of small, well behaved...