Dunder Mifflin, this is Pam.
Sure, can I ask who's calling?
Just a second.
Jim Halpert.
What? How did you get this number?
Stalker.
Katie and Jim met in the office,
and now I guess they're like going out or dating or something.
And, uh,
I don't know. You know, they're just,
she calls them and they, you know, I'm sorry.
I feel like I'm talking really loud.
Am I talking really loud?
So we're still on for lunch? You're meeting me here?
Okay. Great. Bye.
Hey, you can just give her your extension.
Okay.
Seven Eight and clear. That's nice.
Where's that?
That's here.
Really?
Wow.
Howard slash Ryan.
Ryan Howard is sitting in my office,
and he has been a temp here for a couple of months.
He's been a temp here for a couple of months.
I'm not sure if he's working here.
I don't know.
He's been a temp here for a couple of months.
He's been a temp here for a couple of months,
and he's kind of gotten to lay the land a little bit,
had a few laughs along the way,
and now he wants to know what I think.
The temp agency wants to know what you think.
Shall we?
Let us proceed.
First up, proficiency in necessary skills.
Excellent.
Ha ha ha ha.
Michael's in there right now evaluating the temp.
He hasn't evaluated me in years.
Five years from now, what do you want to do?
Where do you want to be?
Well, I'm interested in business.
Oh, good. Ambitious. Excellent.
Want to be a manager?
No, actually, what I want is to own my own company.
That is ridiculous.
Ryan's about to attend the Michael Scott School of Business.
I'm like Mr. Miyagi and Yoda rolled into one.
Much advice, you seek?
Do you know who that is?
Fah-Zee-Bear?
Mmm, no. That was Yoda.
There are ten rules of business that you need to learn.
Number one, you need to play to win.
But you also have to win to play.
Got it.
And I will give you the rest of the ten at lunch.
Hey.
Michael and I have a very special connection.
He's like Batman. I'm like Robin.
He's like the Lone Ranger and I'm like Tonto.
And it's not like there was the Lone Ranger and Tonto and Bonto.
Rule three, reach for the stars.
And if you fail, see rule four.
Rule four, failure is not an option.
Oh, my God. Ryan is going to love these.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
And at the end I will reveal that they were all just one rule.
That is so cool.
Plus you can go rule five, see rule six.
Rule six, see rule five.
No, I'm not trying to trick him.
I'm trying to be a good mentor.
So...
Kill or be killed.
No.
Shoot to kill or kill to shoot.
No, come on, Dwight.
I have to have ten of these by lunch.
I promised Ryan.
Ask for an extension.
I'm not asking the temp for an extension.
Unless I really need it.
I know Michael's every move.
It's not something you can just pick up.
I could write a book about him.
Literally.
I started one once, but Michael made me stop.
Hey.
How's it going, man?
Good.
What's up?
Oh, nothing much.
What's up with you?
Uh, I'm good, thanks.
Good.
Good, I'm good too.
I'm gonna have a crackin'.