All right, let's get started.
Oh, first off, we're supposed to be pushing card stock this week.
So let's push card stock this week.
Also, what is this?
Tape recorder.
For what?
For recording.
Michael is on vacation, and he has asked me to record all meetings
and to type up the transcripts.
Okay. Karen, any news from that law firm?
Yeah, the deal closed yesterday. It's a six-month commitment.
Oh, my God. Dwight, what are you doing?
What?
You're not allowed to take off your pants in the middle of the office.
I'm not.
Dwight, you know what? Just back off, okay?
That's making me uncomfortable.
This is sexual harassment, by the way.
Oh, my God. He's got a knife.
I do not have a knife.
No, let the record show that Dwight K. Schrute is now completely nude
and is holding a plastic knife to Stanley's neck.
Let the record show that Jim Halpert is a liar.
Dwight Schrute is now wearing a baby's bonnet.
I am not.
Oh, Jim Carrey just walked in.
Dwight, get his autograph from Michael.
Jim Carrey did not just walk in, okay?
Dwight, what is that on your stomach? Is that a Muppet Baby statue?
Oh, my God, Karen, you're right. That is animal from the Muppet Baby statue.
You can't see my stomach.
I am now chopping off Phyllis's head with a chainsaw.
Ring-a-ling-a-ling.
I just had the best, most romantic week of my life in Sandals, Jamaica.
Went with a lady, and we laid on the beach and drank fruity drinks for free
because it was all-inclusive.
And then I flew back to Scranton, and then I lost one of my bags.
Hey, Mr. Telly Man, telly me banana.
Six hand, seven hand, eight hand, brunch!
So delicious.
Dinner, too.
And every morning, I would watch the sunrise, and I would eat a mango.
That is how I want to feel all the time.
It's called island living.
You know how they say, take a chill pill?
In Jamaica, I took one.
Guy on the Beach sold it to me for $40,
and after I finished vomiting, I was more relaxed than I ever have been.
Lost six pounds, too.
That's how I want every day to be.
Michael sends me a postcard from every vacation he goes on.
Atlantic City, he wishes I was here.
Busch Gardens, Virginia, all I got was this lousy postcard.
And this time, I'm Jamaican-ing him crazy.
I don't know how far away he thought he was,
because he put $10 worth of stamps on this.