Pam?
Yeah?
Did you see Oprah yesterday?
No, I didn't.
I, uh, I am going to be a father.
What was Oprah about?
Angelina Jolie was on, and she adopted a baby from Asia,
and she said that it changed her life,
and that really inspired me.
So I want you to look in to see how much
a little Chinese baby would cost.
That's a really big decision.
I know.
Maybe you should wait before you adopt, or not adopt.
Just do it, okay?
Roy's sister looked into it,
and the application alone costs $1,000.
Oh, um, well, find out if there's a cheaper,
less expensive baby out there, okay?
You know, she also said the waiting list is like eight months.
Eight months?
Yeah.
I don't even know if I want a baby in eight months.
Probably won't.
You know what, Pam?
If in ten years I haven't had a baby,
and you haven't had a baby...
No, Michael.
Twenty years.
Thirty.
Sure.
It's a deal.
All right, three pairs of pants.
Three pairs of socks.
Three packs of condoms.
Yesh.
Fun jeans.
Right there.
Ah.
Sign.
Per diem.
Guess where I am going.
I will give you a hint.
It is a booze-fueled sex romp where anything goes.
Today I'm headed to Philadelphia to see a movie.
I'm going to be in the movie.
Anything goes.
Today I'm headed to Philadelphia for the annual Northeastern Office Supply Convention.
Ah!
These things tend to be kind of crazy.
All right, sure you don't want to come?
Yeah.
It's going to be fun.
Change your mind.
We can get you a cot.
A couple of years ago I went to one in Hartford, Connecticut,
and Todd Packer and I went to this bar and met a girl.
And Packer decides to make out with her.
Well, it turns out that her boyfriend is the bouncer at the bar.
Hilarious.
The bouncer chases us out to Packer's vet, jump in the vet, he peels out,
and I don't make it to the car.
And the other bouncer's caught up with me and really did a number on me.
It was in the paper.
But to answer your question, yeah, I am really excited about this weekend.
Don't be mad.
It is a business trip.
But I don't understand.
It's for managers.
Monkey, I am an ARM, Assistant Regional Manager.
I know.
I just...
I was just really hoping we could spend some time together.
Are you still there?
Yes, monkey.
Don't monkey me.
You can't wait to get out of here, ARM.
In the Martin family, we like to say,
looks like someone took the slow train from Philly.
That's code for check out the slut.
What is...
Why are there flies in here?
Oh, my God.
Are you so excited for tonight?
I'm so excited.
You guys are going to be so excited.
Oh, my God.
Are you so excited for tonight?
I'm so excited.
You guys are going to click.
I can feel it.
So what are you wearing?
This.
You look so pretty.
Thank you.
Yes, I have a date.
He's a cartoonist for the local paper,
which is really neat because I like to draw, too.
I'm kind of nervous.
I haven't been on a first date in nine years.
Probably shouldn't broadcast that.
Sign.