David.
Oh, Michael.
You all set?
Isn't our interview tomorrow?
Yes.
I just happened to be in the neighborhood.
Thought I'd drop in, say hello.
Just happened to be in midtown Manhattan.
Thought I'd catch a show.
Know on a work day?
No.
You know what?
Since I got out of college, I've been working on a new project.
And I've been working on it for a while.
And you know what?
I've been working on it since I got out of college.
I'm a little bit more experienced.
I don't know if it's the right word to describe it.
You know what?
I've been working on it for a while.
And I've been working on it for a while.
And I've been working on it since I got out of college.
Thought I'd catch a show.
Know on a work day?
No.
You know what?
Since I'm here, let me ask you a few questions about the job.
Okay.
How many people are you interviewing?
You're only interviewing branch managers and some lower level company people.
Ah, well.
Good.
Out of curiosity, are you interviewing anyone who has been here longer than I have or managers more people?
I don't think so.
Great.
Question.
When you merged those branches, who did you put in charge?
I believe we put you in charge.
Ah, great.
No further questions.
Okay.
I am really looking forward to our interview.
And I'm really looking forward to working with you.
I have got it made in the shade.
I know this company.
The other branch managers are total morons.
Hey, Pam.
Yeah, I forgot what day the interview was and I drove to New York accidentally.
Be like three hours late.
See, I have six hundred.
Yeah, I don't have...
Hey.
Hey, Kevin.
What's different about you?
You look worse.
Thank you.
You got a haircut.
It's sexy, hot.
Oh.
Turn around.
No.
Come on.
No, thanks.
Do it.
Let it do.
What's up, big haircut?
You are no longer Big Tuna.
From henceforth, you shall be known as Big Haircut.
Andy, I just...
What, just Big Haircut?
No.
Sorry, I can't hear you, Big Haircut.
Yep.
What?
I just suggested that I get a haircut for the interview tomorrow.
So that I could look presentable and not, as she so lovingly puts it, homeless.
Hey.
I think it looks great.
Thanks, Pam.
After I had my little outburst at the beach, Jim was really nice about it.
He just basically said that he missed my friendship too and I would always mean a lot to him.
And I understand where he's coming from.
For the record, I am not embarrassed at all.
It needed to be said and I said it.
And it only took me three years to summon the courage.
So, thank you.
Yeah.
You wanted to see me?
Yes.
The time has come to name my own replacement.
So, please hand this letter of congratulations to Dwight K. Schrute.
But that's my name.
Dwight.
Congratulations, A-Wipe.
Don't screw the pooch.
Thank you.
Okay.
Thank you, Michael.
Thank you, Dwight.
Stop crying.
Thank you.
Hey.
About the beach.
It's okay.
We all say things without thinking.
Oh, no.
It's not that.
I've actually been thinking that for a long time.
And I'm glad I said it.
I just am sorry if it made you feel weird.
Oh.
Okay.
Pam is kind of a bitch.
Hey.
What if we leave tonight?
Grab a bite, get a hotel room, enjoy the city a little bit?
Uh...
I just have so much paperwork to do.
Wow.
Done.
Okay.
Let's do it.
So I was wondering if Karen and I could get off a few hours early
because we wanted to spend the night in the city.
Why, so you can do it?
Whoops.
No.
Well, I was thinking that actually we could all leave tomorrow
and do a convoy, you know?
Convoys are really fun.
Pull up next to each other, give each other the finger,
moon each other.
Uh, we're gonna go tonight,
but we're gonna see you there tomorrow morning, right?
All right.
Your loss.
Wait, how would you moon us if you were driving?
Cruise control.
Oh.
So, Jim, who do you think is hotter, Pam or Karen?
Yeah, I'm not gonna talk about this now.
Pam is taller.
You sure?
Yes.
She has bigger breasts, too.
Wow.
But I think Karen has a prettier face.
Mm-hmm.
What else?
Well, I mean, Pam's face is really pretty, too.
It's a very tough call.
Mm.
Really tough call.
Yeah.
You know what?
Why don't you take the rest of the day, figure it out,
and then come back and tell me what you got?
Will do.
All right.
Yes.
Hey, Pam, I've been meaning to say something to you.
I really miss our friendship.
Aw, that's very funny.
I've never heard you talk that much.
I thought it was Kelly.
Are you kidding?
I would never have done that.
It was pathetic, though.
No, that's Pam.
You know what?
Don't even worry about it.
Everyone was so drunk up at it, no one even remembers what you said.
I remember.
I blogged the whole thing.
www.creedthoughts.gov.www.com
Check it out.
Last year, Creed asked me how to set up a blog.
Wanting to protect the world from being exposed to Creed's brain,
I opened up a Word document on his computer and put an address at the top.
I've read some of it.
Even for the internet, it's pretty shocking.
There's Jim.
My buddy Jim.
Oh, man, so many memories.
So there's Phyllis and Stanley, hard at work.
Toby, you ruined the picture, man.
I'm sorry.
You want me to get you and...
No, no, no.
You know what?
You guys should...
There's something I want to say to you that I've never said to you before.
Pam has actually inspired me to just say the truth.
I hate your guts.
I know.
Wow, that felt so good to say.
Oh, what a relief.
I feel invigorated.
Well, good luck on the interview tomorrow.
Oh, hey.
Thanks for jinxing me, jerk.
And it's not just me.
Everybody here hates you.
Okay.
Anything funny?
Um, I'll tell you, but you have to promise me that you won't make a big speech about
it two years from now.
Can you do that?
Forget it.
All right.
Hey, Pam, do you do yoga?
No.
Oh, that's gonna hurt you.
That's gonna hurt real bad.
There they are, the accounting department.
I shall miss your humility and your promptly printed checks.
Do you think it's gonna be weird working with Jan in New York?
No, not at all.
I haven't talked to Jan since we broke up.
And I think if she had something to say, she would have called me.
Maybe you should talk to her before...
No, no, no, no.
You know what?
It's a done deal.
I basically have the job already.
There's nothing she can do to stop it now.
I already sold my condo.
Mike, what?
Why?
I'm sorry, that just doesn't make sense.
Yes, I...
Why?
Who gave you that advice?
Yeah, Michael, you should never sell your condo.
I have to buy another place.
But you said you were in debt.
You're not sure that you have the job.
I sold it on eBay.
The buyer was very motivated, as was I.
It went for 80% of what I paid, sold in record time.
You know, the three of you have always worked together like a three-wheeled unicycle.
Thank you.
Like a string quartet.
Like a fork.
Like three finely tuned engines in the same car.
Or a tri-tip steak.
Or...
How would you like to spend the night with the regional manager of Dunder Mifflin Scranton?
No, Dwight.
I don't care if that's how they consolidated power in ancient Rome.
No, no, not Michael.
Me.
I'm taking his job.
Not now.
Goodbye, Kelly Kapoor.
Jim, Jim, Jim.
Jim, Jim, Jim, Jim, Jim, Jim, Jim.
Oh, hey Dwight.
I am going to be your new boss.
It is my greatest dream come true.
Welcome to the Hotel Hell.
Check in time is now.
Check out time is never.
Does my room have cable?
No.
And the sheets are made of fire.
Can I change rooms?
Sorry, we're all booked up.
Hell convention in town.
Can I have a late checkout?
I'll have to talk to the manager.
You're not the manager, even in your own fantasy?
I'm the owner.
The co-owner.
With Satan.
Okay.
Okay, just so I understand it, in your wildest fantasy, you are in Hell,
and you are co-running a bed and breakfast with the devil.
Yeah, but I haven't told you my salary yet.
Go.
$80,000 a year.
Once I am officially regional manager, my first order of business will be to demote Jim Halpert.
So I will need a new number two.
My ideal choice?
Jack Bauer.
But he is unavailable.
Fictional.
And overqualified.
I will see you at the interview.
Yes, you will.
Who is Dee Abramson?
Oh, he's from that company in Pitts Michael.
Why are you here?
Uh, how are you?
I'm good.
How are you, Janet?
It's good to see you.
I'm great.
Can we talk privately for a minute?
Why privately?
I just, I don't like the way that we laugh things.
Okay, sure, fine.
Why don't you wait in my office?
I have some important business matters to take care of.
Okay.
Pam, Def Con, Tan, Houston, we have a problem.
What do you want me to do?
Uh, I may need some immediate assistance if you would slowly and quietly gather the ladies in the conference room.
Ellis, Angela, Karen.
What about Meredith?
No.
She's an alternate.
So, how you been?
Good.
Yeah.
Sorry to drop by unexpectedly.
I, uh, I tried calling but I kept getting voicemail.
Weird.
Yeah, I didn't get both of your messages.
Ah.
So, uh, Michael leads us in the conference room.
Who's with Janet again?
Hey, um, before I leave tonight, would you mind making a half a dozen copies of Jim's and my sales reports for interviews tomorrow?
Uh, sure.
Thanks.
I really hope you get the job.
After you ended everything with us, I went on a vacation.
Hmm.
It's kind of clear my mind.
Sounds good.
Sounds fun.
It was.
Yeah, it was good.
I think I should just get right to the point.
Okay.
You know, um, I, I, I feel good about myself for the first time in a really long time.
And I've made some big changes in my life and I miss you.
I want us to go back together.
Do you excuse me for a second?
Oh.
Defcon 20.
She wants to get back together.
What are you gonna do?
I don't know.
That's why you're here.
Help me.
Do you want to get back together with her?
No.
What do I do?
Just don't get back together with her.
What if she makes me?
How can she make you get back together with her?
She made me do a lot of things I didn't want to do.
This was a terrible relationship.
You were not happy when you were with her.
I wasn't.
You're so much happier now.
Just go in there and be strong.
You're right.
You are absolutely right.
I need to go in there and tell her that we can't be together.
Right.
Wow.
Do it.
I'm in a very good place right now.
Thank you.
Okay.
Jan?
We need to talk.
Jan is in a different place right now.
And it is a sign of maturity to give people second chances.
So I'm going to hear her out.
Oh, my God.
Yeah.
Bigger, actually.
That's crazy.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, my God.
Can you really that?
Unbelievable.
Wow.
So you could put the cup right there.
I know.
No, it's fine.