So do you want to see it or not?
I don't know.
They're like Friday Night Crowds.
Oh my God, you're like agoraphobic.
Agoraphobic?
Yeah.
Really?
You would rather sit on your couch and watch a Phillies game than go out to a movie with
your awesome girlfriend.
Absolutely correct.
Later, Jim.
Kev, have a good weekend.
Yeah, good.
Bye.
Okay, so this is what's gonna happen.
You're gonna suck it up.
Here we go.
And we're gonna go to dinner.
Okay.
And then we're gonna go to the movies.
Sounds good.
Hey, helper!
Hey.
Roy!
Ah!
Pam, please call security!
Every day for eight years, I have brought pepper spray into this office to protect myself
and my fellow employees.
And every day for eight years, people have laughed at me.
Well, who's laughing now?
No need for consternation.
Everything is under control.
Michael, last Friday, one of your employees attacked another employee in your office.
It was a crime of passion, Jan.
Not a disgruntled employee.
Everyone here is extremely gruntled.
Is Toby there?
No.
I'm here, Jan.
What's the situation, Toby?
Well, we fired Roy, obviously.
And Jim won't press charges against Roy or the company.
Thank God.
Yeah.
But now apparently, Darryl has some issue with this.
No, he has been wanting a raise for a couple of months and he's just using this Roy thing
as leverage.
Are you gonna take care of this?
Yepers.
What did I tell you about Yepers?
I don't remember.
I told you not to say it.
Do you remember that?
Yeah.
I really don't want to talk about it.
I don't mean to be rude, but I just, I don't want to comment on what happened.
It sucked.
I guess all things considered, I was lucky Dwight was there.
And Roy was lucky that Dwight only used pepper spray.
Not the nunchucks or the throwing stars.
Hey man, I never got a chance to thank you for stopping Roy.
Thank you.
Thank you not necessary and thus not accepted.
I saw someone breaking the law and I interceded.
Okay.
Um, gotcha something.
Don't want it.
You don't know what it is.
Don't want it, won't open it.
Don't need it, won't take it.
Citizens do not accept prizes for being citizens.
It was a little glass display case for his bobble head.
That would have made us even, I think.
He saves my life.
I get him a box for his death toy.
Stephen.
No, don't call me a hero.
Do you know who the real heroes are?
The guys who wake up every morning and go into their normal jobs and get a distress
call from the commissioner and take off their glasses and change into capes and fly around
fighting crime.
Those are the real heroes.
Angela, Roy's check.
He's coming in later to pick it up.
Man, I cannot believe I missed the fight.
It was crazy.
You saw it?
Describe it please.
Well, I heard some shouting and I look over and Roy's by reception and you can just tell
he's going to punch somebody.
Jim says something, Roy stomps over there, all of a sudden, bam, Roy goes down and Dwight
standing there like an action hero.
It was insane.
Well, good for Dwight.
Okay, I want you to be Daryl and ask me for a raise because I need to try out some of
these negotiation tactics on you.
Where'd you get that?
Wikipedia.
Wikipedia is the best thing ever.
Anyone in the world can write anything they want about any subject so you know you are
getting the best possible information.
Okay, Daryl, ask me for a raise.
Hey, Mike, since Roy left I've been doing a lot more work and I need a raise.
Hmm, well that's interesting, Daryl.
I think that maybe you should cry importantly and not cry for the next week.
I can't hear you.
What I'm saying is that no one really loves you.
Still nothing.
Okay, see what I did?
No.
And by whispering I established a dominant physical position.
Nice.
Okay, let's try another one.
Okay.
Walking out of the room unexpectedly.
And what happens in this one?
It's a surprise.
Okay.
Go ahead, ask me for a raise.
Can I have a raise?
Sex, Steve Martin, Daryl Andrews.
What?
No, what did you say?
I didn't say anything.
I was waiting to see what happened.
That's interesting, what you were getting at.
I saw the perpetrator advance towards the victim at a high rate of speed.
His head was thrown back, his shoulder and arm cocked, indicating an attack position.
Perp grabbed the victim.
I removed my weapon from its secure hiding place.
Oh, which is where?
Irrelevant.
I discharged it at a distance of a little over a meter into the perpetrator's eyes,
nose and face area, rendering him utterly and completely disabled.
Then I contacted the authorities.
The end.
Thanks, Dwight.
That is the bravest thing I have ever heard.
I can't imagine what I would have done.
I can.
You would have left me to fend for myself.
Like the time we were on the Ferris wheel and that kid dropped a milkshake on me and you just laughed.
Well, that was funny, that's why.
Oh, it was?
Okay, well the next time you get scared that you think a murderer is in your apartment in the middle of the night
and you call me to calm you down, you can just call somebody else because I'm not going to do it anymore, Ryan.
There's a bunch of people back here, maybe.
Guys.
I don't think Michael intended to punish me by putting Ryan back here with Kelly.
But if he did intend that, wow.
Genius.
Yeah.
You ready for me?
Yes, yeah, absolutely.
Have a seat.
You know what?
Actually, let's go into the conference room.
Okay.
No, you know what?
Let's stay here.
Let's go.
Yeah, let's go.
Tactic number six.
Change the location of the meeting at the last second.
Totally throws them off.
Number fourteen.
Declining to speak first.
Makes them feel uncomfortable, puts you in control.
I am declining to speak first.
Okay, I'll start.
It's pretty simple, really.
I think I deserve a raise.
I'm scheduled to get one in six months, but I'd like that to be moved up to now.
Hmm.
I'm sorry.
Darryl, you are a good worker and a good man.
I just, you know, times are tight.
And I just don't think corporate's going to go for this right now.
Are you wearing lady clothes?
What?
Those look like lady pants.
No.
This is a power suit.
That there's a woman's suit.
I do not buy women's clothes.
Would not make that mistake again.
I'm gonna call Roy, man.
Okay.
This is gonna make me feel better.
This is too good.
You know what?
Pam, would you please tell Darryl that this is not a woman's suit?
Oh my God, that's a woman's suit.
You're wearing a woman's suit?
No, I do, I wear men's suits.
Okay?
I was wearing men's clothes and everybody was rifling through them like crazy.
And I grabbed one.
And it fit.
So I don't think that this is totally just a woman's suit.
At the very least, it's bisexual.
Who makes it?
Um, mysterious.
And it is mysterious because the buttons are on the wrong side.
That's the mystery.
It's got shoulder pads.
Did you see that line?
Can you stop it, please?
So none of that tipped you off?
It's European, okay? It's a European cut.
Michael, the pants don't have any pockets.
No, they don't, see?
Italians don't wear pockets.
It's been a really rough couple of days.
This helps a little.
Hey, maybe you want to come over and read my closet.
No, I don't want to do that because I'm twice your size anyway.
You look like Hillary Clinton.
Um, let's just do this in 15 minutes, okay?
Okay, can you stand right there for one second?
I've got to send some emails.
Negotiations are all about controlling things,
about being in the driver's seat.
And you make one tiny mistake, you're dead.
I made one tiny mistake.
I wore woman's clothes.
So, Karen, how do you feel that Roy tried to kick your boyfriend's ass over another woman?
I feel great, Kevin. Thank you.
You must have been scared out of your mind.
Well, you know what happened so fast,
I didn't really have the time to be scared.
What happened?
Exactly.
I wasn't here, so I haven't really heard the whole story.
Well, Jim and I were talking,
and Roy walked in, looking super angry.
And he's a big dude, you know?
And all of a sudden, Jim pushed me out of the way,
and Roy cocked his fist,
and then bam, bam, bam, bam.
And then, bam, Dwight sprays him and knocks him on his butt.
Goodness.
When I heard Jim and Pam had kissed,
my reaction was to have lots of long talks with Jim about our feelings.
Roy just attacked him.
I'm not sure which one Jim hated more.
Let's get down to business.
Why don't you tell me why you think you deserve a raise?
Well, it's simple, Mike.
I mean, we merged these two branches, right?
So now we're shipping twice as many orders as we used to.
And with Roy going, we got a smaller crew.
And I'm picking up all of his slack,
so I think I should be compensated fairly by getting a raise.
That was a very good point.
What? I can't hear you.
I can't... What, Mike, are you...
You make a very compelling argument.
Sorry I almost got you killed.
Yeah.
That was nuts.
He could have broken your nose or something.
Crazy.
It's just so stupid.
I mean, getting back with Roy and everything.
I mean, what was I thinking, right?
No, I mean, you guys really seem to have a strong connection.
Not anymore.
It's completely over now.
We'll see.
I'm sure you guys will find your way back to one another someday.
Jim.
I am really sorry.
Oh, yeah. Don't worry about it.
I'm going to give you a piece of paper.
I want you to write down how much you want,
and I want you to slide it back across the desk to me.
Why can't I just tell you?
Because that is the way these things are done in films.
Slide it, slide it.
There you go.
Oh.
Come on. Be serious.
I am serious, Mike. That's a 10% raise.
That's what I want.
I can't give you that. I don't make this much.
Come on. Be for real.
I don't.
I'll prove it to you.
There it is.
Paste up.
Are you serious? You're earning this?
Plus perks, yes.
Mike, this is barely more than I make.
You've been here 10 years, dog.
14 years.
No, please don't.
I'm sorry, Mike. Some more folks got to hear about this.
Okay, let's take 15.
A boss's salary isn't just about money.
It is about perks.
It... For example,
every year I get a $100 gas card.
Can't put a price tag on that.
Okay. If you don't want a gift,
at least let me buy you a beer.
Or lunch or something.
When Han Solo returns to the Death Star
in the Millennium Falcon
and shoots down the TIE fighters and saves the rebel cause,
do you think he does so for a free beer?
Boy, I...
Why are you so interested in buying me something, Jim?
What's your angle?
It's like when he annoys me
and I want to screw with him to get him back,
he never sees it coming.
But now I want to be nice to him and actually give him something.
And he's like an eel.
I just can't grab onto him.
I'm furious.
Maybe you just feel guilty about all the pranks.
Well...
Yes, that's probably what it is.
So what do I do?
Hmm.
I don't know. Maybe you should go back out there
and sell paper so we can go on a trip.
Michael. Hmm?
Here's the $15 I owe you.
No, thank you. Yeah.
I heard you might need it. So...
Here's the $40 you gave me.
I didn't give you $40.
In a way, you did.
Yeah. I heard how much Michael makes.
I still think he's way overpaid.
14 years.
14...
I know.
Okay.
All right. I gotta go.
Okay. Here's a straight dope.
No tricks, no Wikipedia.
What? I talked to corporate
and they told me that I can only give you a 5% raise.
That's because of you, Mike.
They're not gonna give the working man more than the boss.
Well, what am I supposed to do?
It's your own raise.
You gotta get out there and earn, son.
I'm not gonna go out and ask for a raise right now.
That is ridiculous.
Well, when they merge the two branches together,
they put you in charge, okay?
And we're shipping more now than we ever have.
That's true. Yeah, that's true.
You gotta call your girl and get paid.
Show her who wears the pants in a relationship.
You know what? I should.
Yeah, you should.
I've been a loyal employee for a long time.
14 years long.
You know what? I deserve a bump.
Make it happen, Captain.
I am making it happen, Sergeant.
I remember it was very late at night,
like 11, 1130.
A big fella comes in screaming about
God knows what.
I think maybe Halpert had stolen his car,
something like that.
So the big fella pulls out a sock filled with nickels.
Then Charute grabs a can of hairspray and a lighter.
You're useless.
Well, why don't we talk next month after the quarter ends?
No, Jan.
I've never asked for a raise in 14 years.
This is long overdue.
I want to do it today.
Today, alright.
Well, if you want to do it today,
we should do it in person.
And can you get here by five?
Yeah, um, yeah.
I'll leave right away.
Great. And listen, because of our situation,
we're going to need to have a third party present.
Yes, I'm bringing Daryl.
Daryl from the warehouse?
No, Michael, we need an HR rep.
So you should just bring Toby.
Hey, I'd rather kill myself.
No, Toby is terrible.
Toby is the worst human being I've ever known.
Fine.
You are so mean.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Yes, you do, Ryan Bailey Howard.
You call me stupid.
Toby, come on, let's go.
Where?
I'm going to smack you in the head with a hammer.
Come on, let's go.
What is so stupid about wanting to name a baby Usher?
Usher, Jen, for Hudson Capoor.
Don't you see why that's insane?
Oh, so I'm crazy?
I'm crazy about you.
Don't you see why that's insane?
Oh, so I'm crazy now?
Comfortable, Mike?
Yeah.
How about you, man?
No.
Don't ever touch a black man's radio.
Or stockard.
Or shower.
I won't touch yours, by the way.
Thank you.
I haven't been in New York in a long time.
You better get out of the way.
Maybe I'll stay overnight.
I got a cousin live down there.
And when we get home?
Oh, you can stay too.
He's got a big place.
Where do y'all stay?
It's not that big.
The bus is going to get you home quick.
Hold on.
And then all of a sudden, Dwight stood up and was like,
No!
Then what'd he do?
Well, you should just read the report that Toby did.
He took everyone's stories.
It's Kelly.
Oh, yeah, I could totally help you with that.
Okay, let me just get the folder out.
Okay, it seems here that you
ordered 12,000 reams of paper.
Oh, 12 reams.
Hey, guys.
Jan is ready for you.
Oh, yeah.
Okay.
I'm bringing it home now.
And don't forget the new black man phrase I told you.
Pippity poppy, give me the zobity.
Yes, sir.
Remember that.
I'll be right outside if you need me.
All right.
Yeah, I'm talking about some new phrases.
I want them to get the raise.
I just can't help myself.
Just can't help myself.
Hey, man.
I'm sorry.