Hey. Hey.
Who are you faxing so early in the morning?
Oh, um, kind of hard to explain.
I don't have a ton of contact with this Grand Branch,
but before I left, I took a box of Dwight's stationery.
So from time to time, I send Dwight faxes.
From himself. From the future.
Dwight, at 8 a.m. today, someone poisons the coffee.
Do not drink the coffee. More instructions will follow.
Cordially, future Dwight.
No!
You'll thank me later.
There she is.
Jan Levinson.
First thing in the morning.
Love to start the day with you.
I'm so excited.
Jan Levinson. First thing in the morning.
Love to start my day with a hotty bowl of Jan.
Michael.
Just call me Levinson in the morning, baby.
Michael. Yes.
I'm here to tell you that we are closing this Grand Branch.
I don't understand.
The board voted last night to close your branch.
On whose authority?
The board's.
What?
I'm very sorry. I don't relish telling you this.
You've been a big part of this company.
And the board asked me to thank you for your years of service.
You're welcome.
A small number of people will be transferred to the Stanford branch,
and the rest will be getting severance packages.
Am I a small number person, or a severance package person?
Or a severance package person?
Well, we haven't made final decisions about personnel yet.
But you're a severance package person.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Oh, my God.
No.
What are they talking about?
I don't know.
Is it serious?
I don't know, Kev.
If you find out anything,
call me.
You got it, buddy.
Are you all right, Michael?
I'm not sure.
All right.
You know what? I don't get it.
I don't get it.
Because our numbers aren't that bad.
Things are looking up.
It's not all about numbers, Michael. It's about talent.
Oh, you got it. Josh?
Our CFO believes that Josh is going to play an important role in our company's future.
What role is that? King of the stupid universe?
Don't do this, Josh.
I think we're finished, and I need to go.
I would appreciate it if you would please use discretion until we get our ducks in a row.
I know you're mad.
But don't do this to me. I know I hurt you.
But please do not do this to me.
Don't hurt me like I hurt you.
Jan.
It is an outrage.
That's all.
They are making a huge, huge mistake.
Let's see Josh replace these people.
Let's see Josh find another Stanley.
You think Stanlies grow on trees?
Well, they don't.
There is no Stanley tree.
Do you think the world is crawling with philuses?
Show me that farm.
With philuses and kevins sprouting up all over the place right for the plucking.
Pictures, memories.
Look at that. They grow up so fast.
Hey, stranger.
That sounds weird, please.
Sorry, I just feel like we haven't talked in a while.
Well, we have nothing to talk about Dwight.
Just do your work while you still can.
When you become close with someone, you develop a kind of sixth sense.
You can read their moods like a book.
Right now, the title of Michael's book is
Something Weird is Going On.
Colon.
What did Jan say?
The Michael Scott Story.
By Michael Scott with Dwight Schrute.
Hey, did you hear about your friends in Pennsylvania?
Rumor has it that the Scranton branch is...
Really?
That's bad.
Sorry, Scranton branch is closing.