Hello son. If you're watching this that means I'm already dead. Life is a...
How do you know it's gonna be a boy?
Would you stop interrupting please?
Yesterday I was scraping some gunk off my wall sockets with a metal fork and I gave myself the nastiest shock.
And when I came to I had an epiphany.
Life is precious.
And if I die, I want my son to know the dealio. The dealio of life.
Here are some things that I want to teach you that your mother won't be able to.
To jump start a car, first pop the hood. Then you take these bad boys and clip them anywhere on the engine.
Then you take these and clip them wherever.
Number eight. Learn how to take off a woman's bra.
What?
We will demonstrate on Pam.
No.
And...
Come on. You just twist your hand until something breaks.
How?
Well, you get the picture. Thanks Pam.
And remember, no matter what, I will always love you.
What if he's a murderer?
He's not going to be a murderer.
Maybe that's how you die.
You know what Dwight? Do you want to do this or no?
I want to do this.
Okay.
From the top. Ready?
Three.
Action.
Hello everyone.
As you know, we are six days away from Phyllis' wedding.
So get your suits to the dry cleaners and get your hair did.
And Karen, you might want to invest in a dress or a skirt of some kind if you don't already have one.
This may be Phyllis' only wedding ever.
It's my job to ensure that none of you look like ragamuffins.
I'm trying to get everyone excited about Phyllis' wedding.
Because I want her to get people excited about my wedding when the time comes.
Which won't be hard because it's going to be awesome.
A lot better than hers, that's for sure.
It'll probably be on a boat.
So I am instituting prima nocta.
Prima nocta, I believe from the movie Braveheart and confirmed on Wikipedia,
is when the king got to deflower every new bride on her wedding night.
So...
I'm sorry. I had a very different understanding as to what prima nocta meant.
And I would never ever want to do that.
I mean, for the women to have to do.
That's...
So let us take a moment of silence for the women of Braveheart.
For the brave women.
It couldn't have been fun.
Sometimes I feel like I can talk my way out of anything.
What's up, spin stars?
Nothing.
You know, this is a luncheon shower. Girls only.
No problem.
The guys are having a little shin dig of their own in the warehouse.
From 2.30 to 3.15.
It is the only time that pop was available.
Sort of a guy's night out.
A GNO, if you will. A gno.
Actually, it's more of a guy's afternoon in.
A GAI. A gay.
Not...
It's not gay. It's just a...
It's a bridal shower for guys. A guy shower.
An hour-long shower with guys.
There are 200 things that every man should know.
99 are in this book.
101 are in this one.
How to Throw an Awesome Bachelor Party.
Only one in both books.
I already know how to shuffle a deck of cards.
And I can tell the difference between red and white wine.
And I know to stay away from a woman when she's having her menstrual cycle.
Fun facts, but important facts.
This must be incredibly painful for you.
Not really.
Well, if it is, I'm a good listener.
And I can grab a couple pints of B&J, curl up, you know.
No, that sounds good. But I'm fine. Unfortunately.
Alright. Well, I am a resource, Pam, so...
Yeah, I know.
I guess Jim and I have had a little bit of a rough patch for the past couple weeks.
But we had some really good talks.
And actually now I think that we're better than ever.
Karen and I had a long talk last night.
And the night before that.
And every night.
For the last night.
And I think that's the best part.
And every night.
For the last five nights.
Something's up with Jim and Karen.
Not that I've been eavesdropping.
It's not really any of my business.
But I've gotten pretty good at reading the back of Jim's neck.
Well, well, well. If it isn't the runaway bride.
Michael's in his office.
You know, Pam, you try to act like Miss Priss.
But I know you're a hellion under that buttoned up blouse and glasses.
I don't wear glasses.
Dunder Mifflin, this is Pam.
Yes, that will take...