Okay. What is your goal for after lunch?
Ahem. I will do my job to the best of my abilities.
Heaven help us. Specifically.
I will do my regional manager job
to the best of my capabilities.
Specifically, Michael.
Specifically, Jan,
I will make at least 10 phone calls to clients.
Yes, I have to begin every day
by letting Jan know what I intend to accomplish
and then I have to call her at the end of the day
to tell her what I did accomplish.
But it's not mandatory.
It's something that I wanted to do.
And so it's voluntary, really,
even though she makes me...
I think she just wants to hear my voice
because we're no longer lovers,
and she's just hurting.
But things are going well with Carol.
I've seen her seven times in the last three months,
and I'm growing very fond of her kids.
Tommy, who I call Tomas,
and the little girl.
Are you in the toilet, Michael?
No.
Well, I know sometimes you are
and that you wouldn't tell me,
so I'm just going to assume that you are
and call me back when you're finished.
Okay.
Yeah, I'm not a temp anymore.
I got Jim's old job,
which means at my ten-year high school reunion,
it will not say Ryan Howard is a temp.
It will say I'm a temp.
I'm a temp.
It will say Ryan Howard is a junior sales associate
at a mid-range paper supply firm.
That'll show him.
You have no idea how long I wanted to do that.
Me too.
I think we're just drunk.
No, I'm not drunk.
Are you drunk?
No.
Jim.
Are you really gonna marry him?
Okay.
Jim is gone.
He's gone.
I miss him so much.
Oh, I cry myself to sleep, Jim.
False. I do not miss him.
No, that is the fun of this place.
I call everybody Faggy.
Why wouldn't anyone find that offensive?
Okay, I think Oscar would just like if he's lame
or something like that.
That's what Faggy means.
No, not really.
Apparently you called Oscar Faggy.
Yeah.
For like the movie Shakespeare in Love
more than an action movie.
It wasn't just an action movie.
It was Die Hard.
Alright, Michael, but Oscar's really gay.
Exactly.
I mean for real.
Yeah, I know.
No, he's attracted to other men.
Okay, little too far.
Across the line.
Okay, I am telling you, Oscar is an actual homosexual.
Yeah, he told me this morning.
Obviously he hopes he can count on your discretion.
I would have never called him that if I knew.
You don't call
retarded people retards.
It's bad taste.
You call your friends retards
when they're acting retarded.
And I consider Oscar a friend.
Listen, man, I'm so sorry.
I had no idea.
Oh, it's fine.
No, it's okay.
I feel terrible about it.
I have been calling people faggys
since I was in junior high
and I have never made this mistake.
If I don't know how to behave
it is because
I am just so far the opposite way.
You know?
I'm just, I can't even imagine
this thing.
Maybe we could go out for a beer
sometime and you can...