Good morning, Pam.
Oh, welcome back, Andy.
Drew. I'm Drew now.
Oh. Drew. Sorry.
Apology not accepted.
Because it wasn't even necessary in the first place.
Several weeks ago, Andy Bernard had an incident.
Aah! Ow!
But after five weeks in anger management, I'm back.
And I've got a new attitude and a new name
and a bunch of new techniques for dealing with the grumpies.
Morning, Jim.
Hey, Andy. How are you, man?
Good. Drew.
What's that?
You can call me Drew.
No, I'm not gonna call you that.
Cool.
I can't control what you do. I can only control what I do.
Andy.
Drew.
Dwight.
How's it going, man?
Yes. I have decided to shun Andy Bernard for the next three years,
which I'm looking forward to.
It's an Amish technique.
It's like slapping someone with silence.
I was shunned from the age of four until my sixth birthday
for not saving the excess oil from a can of tuna.
Jim, could you please inform Andy Bernard that he is being shunned?
Andy, Dwight says, welcome back, and he could use a hug.
Okay, tell him that's not true.
Dwight says that he actually doesn't know one single fact about bear attacks.
Okay, no. Jim, tell him bears can climb faster than they can run.
Jim, tell him!
Andy, that's too far.
Damn you.
When people think of Andy, they think of hate and anger.
When people think of Drew, they think of baked goods.
Oh, my God. These cookies have no flavor.
How is that possible?
They are the worst.
Who's this brew check?
Drew isn't a girl.
He's a bear.
She's Andy.
Oh, no. Nobody likes my cookies.
I'm so angry.
I hit something.
Totally kidding, guys.
A little device I learned to diffuse tension.
Be the first to make fun of yourself.
Because if they make fun of you before you do, then you might lose your mind.
Is that the last of it?
I'm sorry.
It's okay. I can't always have what I want, but I can always want what I have.
Well, would you like a cup of no coffee?
Because that's what we have.
Is it fresh?
Are you going to beat me up?
Um...
No.
People don't need to be afraid of me.
I can't achieve anger anymore.
And I have a new car, a Toyota Prius, because Andy didn't care about fuel efficiency.
But Drew has seen an inconvenient truth nearly twice.
Today is safety training day.
Toby is leading ours upstairs.
But I am giving everyone a little bit of a treat.
We are going to listen in on Darryl's presentation to the warehouse.
And if I know Darryl, it's going to be zappity.
Okay, come on, everybody. Go time.
Don't worry, Pam. You will be answering phones for the rest of your life.
Your long, lovely life.
Saved it.
Here we go.
Field trip.
Step lively.
Go into the science museum.
That's the best way to do it.
I'm going to go to the science museum.
Field trip.
Step lively.
Go into the science museum.
Learn by touching.
I've been told that I'm a tactile learner.
Buddy system, everyone. Buddy up. Find a buddy.
Now, this is the forklift.
You need a license to operate this machine.
That means the upstairs office workers can't drive it.
Quiz. Mike, should you drive the forklift?
I can and I have to.
No, no, no, no, no. I said should you. You should not drive it.
You should not drive the forklift. You understand that?
You're not allowed to drive the forklift.
It's not safe. You don't have a license.
Guys, I'm not the only one who's driven the forklift.
Pudge has driven the forklift.
Madge.
I thought your name was Pudge.
No, it's always been Madge.
Okay. Um, her.
Yes, her is qualified to work a dangerous machine. You are not.
Okay?
Fine.
Do you understand that?
Yes.
We do safety training every year or after an accident.
We've never made it a full year.
This particular time I was reaching for a supply box on the top shelf
when one office worker, who shall remain nameless,
kicked the ladder off from under me and yelled,
Gerald, how's it hanging?
And I fell and busted my ankle.
I'm legitimately scared for my workers.
The baler can flatten a car engine.
It can cut off your arm and crush your entire body without skipping a beat.
Yeah.
How many people a year do you think get their arms cut off in a baler?
Baler? I hardly know her.
Damn it, Michael. Pay attention, man.
Anybody want to take a guess?
I bet a buck says it's over 50.
You really want to bet?
Anybody.
Ever since March Madden ascended, I am so bored.
How many?
Okay, you're on.
Ten people, Michael. Ten people.
Would you like to be one of them?
No, don't worry about it. We'll just go double or nothing.
On what?
I don't know. I'll figure something out.
What are you guys talking about?
These are very dangerous machines down here,
and the upstairs workers, Michael, should not go anywhere near them.
Yes, yes. But it wouldn't be the worst thing in the world.
It wouldn't be the worst thing in the world.
What the hell is wrong with this man?
It's a big red trash compact, and that's very dangerous.
Disrespect the baler.
Okay, okay, okay. I got it. I got it.
Only on the rarest of occasions would I go near it.
No, do not touch it. There is no occasion for you to go near this stuff, okay?
You should work out, Ryan. You look so hot.
Totally. We should both work out.
Screw you.
Kelly, Ryan looks great. You should be thankful that you get...
Sir, could you please, please focus on Daryl?
Try.
Summing up.
Summing up, Daryl. Summing up.
Toby now has the floor,
and he is going to try not to screw this up like everything else in his life.
Let me rephrase that.
I believe that you can do safety training and make it sound just as good as Daryl.
Here we go.
Okay, one thing you're going to want to look out for is carpal tunnel syndrome.
It's recommended that you take a ten-minute break from typing every hour.
For your circulation, you're going to want to get up out of your chairs
and move around about ten minutes every hour.
Yes, good. Fine.
Like stretching and...
Yeah, your computer screen can be a big strain on your eyes,
so it's also recommended that you step away from about ten minutes every hour.
Wow, that is...that time really adds up. That's like a half an hour every hour.
Take them at the same time.
Okay, you know what? You're making us sound kind of lame,
so skip ahead to the really dangerous stuff.
Like sometimes computers can explode, can they not?
No, no.
You always want to keep a sweater or cardigan of some sort in case it gets drafty.
What about a long sleeve tee?
Well, that'll work.
Long johns? A shawl?
You know, anything that warms you.
Okay, you know what? I think that everybody is going to vomit due to boredom.
Sorry. He is very lame.
Um, see...
Seasonal Affective Disorder.
A depression that includes weight gain, fatigue, irritability,
brought on by the low light of winter.
Thank God we only had a baler to deal with.
Yeah, that dim light is a bitch, ain't it?
Okay, guys, you know what? I didn't interrupt when you were having your presentation.
Actually, you did.
Yes. Okay, let's do another one. This is a good one.
A particular concern for office workers is a sedimentary lifestyle which can contribute...
Sedentary.
Yes. Which can contribute to heart disease.
Heart disease kills more people than balers.
That's called having a fat butt, Michael.
No, no, it's sedentary.
Yeah, that's fat butt disease. That's what you suffer from?
Yeah, fat butt disease, Mike.
Excuse me, Sea Monster, you weigh like a thousand pounds.
Yeah? I bet you'd like to swim with this Sea Monster, wouldn't you?
Ryan!
Dude, please tell your girl to shut up.
What?
Kelly, you insulted the gentleman. Please apologize.
Are you kidding me?
All right, we out of here.
Daryl, I did not walk out in the middle of yours, so I...
Yeah, but ours was real, Michael.
Yes.
That's what we've been trying to tell you, Mike. It's serious down there.
We do dangerous stuff, man. This is shenanigans, foolishness, nerf ball.
You live a sweet little nerfy life, sitting on your biscuit, never having to risk it.
Okay.
What, this nerf isn't cool anymore?
Daryl thinks he's such a man because he works in a warehouse.
Well, big deal. I worked in a warehouse. Men's warehouse. I was a greeter.
I'd like to see Daryl greet people. Probably make him feel like wimps.
Not me. I...
Hello, I'm Michael. Welcome to Men's Warehouse. We have a special on khaki pants today.
This is one example.
Ten.
Really, ten. That's your guess. You're a professional accountant.
There's like ten green ones.
Forty-two.
I'm gonna say fifty.
Fifty-one.
Oh, come on. That is lame.
It's a strategy. It's called being smart. Thank you.
Oh, jeez.
I don't know how the whole betting thing started, but it's fun.
Ten.
Kev's out.
Damn it.
Forty-seven. Forty-eight. Forty-nine. Jim wins.
Oh!
That is not fair. He has spent hours up here at reception with you. Hours. And hours.
Okay. Okay.
No, constantly. Like for years.
Okay. Pam, depression is as scary as a bailer, right?
I don't understand the question.
Working in an office can lead to depression, which can lead to suicide.
I mean, this is really serious stuff.
Yeah.
Nobody commits suicide because they work with a bailer.
And yet those guys are making fun of me, calling me a nerf. That...
It's really hard to demonstrate depression. Their safety training had visuals.
Yeah. You are so right.
They had visual aids, and all we had were the facts.
You don't go to the science museum and get handed a pamphlet on electricity.
You go to the science museum and you put your hand on a metal ball, your hair sticks up straight, and you know science.
So you're okay?
Indubitably.
We got beat today, Dwight, but it was not a fair fight.
No, it was not.
Mind me again, what was the fight exactly? Who was it between and what was the outcome?
It was the warehouse guys.
Right.
Dwight. They embarrassed us because they had a much scarier safety presentation.
They used props, they used visual aids, and they just made us look like dope.
Idiots. God, what are we going to do?
I don't know. I don't know. Because you know what our killer is?
Depressions.
Wolves.
Depression.
Visual aids.
Yes.
A quilt. A depression quilt.
No time to sew a quilt.
You know what's funny? Robin Williams.
When a cat gets stuck in a washing machine.
City slickers.
Talking like Borat.
You know what's not funny? Safety.
Or making fun of the person trying to talk about safety.
Not nice.
I must show people how dangerous offers can be. High five.
Now that's funny.
How do you make depression sexy?
How do you get people interested in depression?
That is the conon, conum, conumbre.
I got it.
Give me the number for the giant big box toy store.
Those warehouse guys think that we are all flabby middle management nerf balls.
Well, I'm going to show them that we have nerfs of steel.
You may be asking yourself, what am I doing on a trampoline?
Well, I thought I'd bounce here for a while, release some stress, and then move on with my day.
Not.
Here's a plan.
Dwight is going to gather all of the office workers and all of the warehouse guys.
We're going to have another safety seminar.
Only this time, where's Michael? Oh my God. He is on the roof.
Now I've got their attention.
I tell them about the cold hard facts of depression.
And then I say, hey, you ever seen a suicide?
And I jump.
And they freak out.
And they get to see the dangers of depression with their own eyes.
Nice side note, they might think, hey, I should have been nicer to Michael.
But that's not why I'm doing this.
And then I land on the trampoline, take a couple extra bounces for fun.
I climb off, walk around the corner. Ta-freaking-da!
So then the next movie moves to the top of the queue.
So number five becomes number four, number six becomes number five, number three becomes number two, et cetera, et cetera.
And let's just say that I just sent back Love Actually, which was awesome.
And they sent me Uptown Girls, which is also awesome.
But guess what? Now I want to see Love Actually again.
But it's at the bottom of the queue. Oh no, what do I do?
What I do is this. I go online, I go click, click, click.
And I change the order of the queue so that I can see Love Actually as soon as I want to.
It's so easy, Ryan.
Do you really not know how Netflix works?
I guess I forgot.
You're such a dip.
Ryan, well done. Two minutes, 42 seconds.
Additionally, Pam, you win ten because she said awesome 12 times.
And Jim, you win five because she mentioned six romantic comedies.
You know, guys, I recently learned some pretty cool stuff about the difference between feeling something and acting on that thing.
Can you tell Andy to focus on the springs, please?
Yeah, Drew?
Yes, bosses.
You know, Drew, why don't you go inside? Dwight, come here.
Where should we put this?
OK, turn around and do a broad jump for me on go. Ready?
Go. One missus.
OK, you went that far on a one missus.
Ippy would take you to here.
This trajectory times the propulsion from your quadriceps would be about three Mississippi, maybe three and a quarter.
So one missus, correct? Ippy. Two Mississippi. Three Mississippi. E. Right here.
OK, good. Thank you.
I'll take our time. Do this right.
OK, let's do this thing. I'll go summon the troops.
Maybe we should test this first. Let him in style. Throw a TV over.
We measured it once.
Go buy some watermelons.
Feedless?
Just...
Creed is eating an apple. I found a potato.
Hey Creed.
Hi.
Nice.
I don't know this place as well as I thought I did. I'm getting cleaned out.
Hello? Hi Bob the Ants.
That's three times in ten minutes.
Where's my five dollars?
You are my little teddy bear.
My mom's.
I always knew my co-workers were annoying. I never realized I could profit from it.
Go ahead Bob Vance. Call Phyllis all day.
Ready? Let's do it. Drop that sucker.
Yeah. Bingo! Whoa whoa whoa!
Deactivate the car alarm. Clean up the mess.
Okay. Find out whose car that is.
If it's Stan Lee's call the offices of James P. Albini. See if he handles hate crimes.
Got it. Also take apart the trampoline sticking in the baler.
We're not allowed to use the baler.
Have Patch do it or the sea monster.
I'm on it.
Let's go.
I'm temporarily lifting the shun.
Thank you.
Means nothing. I need you to do something for me.
Anything.
Okay calm down. I need you to acquire an inflatable house and or castle.
You mean a moon bounce.
What do you think? You've got an hour.
Okay. I mean I need petty cash.
Shunning resumed.
Do you want a drawbridge?
Unshun.
Yeah that sounds good. Reshun.
Oh yeah this is much better. Safer. Excellent decision.
Yes. Thank you for seeing that.
When you land try and land like an eight year old.
These bouncy castles are not designed for adults.
I don't know if I want to do this.
You want to do another test? I got plenty of watermelons in my trunk.
No. No more. The tests are going terrible.
If we keep doing them I'm not going to want to jump.
This is about doing. Not thinking.
Right. Doing. Totally doing. Rock and roll.
Rock and roll. That's right. I'm not thinking.
Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah.
Woo. Woo. sauam.
Woo. Woo.
Woo.
I'm ready to do this.
I'm ready to make a point.
Hey guys listen up.
Michael is up on the roof and acting strange.
Whoa. What's the situation?
Unshun.
I think he's suffering from depression.
Reshun.
Hey. When's the shunning thing going to end?
Unshun. Never. Reshun.
I think he wants you all to come out to the parking lot and watch him die.
Is it nice outside?
It's gorgeous. Let's go.
Do I need my jacket?
No. Really it's very nice. Come on.
Will I be too warm in a long sleeve tee?
Everyone's going to be finding exactly what they're wearing. Let's go.
Let's go.
Come on. Hurry up you guys.
My life.
Oh my life.
Michael. What's wrong?
Everything's wrong.
The stress of my modern office has caused me to go into a depression.
Depression?
Isn't that just a fancy word for feeling bummed out?
Dwight you ignorant slut.
Depression is a very serious illness.
Over 32,000 people die from depression.
It's a very serious illness.
Over 32,000 people commit suicide every year.
According to a 2004 study.
Is that the last year the data was available?
Yes.
My head is in such pain and turmoil.
Don't do anything rash.
Dwight where are the warehouse guys?
I didn't.
I didn't think you needed them for this part.
Okay.
That's.
You said to just.
That's the whole point dummy.
Okay I'm on it.
Okay?
Michael go ahead we're listening.
I'm going to wait.
I don't want to say this twice.
It's too painful and I'm too depressed.
Attention blue collar workers.
What are the odds that this isn't in any way real?
I'd say like 10,000 to one.
Okay I'd like 10 bucks on those odds.
I'd like 10 bucks on those odds.
If someone gives you 10,000 to one on anything.
You take it.
If John Mellencamp ever wins an Oscar.
I am going to be a very rich dude.
Michael is up on the roof and he's acting strange.
Oh my life.
Michael what's wrong?
Everything is wrong Dwight.
The stress of my modern office has made me depressed.
Depressed? Isn't that just a fancy word for feeling bummed out?
Dwight you ignorant slut.
Well you know the first performance was a little off.
But I really think they hit their stride in the second show.
Might even bring my parents tomorrow to the matinee.
And that is why I am going to jump off this roof.
Excuse me.
My favorite part.
This is just offensive.
At least we're outside.
Hey check it out there's a castle over there.
Oh my god there is a castle.
No there's nothing to see over there people.
There's nothing to see.
They found a castle Michael.
Damn it.