How do I explain this to Jan?
Um, well, basically it's like a really big party and everybody gets super dressed up
and there's a bunch of different gods and each of the gods has a special power
like the Care Bears, you know, except-
Oh, please stop talking. Three words or less.
It's like an Indian Halloween.
An Indian Halloween.
Okay, great.
Tonight, one of our most ethnic coworkers, Kelly, has invited us all to a Dwali celebration
put on by her community.
What is Dwali, you may ask.
Well, to have Kelly explain it.
It's, I have, blah blah blah. It's so super fun and it's gonna be great.
A lot of gods with unpronounceable names.
Twenty minutes later you find out that it's essentially a Hindu Halloween.
Pam, could you put Jan on please?
Michael, you're on with Jan.
Hello, Jan.
Michael, what is this about you letting everyone leave work early today?
Well, I was letting everybody go to the big Diwali party.
What is Diwali?
What is Diwali? You don't know what Diwali is?
Wow, Jan, I'm surprised.
It's the Hindu Festival of Lights. I just assumed you'd be familiar with it.
It's the most sacred and honored Hindu holiday in the world.
It's like Christmas, Easter and Halloween rolled into one.
I bet you're not even aware that our own Kelly Kapoor, who works in...
Customer service.
Customer service is a Hindu person.
Of course I know Kelly. I thought she was Muslim.
What? I'm not Muslim.
Well, I think it sounds lovely. I think it sounds like a good idea.
You do?
Yes, of course. It's important to celebrate our company's rich diversity.
And in fact, Michael, if you had planned better, we might have been able to charter a bus to the event.
Wow, I didn't know about that.
Or been a sponsor for the party itself.
For Kelly, that seems a bit much.
Hey, one person is an integral part of the fabric.
She's so wonderful.
Yeah, you should see her naked.
I had promised Carol a romantic evening on the town.
I wanted to take her on this spooky hayride thing, but it was like $70 a person.
And she's allergic to hay.
So I said, pop a Claritin and I will spot you the 70 bucks.
And he's like, I don't like to borrow money or take unnecessary medication.
And I'm like, well, you're really not going to like what I slipped in your drink last night.
And she was like, what the hell are you talking about?
I'm like, I'm kidding. I didn't put a roof over your head.
And we laughed so hard.
It was hilarious. Oh.
So yes, I'm very excited about the Diwali party.
There we go.
Nice dress, Ryan.
It's not a dress. It's a kertha.
Okay.
You look so handsome.
You really do. I love the material.
I know.
How come you didn't give me one?
I...
So between Meredith, Minnie Van, and if I borrow Bob's Yukon, that should fit about 12 people.
I actually might not go.
Feeling kind of tired.
Do you want to make Appletinis and watch Sex and the City at my place?
Oh, I don't know. I haven't decided yet.
I know when you break up with someone, you're supposed to be really social, get back out there.
I'm just not sure that out there includes the Lackawanna County Hindu American Associations
Family Diwali Celebration at West Scranton High School.
I don't know why we're going to this. It's not a calendar holiday.