I'm hungry.
Movie Monday!
The only cure I know for the Monday blues is...
varsity blues.
Let's go!
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
Everybody here?
Yes.
Where's Angela?
Dwight.
Hello.
What does it matter with you?
Would you get Angela, please?
Angela from accounting?
Yes, please.
I'll go look for her.
Movie Monday started with training videos, but we went through those pretty fast.
Then we watched a medical video.
Since then, it's been half our installments of various movies,
with the exception of an episode of Entourage, which Michael made us watch six times.
Entourage!
There you are.
Michael wants everyone inside for Movie Monday.
I don't care. He's wasting everyone's time.
No, he's not. Michael knows exactly what he's doing.
How can you say that?
He was the top salesman in this company's history. I'll never even come close to matching his numbers.
He's not a salesman anymore.
In my opinion, a good manager protects his employees from verbal abuse and manhandling.
Like you would do if you were manager.
Well, maybe not all manhandling.
Kevin, would you like to do the scenes from last week?
Yes.
Why him? Don't whine. Get the windows.
Previously on Varsity Blues.
Okay, Billy Bob got a head injury, but Coach made him play.
So then Lance, he gets sacked, and he's out for the year.
Hello?
Not everyone approves of Movie Monday. I won't say who.
I don't approve. I don't.
Hello?
Let's go after that time man. Let's go, let's go. Let's go.
Hey, man. Hope you're back to the milk beds.
How would a movie increase productivity, Michael? How on earth would it do that?
People work faster after.
Magically?
No. They have to, to make up for the time they lost watching the movie.
No.
Kitchen.
Michael is going to get us all fired. You sat back and let him play that dumb movie, and now Jan has peeped off and we're all going to lose our jobs.
That's not going to happen.
You know she has it out for him now.
That's not his fault. He had to follow his heart.
Ever since Michael dumped Jan for Carol, Jan's been bitching out on him. Reject a woman and she will never let it go, one of the many defects of their kind. Also weak arms.
Dwight, you should be running this office.
Michael would never let me.
It's not up to Michael. It's Jan's call. Talk to her.
I can never do that.
Fine. Sit back and do nothing and let us all get fired.
I know that patience and loyalty are good and virtuous traits, but sometimes I just think you need to grow a pair.
The shrewts are a very loyal breed, but I also have Mannheim blood from my German grandmother, and the Mannheims knew when to cut and run. No sense going down with a losing regime.
But the shrewt blood, it's amazing that when these two bloods mixed, that the whole thing didn't exist.