It's kind of blurry.
That's better.
Question.
What kind of bear is best?
That's a ridiculous question.
False.
Black bear.
That's debatable.
There are basically two schools of thought.
Fact.
Bears eat beets.
Nope.
Bears.
Beets.
Battlestar Galactica.
Bears do not...
What is going on?
What are you doing?
Last week I was in a drug store and I saw these glasses.
Uh, four dollars.
And it only cost me seven dollars to recreate the rest of the ensemble and that's
a grand total of...
Eleven dollars.
You know what?
Imitation is the most sincere form of flattery so I thank you.
Identity theft is not a joke, Jim.
Millions of families suffer every year.
Michael!
Oh, that's funny.
Yes, I understand.
Can I transfer you to customer relations?
Absolutely.
I couldn't be more sorry about this.
I know.
I am upset.
Don't I sound upset?
It is disgusting.
I totally agree.
Well, we're going to be recalling all of that paper.
We have a crisis.
Apparently a disgruntled employee at the paper mill decided that it would be funny to put
an obscene watermark on our 24 pound cream letter stock.
500 boxes has gone out with the image of a beloved cartoon duck performing a comedy
performance, performing unspeakable acts upon a certain cartoon mouse that a lot of people
like.
I've never got a fan.
Oh my god, I am so sorry.
That is so messed up.
Everyone here is so upset.
You have no idea.
And rest assured, your voice has been heard.
Okay, I'll be thinking about you all day.
Customer services, Kelly!
Oh my god, I am so sorry.
That is so messed up.
Everyone here is so upset.
You have no idea.
And rest assured, your voice has been heard.
Okay, I'll be thinking about you all day.
Customer services, this is Kelly!
Oh my god, I am so sorry.
That is so messed up.
Everyone here is so upset.
You have no idea.
I'll be thinking about you all day.
Customer services, this is Kelly!
Oh my god, I am so sorry.
That is so messed up.
Everyone here is so upset.
You have no idea.
I'll be thinking about you all day.
Customer services, this is Kelly!
Oh my god, I am so sorry.
That is so messed up.
Everyone here is so upset.
You have no idea.
I'll be thinking about you all day.
Everybody in here!
Stapped!
No time to lose.
Cry Man Squad, F and C, double time.
Cry Man Squad?
Crisis Management Squad.
F and C, double time?
Front and center, twice as fast as you would normally go.
Any other questions?
One more.
Why are you talking like that?
To save time, Jim.
Actually, I think you can make the argument
that it wastes time.
Yeah, she has a good point.
I mean, for example, with the last thing you said,
by the time you explained it, it actually took us a lot of time.
You know what?
Forget it.
The key to a crisis is dealing with it right away.
Like that aspirin company that sent out the poisoned aspirin
in the regular aspirin bottles.
If you don't act fast, you will lose customers.
Where is Creed?
Creed?
Quality assurance.
Your job, I really think you screwed the pooch on this one,
Creed, because of you.
The entire company is in jeopardy.
Every week, I'm supposed to take four hours
and do a quality spot check at the paper mill.
And of course, the one year I blow it off, this happens.
We have a lot of angry customers out there.
This puts us at threat level midnight.
Accounting, you are on customer service duty today.
That's really not our job.
Midnight, Oscar.
Don't worry, Kelly will be training you first.
Kelly's training us?
This day is bananas, B-A-N-A-N-A-S.
This day is bananas, B-A-N-A.
I don't have a headache.
I'm just preparing.
Jim, big fire in your house.
Your client, Dunmore High School,
sent out their prom invitations on this paper.
Went home to all the kids.
Yeah, I gotta call that on.
No, no, no, no, not good enough.
This is a Keystone account.
I want you in the school, in person.
I want you to bring a partner.
I'll go.
No, sweet cheeks, we need somebody
who's actually made a sale.
Andy, you go.
William Doolittle at your service, AKA Will Do.
Yeah, I'm definitely gonna go along.
No, no, I need two men on this.
That's what she said.
No time, but she did.
No time!
Guys, get on this.
Dwight, I want you to be in charge of the press conference.
Yes, you're entering the no-spin zone.
We're having a press conference?
No, Pam, the press are just gonna find out by themselves.
Not.
Here's the thing, when a company screws up,
best thing to do is call a press conference.
Alert the media, and then you control the story.
Wait for them to find out, and the story controls you.
That's what happened to O.J.
I have invited Barbara Allen, one of our oldest clients,
to come in here and meet with me for a personal apology.
The press wants a story, I will give them a story.
Oh, did the press ask for a story?
Here is your headline.
Scrin area paper company Dunder Mifflin
apologizes to valued client.
Some companies still know how business is done.
Okay?
Battle stations, everybody, let's go, go, go, go, go, go!
Hello, CNN?
I need to speak to your Scranton area bureau chief.
All right, then, the bureau chief
for the greater Wilkes-Barre area.
How about Lackawanna County?
Okay, northeastern Pennsylvania, then.
This is extremely urgent.
No, you put your supervisor on the phone.
Yes, hello, Creed Braden,
quality assurance, Dunder Mifflin Scranton.
I was supposed to meet with one of your floor managers
last week for a quality inspection,
and he or she wasn't there.
And I'm trying to remember who it was.
Who wasn't there last week?
Debbie Brown, and which day was that?
Wednesday the 11th, perfect.
The only difference between me and a homeless man is this job.
I will do whatever it takes to survive,
like I did when I was a homeless man.
Customer service isn't like accounting.
It's not just typing numbers into a calculator
and then it tells you an answer.
We do a lot more than that.
Okay, or handout checks or whatever it is you do.
Look, I know the reason that you guys became accountants
is because you think that people don't like you.
But guess what?
From now on, you guys are not losers.
So give yourselves a round of applause.
I wonder how many phone calls you're missing
while you're teaching us to answer phone calls.
I know, right?
Probably a lot.
Can you just tell us what we need to do so we can go?
Okay, Angela, I love your enthusiasm.
All you need to know how to do is pick up the phone
and say, customer service, this is Kelly,
except don't say Kelly, say your own name.
Or if you're bored, you can just make up a name.
Like one time, I said I was Bridget Jones
and I took like this for the whole conversation.
Oh, can I be Australian, mate?
Absolutely.
Hello, mate.
I like ice cream.
I need a boyfriend.
I like ice cream too, mate.
Alligators and dingo babies.
All you need to do is make sure
that you make a connection with the customer.
They just wanna know that you're sorry.
Do that and you'll be fine.
Make sense?
Mm-hmm.
Okay, role playing time.
All right, I think I'm trained.
Ooh, can I be a pirate?
Bear me.
What's that?
Amy, that water.
I always say bear me.
Gets a laugh like a quarter of the time.
So how's, what's her name?
You knew her name.
Who, Karen?
Yeah, she's only one of my oldest friends.
How's the apartment hanging?
It's fine.
Nice.
Check out this sunshine, man.
Global warming, right?
Today was supposed to be really cold, I bet.
What about music?
You got any music?
Yeah, I should've said so.
Riddity-diddity, gimme the beat, boys, and free my soul.
I wanna get lost in your rock and roll and drift away.
Riddity-diddity, bittity-diddity, gimme the beat, boys,
and free my little soul.
You know, I was thinking more like a CD or a CD.
You're cool, dude.
My girlfriend made an awesome mix, bear me that disc.
Lord, bear me strength.
So tune in when we get in there,
let's do a really good job, okay?
So that really need to be said.