Hey.
Oh, what's this?
That is a demerit.
Jim Halpert, tardiness.
Oh, I love it already.
You've got to learn, Jim. You are second in command, but that does not put you above the law.
Oh, I understand. And I also have lots of questions. Like, what does a demerit mean?
Let's put it this way. You do not want to receive three of those.
Lay it on me.
Three demerits, and you'll receive a citation.
Now, that sounds serious.
Oh, it is serious. Five citations, and you're looking at a violation.
Four of those, and you'll receive a verbal warning.
Keep it up, and you're looking at a written warning.
Two of those, that'll land you in a world of hurt.
In the form of a disciplinary review, written up by me and placed on the desk of my immediate superior.
Which would be me.
That is correct.
Okay, I want a copy on my desk by the end of the day, or you will receive a full dissadulation.
What's a dissad... what's that?
Oh, you don't want to know.
Hey, Phyllis. You all right?
I think I just got flashed.
What? Really?
In the parking lot.
Oh my God.
Move!
Okay, I'll call the real police.
What happened? What can I do to help?
Okay.
I'll check the web.
Thank you.
The police are on it. They say they've already had three calls.
Can you tell us what happened?
Um, I was walking to the building and this man asked me for directions.
And he was holding a map.
And when I walked over, he had it out on the map.
Phyllis, you're a married woman.
The guy was just hanging brain. I mean, what's all the fuss?
If that's flashing, then lock me up.
Hey, what's going on?
Phyllis got flashed in the parking lot.
Okay, you need to stop that right now.
Phyllis.
Sure?
What's happening?
Some guy exposed himself to Phyllis in the parking lot.
Really? Is she okay?
Yeah, Bob Vance took her for a walk to calm down.
Okay.
Phyllis, you say?
Hmm.
What is so funny?
Um, I mean, did you even see Pam?
Or Karen from behind?
I'm guessing not.
I'm sorry.
It's pretty funny when you think about it.
Oh, not really.
It's disgusting and demeaning.
Okay, masters of comedy. A guy dropped his pants.
Have you ever been to the circus?
Okay.
He's back!
Hey, what's going on? There's a police car in there.
What? Oh.
What's going on?
Oh, Phyllis got flashed.
I don't think laughing about it's an appropriate response.
Oh, come on. We were laughing at Phyllis, but she's not even here.
So no harm, no foul.
I don't think the woman in the sauce...
Incidentally, where were you during all of this?
Maybe you're the flasher.
I was at a parent-teacher conference.
Uh-huh. Prove it. Let's see your penis.
I...you know, as that was coming out of my mouth,
I knew that it was wrong.
In all the excitement, I forgot that my primary goal is to keep people safe.
Women can't have fun if they don't feel safe.
For example, Jan and I have a safe word in case things go too far.
Foliage.
And if one of us says that word, the other one has to stop.
Although last time, she pretended she didn't hear me.
So how are you liking the Wall Street Journal subscription?
Love it.
Are you reading it every day like we decided you would?
Uh, yes, I am.
Good, good. It's the best business reporting, isn't it?
Uh, yeah, it's okay. I just...I don't think the cartoons are very funny.
Wait, wait. What cartoons?
The cartoon that goes with each article.
This one says Melcharmazen. I don't...I don't know. I guess I get it.
You should really start recycling.
Hey, um, Michael, come over after work tonight, okay? I miss your body.
I don't know. I feel...I drive a lot.
I'm spending a fortune on gas and tolls.
I'll give you $200, and if I get up before you, I'll leave it on the dresser.
Um, that...I don't know. That makes me kind of uncomfortable.
$300?
I...I don't know.
Whatever. Just let my assistant know if you're coming over so you can get more vodka, okay?
Hunter, are you on?
You got it, Jen.
Employees of this office are very small and delicate.
Deserve protection from local pervs.
Better a thousand innocent men are locked up than one guilty man roam free.
I am sick over this thing.
Those people out there are clearly afraid.
And that can't happen. Not in my house.
Agreed. Let me show you what I've been working on.
Okay.
There are several penises there. I'd love Phyllis to run her eyes over.
And I'll see if we can catch this pervert.
This is the last thing that Phyllis needs to see right now, Dwight.
Look at that one.
Dwight, are those your pants?
That's a Polaroid.
Attention, everybody. Dwight has something he would like to say.
Due to a recent incident involving Phyllis, a man, a map, and his penis,
I think you know what I'm referring to,
Michael has authorized me to form an emergency anti-flashing task force.
Question. Won't that interfere with your other task forces?
Answer. No, because this is being given priority one.
This is a petition for the business park to upgrade the security cameras
as well as install two floodlights in the parking lot.
And I know what you're thinking.
Won't that just shed more light on the penises?
But that is a risk we have to take.
Pam, you can draw, kind of.
Why don't you work with Phyllis on drawing a picture of the exposure
that I can post around the community?
Phyllis?
Phyllis. Sorry. I've got penises on the brain.
Back to work, everybody.
I don't often miss Roy, but I can tell you one thing.
I wish someone had flashed me when I was with Roy,
because that would have been the ass-kicking of the year.
Especially if it had been Jim.
He would not have wanted me to have seen Jim's...
Oh, I am saying a lot of things.
I'm sorry.
Thanks.
Hey, good looking. What you got cooking?
I got nothing cooking. It's cooked.
It's borscht and it's served cold.
Hey, listen, I'm sure everyone's already told you,
but your presentation out there is pretty inspiring stuff.
Must be nice being a woman around here,
knowing they have a protector in you.
If you were trying to kiss my ass, I would not suggest it.
Believe me, you do not want to kiss this ass.
Borscht, according to Dwight, is best served cold.
You know what else is best served cold?
Yeah, gazpacho.
You see what I'm doing?
I am establishing a mutual love of cold soups.
This is the first step in my plan to win Dwight's trust.
I should make you my Vichyssoise.
I will never be your Vichyssoise.
I didn't really get a good look.
That's okay. I don't feel like answering phones.
Did you guys see this memo that Dwight sent out?
Women will be sent home if they wear makeup or heels exceeding one quarter inch.
Females are not allowed to speak to strangers unless given written authorization by Dwight Schrute.
This is ridiculous.
Attention, I am removing all bananas from the kitchen.
Dwight, this memo that you distributed is insulting.
Desperate times call for desperate measures.
Sleeves down to the wrists, button up collars, and muted colors.
Nobody dresses like that.
Okay, you know something Dwight, we are not the terrorists.
Why don't you just take these women, put them in a burlap sack, and hit them with a stick?
Because that's what you're doing.
I celebrate these women. They deserve the right to dress as they please.
If Pam wants to show more cleavage, she should be able to. I encourage that.
Look, it's really simple. We just want you guys to treat us with respect.
See? That's what we're talking about. Did you hear that Dwight?
Yes. Did you hear that Michael?
No Dwight. Respect. R-E-S-P-S-V-E-T.
Find out what it means to me.
Alright, you know what? That's it.
Conference room, five minutes. Women's appreciation.
Wait a second, how are you qualified for that?
Oh, I don't know, James. Did I come from a woman? Have I slept with a woman? More than one?
Less than three.
That is not current.
You know what? Why doesn't Oscar run the meeting? He's a homosexual.
Why don't you run the meeting? You play with dolls.
Those are collectible action figures and they're worth more than your car.
You know what? I am the expert. I will conduct it. I know the crap out of women.
I would like to apologize for all of the men who thought this was a laughing matter.
Are we still discussing this? I say again, what is the big deal?
Nobody likes to be flashed. When Meredith flashed me at that Christmas party, I nearly vomited.
I don't remember doing that. What a surprise.
Okay, no catfights. Please, let's... My point is... My point is...
A penis. When seen in the right context is the most wonderful sight for a woman.
But in the wrong context, it is like a monster movie.
Alien.
Why don't you shut it... Shut up.
Okay, so what I want to engage us in today is a hardcore discussion about women's problems and issues and situations.
Magazines and TV shows and movies portray women as skinny, tall goddesses.
Well, look around. Are women like that? No. No, they are not.
Even the hot ones aren't really that skinny.
So what does that say? That says that you women are up against it and it is criminal.
Society doesn't care. Society sucks. I don't even consider myself a part of society.
FYI, because I am so angry over all of this.
If it were up to me, you ladies would be the fashion models.
Yes, Indy. Then the fashion models could come here and work with me.
What you're saying is extremely misogynistic.
Yes. Thank you. That was not necessary, but I appreciated it. And it proves my point. Women can do anything.
I'm saying that you're being sexist.
No, I'm being misogynistic. That is insane. I am not being sexist.
That's the same thing. Yes.
When I got my haircut chart, you asked me if I was a lesbian.
Because wow, that was one possible explanation as to why you got that haircut.
And when we get mad, you always ask us if we're on our periods.
I have to know whether you're serious or not.
I wish I could menstruate. If I could menstruate, I wouldn't have to deal with idiotic calendars anymore.
I'd just be able to count down from my previous cycle. Plus I'd be more in tune with the moon and the tides.
Orgasms! Why can't women have them? Yep.
No, I'm not a lawyer, but I don't think this is the place to do this.
Sometimes I imagine what it would be like to be a woman.
I have a full length mirror in my bathroom. And before I get dressed, I will tuck myself between my legs just to see.
And it's uncomfortable. So maybe I do understand.
Can we just get back to work? Okay, yes.
This is not work talk. You're right, you're right. And you know why?
It's because of where we are. This is a masculine environment.
We need to find a place where you feel comfortable. You know where we're going to go?
Steamtown Mall.
We're going to the mall. Bye Ryan! Bye!
Frankly, it's kind of insulting. But I have a bunch of stuff I need to return to my car. So I can do that.
Malls are just awful and humiliating. They're just store after store of these horrible sales people making a big fuss out of an adult shopping in a junior section.
There are petite adults who are sort of smaller who need to wear maybe a kid size 10.
Okay, let's go ladies of Dunder Mifflin. Hey, we should have a calendar printed up, Pam. Put that in my good idea folder.
Let's go!
Are you finished with the sketch? Yeah.
Hmm, doesn't seem like the type.
Phyllis got a good look.
Let's go, fall out. Let's go. Move, move, move, move, move.
I got a shotgun!
Oh, Merritt, slow down. We're not going to get there any faster if we're dead.
Thanks, I know how to drive.
Oh, yeah, you really shouldn't litter. My car, my rules.
I plan on plastering this pervert's face everywhere. You can run, but you cannot hide.
Hey, Jim. You want to go in the women's bathroom?
No, thank you though.
You aren't curious?
Not really, I've seen a bathroom before.
Yeah, but it's every guy's fantasy.
I think you mean a girl's locker room. And in the fantasy there's usually girls in it.
Yeah. I'm going in.
Go crazy.
Oh my god.
I really appreciate your letting me work alongside you so closely today.
Of course you do, Moonface. That's because you're a preppy freak, you're the office pariah, and nobody likes you.
So, start hanging these all around the building.
This guy looks like a real deviant.
No duh, that's why we've got to catch him. Start hanging those.
Aye, Captain.
More like aye, aye, General.
Let me be clear. There's only one thing that's important to me and it's not friendship. It's dominance.
And I think I know a thing or two about dominating.
Okay, I lived with the dominatrix for three years in Stanford.
Mistress Lila taught me more than any college professor I ever had while attending Cornell, which is where I went to school.
I don't think she's going to make it.