Damn, lost another file.
Gonna have to reboot again.
Hey, Dwight, do you want an Altoid?
What do you think?
In school, we learned about this scientist who trained dogs to salivate at the sound of a bell by feeding them whenever a bell rang.
So for the past couple weeks I've been conducting a similar experiment.
Dwight, do you want an Altoid?
Okay.
Altoid?
Sure.
Ben Twight?
Yes.
What are you doing?
I...
What?
I don't know.
My mouth tastes so bad all of a sudden.
Ugh.
Always the bridesmaids, right ladies?
Okay, for this next one everybody hop out. Just Phyllis and Dad.
Actually, let's bring Mom back in and the sisters and you and you and you.
Great.
Phyllis is getting married and I am in the wedding party.
She has asked me to push her father's wheelchair down the aisle, so basically I am co-giving away the bride.
Since I pay her salary it is like I am paying for the wedding, which I'm happy to do.
It's a big day for Phyllis, but it's an even bigger day for me, employer of the bride.
Yes, I put Michael in my wedding.
It was the only way I could think to get six weeks off from my honeymoon.
No one else has ever gotten six weeks before.
Phyllis ended up using the exact same invitations as Roy and me.
So it was kind of like being invited to my own wedding and I was like, wait, I thought I called that off.
So what's in the box?
A toaster. You?
A toaster.
Unbelievable.
Hello Angela.
Hi Dwight.
You look as beautiful as the Queen of England.
Thank you. Don't linger, break left.
Left.
The Shrewts have their own traditions.
We usually marry standing in our own graves.
It makes the funerals very romantic, but the weddings are a bleak affair.
I really enjoy old fashioned weddings.
I'm offended by modern ones, so we'll see.
Those flowers are nice.
Yeah, P&R.
Phyllis and Robert.
Of course.
Also Pam and Roy.
There she is.
I swear Phyllis, you are as beautiful as the first day you started work at Dunder Mifflin.
Thanks Michael, that's sweet. Same as when you said it outside.
How you doing?
Are you excited?
Yes, very.
Me too.
If you need to vomit, that is okay. I did.
Do you want to talk about tonight?
No.
Because I know you're probably worried about pleasing Bob. A lot of pressure.
Phyllis, did you break wind?
It's okay.