Jim, could you come in here, please?
I'm sorry.
Hi, Jim.
Hello.
I am Harvey, a computer.
Jim sucks.
I'm sorry.
Oh, wow!
That's so rude.
I'm sorry. I can't control him.
Yeah, he can. You know I can't pay him.
For this? Pay him!
Pam, you look very hot today.
Pam, meet Harvey. This is Michael's new friend.
Great.
Me so horny, me love you long tim.
Whoa.
That is gross.
Who's long tim?
Damn it.
Long time. Me lob yoy long time.
Well, Yoy should bring long tim in one day.
Nope. I'd love to meet long tim.
Yeah, right? Yeah.
You ruined a funny jokyu.
Get out of my offive.
Okay.
Bye, Harvey.
Boobs.
My house isMusic
Angela, that License
That was merit
accounts
that 값
Did you send them?
Is it, Kevin?
Do you really not know? Because it is a big deal.
Five of us transferred from Stanford.
There's two of us left. Me and Karen.
It's like we're touring Willy Wonka's chocolate factory and dropping off one by one.
Well, guess what? I'm not falling in a chocolate river.
And then there were two.
To what?
Stay with me.
Tony.
Martin.
Hannah.
You and me.
I kinda like it here. So...
Eddie Bernard's not going down without a fight.
Huh?
Dwight's still not here?
Oh, he's gonna miss out on all the fun.
You leave a message?
Yes.
What'd you say?
A version of what you told me to say.
You told him his ass was grass and that I'm the lawn mower.
Yep. I just didn't use those words.
Well, okay.
Just tell him to come in when he's here.
Alright?
Have you guys seen Dwight? I really need him for something.
Dwight is late.
Wow. That's really frustrating for everyone. Not just me.
Why? What do you need him for?
He has a bag of really important work things that I need for my job. To do my job.
So, I think it's too late already.
Yeah.
Yep.
Alright.
I'm gonna level with you.
There's no bag of important things.
I made it up.
Punctuality is something I demand from my employees. I need them to show up on time.
So when I finally show up, we can get started right away.
Everything okay?
It's fine. You are in the clear.
Thank you.
I don't want those.
Dwight, care to join us finally? Thank you.
Hey Dwight, pass the Tartie sauce. Get it, Michael?
Yes.
Okay. Here is the dream team. My sales dream team.
Today we are going to team up for sales calls. This was Andy's idea.
And you're literally going to double team them. We are going to double team the crap out of them.
Satisfaction guaranteed.
Saying that we should double things is not a great idea.
Oh yeah. Why don't we have two heads and four arms?
And women have four boobs.
Eight boobs.
Sixteen boobs.
Andy, since this was your idea, you get to pick first.
Hmm. Well, let me think about this for a minute. Oh, I don't know. Michael Scott.
Oh.
PhD. Doctor of sales.
Well, I appreciate that. That's very gracious of you.
Well, it is very gracious of you to accept.
Well, thank you. Okay.
Andy is trying to reinvent the wheel. Why? The wheel works.
Idiot. I am trying to reinvent the roof.
Give me a couple years. You'll see.
Phyllis, our resident senior.
We're the same age. And I'll pick Karen.
Oh, thanks.
Good. Next up, the super fly himself, Stan Lee.
Pass.
You can't pass. You've got to pick somebody.
I'll take the kid.
I'm very flattered. I was his second choice after pass.
So that just leaves Dwight and Jim.
Okay, wait. Does anyone want to trade?
Yeah. Trade.
Dwight and I used to go on sales calls all the time. In fact, I have a picture to remember that time.
Oh, young Jim, there is just so much I need to warn you about.
And yet, tragically, I cannot.
It's just like the old days.
Yeah. You drive me there, I dominate, you drive me back.
Yep. Just like the old days.
I already pushed it.
Yeah, well, I pushed it better.
Let's go, people.
Oh, no, no. Don't want to risk it.
What does Jim bring to a sales call?
Nothing. What do I bring?
A fierce competitive attitude. Plus an extra jacket and roadside boots.