The Stanford branch is closing,
and everybody's just packing up their stuff.
Andy Bernard made these tasteful hats.
That's the other thing you have to watch out...
Yo, Tuna, I want to talk to you about this new boss, Michael Scott.
Yeah?
So what's he like? Likes, dislikes, favorite sports,
favorite movies, favorite men's magazines.
You know what? I think you just need to meet him.
Playing your cards close to the vest, I get it.
Good luck over there, Tuna.
Cross me and I will destroy you.
Sounds good, Andy.
This is going to be an adventure?
Yes, this is going to be very interesting.
All right, I'm out of here. See you later?
Rod.
Hey, is that Josh's computer?
What?
Hey. Hey.
How'd the run go?
Pretty good. I finished.
That's great.
Why is that great?
Because he accomplished something.
What was your mile time?
About seven.
I could beat that on a skateboard.
Well, that has wheels.
Yeah, well, my feet don't, and I could still crush that time.
Really, Dwight? How fast are you?
Let's just put it this way.
Last weekend, I outrun the whole team.
I beat the whole team?
How fast are you?
Let's just put it this way.
Last weekend, I outran a black pepper snake.
Really?
I am fast.
To give you a reference point,
I'm somewhere between a snake and a mongoose.
And a panther.
Man, what is taking Toby so long?
Oh, I'll just time him later.
And you'll compare the times?
Yeah. Are you ready?
No.
Set, go!
My grades are really tight. I can't...
Am I being mean to Dwight?
I don't know.
I did just make him run around the building,
and I have no intention of timing him.
This isn't even a stopwatch. It's a digital thermometer.
He does make my life harder sometimes, and on purpose.
Like, he tried to put meters on the bathroom stalls
as a way of bringing in more money for the company.
Hey, three more laps to go!
You gotta pick it up if you're gonna beat Toby!
I should probably get back to work.
Yeah.
I'm gonna go.
Who's here?
Name tag?
Yes, please.
Karen Filippelli.
Karen Fili... Karen Filippelli!
Probably Italian.
Possibly Filipina.
Or as I like to put it,
my family is doubling in size.
That's all I'm gonna say about it,
because I have a gigantic performance ahead of me,
and I have to get into my head and focus.
And this is... Don't tell me.
Martin...
Na... Na... Na...
Nash.
Martin Nash.
Male, age 37.
Good.
Mocha complexion.
Supplier relations.
Either caught a fish or was standing next to a man
who caught a fish in Key West, Florida.
What are you talking about?
It wasn't clear on the Google Image search.
Righteous.
Who's next?
That's Andy Bernard.
Andy Bernard.
If I were you...
St. Bernard.
I would fire Anthony Gardner...
What?
...before noon to consolidate power.
I'm not firing somebody on the first day.
No, no, no, not somebody. Gardner.
The Japanese camp guards of World War II
always chose one man to kill
whenever a batch of new prisoners arrived.
I always wondered how they chose the man who was to die.
I think I would have been good at choosing the person.