Can you confirm that the straps are tight?
Yes.
But this...
And now the chains.
A lot of people think that Magic Camp is just for kids.
And that's why so many other people in my class were kids.
Self-fulfilling prophecy.
It's really for anybody with a dream and a belief in magic
and a little extra time after school.
Magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic, magic.
And now Michael the Magic will attempt to escape from extreme bondage.
Can he do it? I don't see how he can.
I know how.
He'll dislocate his shoulder and slip his arm out.
No, no. Everyone, now count down with me.
Three!
Sorry, sorry, quick thing.
So is it true that if you can't get out, you don't want anyone to help you?
I will get out.
Oh, yes, I will.
So we shouldn't help you, no matter how much you might beg and plead?
No, all right. This is getting hot. So let's just do this, okay?
Ready? Three!
Two!
One!
Go!
Is everything okay, Michael?
Yes.
I cannot tell you how I plan to escape, other than by using magic.
That is the magician's code.
Separately, on an unrelated note, if you happen to find a small brass key...
All right, ready? Come on, guys. Early worm gets the worm.
Another worm? Are they friends?
This early bird gets the worm.
Pam, would you smell my drum?
No.
No?
Let me smell.
Good, not great.
Michael, you go to parties all the time. Why is tonight so special?
Well, tonight is so special because my boss's boss's boss, the CFO, not his initials, common mistake, is having a little shindig for all the managers in the company, and Jan and I are going as a couple for the first time.
So it's kind of our coming out party, really. And that is why tonight is so special.
Jimbo, last chance carpool.
Oh, no thanks. I think Karen and I will take my carpool.
Sure, might be a good idea.
Yeah.
We can all go together, we can save some gas, have fun. Long trip.
Thanks.
Oh.
Hi, spy.
Yeah.
Why don't I want to go? Didn't expect to need a reason, so let me think here.
I don't know any of these people. It's an obligation. I don't like talking paper in my free time or in my work time. And did I use the word pointless?
I think it's great that Jim was invited. It's important to have contact with the New York execs or they'll think that everyone here is like my...
Cole.
Okay, so promise that you'll wait until we leave the parking lot before you go to the bar.
Yes, boss.
See ya, Pam.
Hey, are you going to Port Richards?
Well, no.
You?
Maybe.
I'm going and sorry about the view. We're all going.
Hey, isn't there some rule against inter-office dating?
I am not doing your dirty work for you.
I hear whispering.
You gotta sign that. No, you gotta put your name in the corner. I've seen other artists do that. It's good, too, because you can know who paints what, you know?
Thanks for inviting me along.
Oh, sure. I really didn't give it any thought.
Wait, should you be going?
Hello, you.
Michael?
Hey, buttercup. I am on my way. I should be there in about 15...
Let me blow this party off.
That's what she said.
Am I on speakerphone?
Yes, you are.
Hello, Jan.
Hi, Dwight. Okay, Michael, take me off speakerphone.
No, no problem.
Okay, let's just go to a motel and just rip into each other like we did on the Black Sand Beach in Jamaica.
Okay, Jan, Jan, this party is actually a very big step for us.
Still on speaker?
Um, I don't know.
Is the camera still?
Maybe.
See you soon.
Okay.
Talk to you later, Jan.
Alright, bye.
Hey, Michael left early, so a bunch of us are gonna go to Poor Richards for happy hour. You should come.
I can't. My brother, he just unloaded the jet skis and kinda took a bath, so we're gonna get hammered.
Okay, well, we're going to a bar.
Hey, you have to come to stuff with me.
I'm serious. If you're gonna be my boyfriend, you have to do boyfriend things.
Okay.
I've decided that I'm going to be more honest. I'm gonna start telling people what I want directly.
So, look out world, cause old Pammy is getting what she wants.
And don't call me Pammy.
Beauty. Thank you, Sal.
Salada.
Thank you.
You're dressed exactly like the servants.
Shut up.
Okay, change shirts.
Wait.
I don't think yours will fit me.
I don't care.
Oh, wow.
Don't put my jacket on. Don't give me that.
That would have been really embarrassing.
Yes.
Crisis averted.
Okay.
Oh, that duck is so cute.
Hey, Pam.
Hey, guys.
Oscar, Angela.
I didn't think you guys would come.
Why wouldn't we come?
Because of reasons.
Are there carbs in vodka?
Hey, folks. What can I get you?
Oh, hey, Meredith. Another vodka?
Yeah. Jack, these are my co-workers.
Sup.
Ryan, Pam, Stanley, Kelly, Kevin, Creed. How'd I do?
Hmm. Gummy and much?
These wings are all fat and bone.
This place is disgusting.
Hi.
Actually, it's polite to arrive early and smart.
Only really good friends show up early.
Ergo defacto, go to a party early, become a really good friend.
Oh, a potato salad?
That's from both of us?
No, it's not.
Wonderful. Let's see where we can put this.
Oh, you know, you probably want to leave the cover on until the guests get here.
It's been sitting in my car all day.
The sun beating down on the mayonnaise.
Just...
You never know.
Kevin, you and Stacey set a date yet?
Yeah.
Oh, my God. When is it?
It's complicated.
I would appreciate some space on this.
Hey.
Hey. You made it.
You said it was important, so...
How's it going?
What's up, Pam?
Hey, Kenny. Sorry about the jet skis.
You guys want a round on me?
Yeah.
Yeah? Let's get you a drink.
Thanks, man.
Hi, Ryan.
Hey.
How are you doing? I've missed you.
I've missed you, too.
Don't you remember me?
Um, you gotta give me a hint.
Um, did you meet me at the gym?
No. Who the hell is Ryan talking to?
Are you a client of that or my friend?
I know.
Oh, not again.
Melissa!
Daddy!
Wait for me outside.
God, I'm so sorry.
She a 16-year-old. What is wrong with you?
No, no, no.
You can't write up to me.
No, no, no, no.
You planned this whole thing.
I was not just buying after...
Oh. You know that line on the top of the shrimp?
That's a feces.
What you looking for? Did you bring dip?
I'm sure that it's catered.
I need you to sign these, Michael.
It's a waiver of some of your rights.
You should read it carefully.
It releases the company in the event that our relationship,
in your opinion or in reality, interferes with work.
You get a copy, I get a copy, and a third copy goes to HR.
Awesome. I'm gonna frame mine.
I could frame yours, too.
You realize this is a legal document that says you can't sue the company.
Over our love.
I've never told you that I love you.
You don't have to, Jan.
This contract says it all.
I am taking a calculated risk.
What's the upside?
I overcome my nausea, fall deeply in love,
babies, normalcy, no more self-loathing.
Downside?
I date Michael Scott publicly and collapse into myself like a dying star.
What's this over the eye?
It's a heart.
Why is this so hard?
That's what she said.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God. What am I saying?
I love this woman!
Oh, my God. Michael, please. Michael, please.
Did you watch Battle Struggle Africa?
No.
No? Then you're an idiot.
Hello, Michael.
Rachel, boy, you clean up good.
The place looks great with all the lights on and everything.
It actually looks bigger with people in it. It's weird.
No.
Jan, glad you could make it.
Oh, of course. Of course, David.
Do you remember Michael Scott from this granted branch?
Of course I do. How are you, Michael?
Jan and I are lovers.
I feel so good if I only say that out loud.
David, can I speak to you privately for just a moment, please?
Okay.
I am attracted to weird, wrong men.
I dated a violent karate instructor and then an unemployed fireman.
Life has been complicated.
I've made some decisions that I'm not proud of.
My marriage, being overly litigious with my family.
I orgasm fairly easily.
Michael was kind of like my dirty secret, you know, having sex with him.
I don't know, I was just turned on by my own degradation.
Why? Anyway, I was told by somebody recently that I respect,
that I am old enough to have a mature relationship,
and that's what this whole evening is about, and I have high hopes.
Oh.
No, actually one of these is supposed to be a light.
Oh, sorry.
So the merger goes smoothly or?
It did, like butter.
Mike Myers, SNL. You should ask Karen. She was one of them.
I'm the only one left. Everybody else was either fired or quit.
And there's one in anger management.
Yeah, but you're great now, right? We're all great. Aren't we great?
We're good.
Michael, please stop that, okay?
Can I get me one anything?
I could go for an appetizer.
No, I'm good.
Bagel bites or something?
Rachel, your house is beautiful.
Thank you.
What's the square footage?
About 5,000.
Does that include the garage?
What? Wow. That's not appropriate.
I'm just, I don't know. It's a common question.
David, how much did this house cost?
These old colonials are great when they're sound.
I'd love to take a look around.
I'll show you around? Sure.
Cool. Let's start with the banisters.
Hey, do you see that guy behind you in the blue blazer against the wall?
Yep.
That's Drake. And just so you know, I don't want to be weird or anything, but we used to date.
Oh. Okay, cool. Thanks for telling me.
And it didn't end well.
Gotcha. All right.
This was a gift from Lee Iacocca, 20-year-old single mom Scotch.
Here is to Mr. Iacocca and his failed experiment, the DeLorean.
Are you okay?
Yeah. Do you have any ice?
How about some Splenda?
One, two, three, up, Jenkins.
Down, Jenkins.
I think I heard the cord over here.
Where? On this side.
No.