Oh, hey, Kevin. Nice of you to join us.
Where were you?
My tire blew out on the way here, Michael.
I almost died. I went into this skid.
Pop quiz.
What?
Why is today a special day?
I almost died.
Today is a special day because I am being honored
as a visiting professor, special lecturer, emeritus.
How did you...
He will be a guest speaker in my emerging enterprises class.
In business school, Kevin. Business school.
Wow.
If you bring your boss to class,
it automatically bumps you up a full letter grade.
So I'd be stupid not to do it, right?
Well, ultimately, I went into business to inspire people.
They say those who can't do teach, I can do both.
I teach doing.
Okay, here we go. Digestive business terms.
Cliff notes on business economics and sales and psychology.
Wow, that's a lot of books.
Do you have one book that sums up all of these?
Those are the books that sum up the other books.
So no?
What are you reading?
Oh, ever since I started here, I've kept a diary of all my sales.
Oh, that could be interesting.
It's just mileage mostly, but there's one chapter that I call wisdoms.
I'm going to read you a series of statements,
and I want you to tell me on a scale of 1 to 10 how smart they are.
I am ready.
Don't do what I say, say what I do.
Five.
Just getting warmed up.
Mistakes are just successes that you mess up.
Five.
This, you know the scale of 1 to 10?
Yeah.
Do you want me to repeat that?
Nope.
She's on her honeymoon. She won't be back for six weeks.
I'll wait.
Here's a joke for you.
Why did Pam hook up with Roy at Melissa's wedding?
Don't, Meredith.
You ready?
You know I don't like to participate in the...
Why did Pam hook up with Roy at Melissa's wedding?
Really? It's just that I don't like to participate in the...
Stop.
It's just... I'm sorry.
It's gossip, and I don't think it's healthy.
Get over yourself.
What's wrong?
Because Roy, you...
...the right...
That's disgusting.
No!
Here we go, college roadshow.
Gotta bring our A game.
What is the most inspiring thing I ever said to you?
Don't be an idiot.
It changed my life.
Whenever I'm about to do something, I think,
would an idiot do that?
And if they would, I do not do that thing.
Will they throw their hats, you think?
What?
A lot of times, at a school or naval academy,
after a rousing speech,
the crowd will throw its hats high into the air.
You understand nobody's graduating.
Yeah, I know. I know.
I'm just saying, if they did throw their hats,
I wouldn't mind for that.
May your hats fly
as high as your dreams.
That was a pretty good line.
It just...
It doesn't apply.
I understand. Wow.
Relax, spazzy boy.
Sometimes you're such a little spaz.
Oh, wait!
We had fun.
I can't wait for your art show tonight.
No, it's just the students from my class in Little Studio.
I wouldn't miss it for the world.
Thanks.
I'm really happy to be back with Roy.
I think it shows
maturity.
Maturity and dignity.
Is that braggie?
I don't mean it to be braggie.
Love you.
You too.
Pam's with Roy.
I'm with Karen.
And Brangelina is with Frangelina.
Moving on.
I can't believe you're back together with Roy.
Oh, yeah.
We have such a solid foundation, you know.
Oh, my God. You're so
in love now.
Oh, you should come to my art show, by the way.
Oh, art show.
I mean, it's not a big deal.
But I think a lot of people from the office are going to be there.
Oh, yeah.
Definitely I'll be there.
For sure.
Campus.
Brings back so many memories
that I would have made.
Hey, Frisbee.
Check that out.
What do you say we get our frizz on before class?
Yeah! Woo!
Dude.
Oh, my God.
Animal stool.
Dwight, what are you doing?
Solving a mystery, if that's quite all right with you.
Come to papa.
Okay, ladies and gentlemen.
What we have here is a bird
that has been trapped in a vent.
Fortunately, I have found it before...
Bird!
No, I won't remain calm!
There it goes.
Goodbye.
Woo!
God, this is so much fun.
I don't want that stupid thing coming under me.
Please, don't do it.
Okay, this is it.
Ryan is doing my intro right now.
Dunder Mifflin can't compete with the modern chains.
And management is unwilling
or unable to adapt.
Their customers are dying off.
I can't hear what he's saying,
but he looks like he's really into it.
Ooh.
Ah!
We have a bat
in the office.
Simple solution would be to open a window.
If we had
windows that could open.
Poop is raining from the ceilings.
Poop.
Okay, thanks.
Animal control will be here
at six.
At six? No, that is unacceptable.
Okay, Jim, you are the number two in this office.
You need to step up and show some leadership.
I'm sorry, what did you say?
So weird.
What? What's so weird?
The bat. I mean, I know I felt it bite me,
but look, there's no mark.
I feel so
tingly.
So strangely powerful.
Come on.
And now,
without further ado,
I present the regional manager of Dunder Mifflin
Scranton, Michael Scott.
Hello, everyone. I am Michael Scott.
And I'd like to start
today by inspiring you.
Everybody, please stand
and get up on your desks.
Just stand right up. Michael, it's not good.
That's a little flimsy.
Okay.
Alright.
More desks.
Oh, okay.
Can I borrow someone's textbook, please?
Thank you.
What have we here?
Oh, economics. Very, very interesting.
You cannot learn
from books.
Replace these pages
with life lessons.
And then,
you will have
a book
that is worth its weight
in gold.
I know these are
expensive,
but the lesson is priceless.
Good.
Alright. I think you're inspired.
Shall we proceed?
There are four kinds
of business. Tourism,
food service,
railroads,
and sales.
And hospitals
slash manufacturing.
And air travel.
It's your job, Halpert.
Ow!
What happened?
The bread on your desk? I just picked it up.
It's white hot.
But Jim, this garlic bread is cold.
What?
No.
It burned me. I...
Bizarre.
No.
One crisis at a time.
If a vampire
bat was in the US, it would make sense
for it to come to a Sylvania.
Like Pennsylvania.
Now that doesn't mean
that Jim is going to become a vampire.
Only that he carries
the vampiric germ.
So, you want
to start a business. How do you start?
What do you need? Well,
first of all, you need a building.
And secondly,
you need supply.
You need something to sell.
Now, this could be
anything. It could be
a thingamajig
or a hoozy whatsy
or
a whatchamacallit.
Now,
you need to sell
those in order to have
a payday.
And,
if you sell enough of them,
you will make
a 100 grand.
Satisfied?
I have a lot of big ideas.
And the trick is to get it out of my brain
and into theirs
in a way that is
easy to swallow.
Simple.
Kids love candy bars.
Oh, this looks great.
I'd love to be there, but my daughter's place
tonight...
Damn it!
You know, one of the other
parents will probably videotape it.
Oh, no. You should go.
Well, it's important to
support local art.
You know, and what they do is
they make art.
Let's try a little
social experiment here.
Raise your hands
if you like to
buy things.
Okay.
I see some people who like to buy things.
You're it. You are the reason
that this world
rolls along.
Give yourselves a round of applause.
Say you want to start
a business.
And business is all about
buying and selling, is it not?
So say you want to
sell
lemonade
or stickers.
Something you have to keep in mind.
You must
and you might want to jot this down.
sell the stickers
for more than you
bought the stickers for.
Okay, I'm seeing some confused
faces out there. Let me slow down a little bit.
Break this down.
Okay.
The more stickers you sell,
the more profit, fancy word for money,
you have to buy
PlayStations and Beanie Babies.
Michael, what we normally do here
is more of a question and answer thing.
Okay, I'm just kind of getting going.
Yeah, I know.
Okay, well, we can do questions.
Very good. First hand up.
As a company that primarily distributes
paper, how have you adapted your
business model to function in an
increasingly paperless world?
Oh, oh. I take
umbrage to that
premise, sis.
Let me ask you this.
How many people exist in the
world?
Over 40 billion. What are they
going to be writing on, rocks?
Anyone else?
Yep.
Just following up on that first question?
No, no, no, no. Never follow.
Always lead.
Okay. New question.
Very good. In the digital age,
email...
You only have me for a limited time?
Yes.
Do you believe your high fixed costs are
warranted given your diminishing market share?
How can I put this? That question
makes you sound gay.
Okay.
Hey, Jim. Here's the
aspart you wanted. Oh, thank
God. There's such a headache from that
glare. What glare?
The glare off Angela's Crucifix.
It's blinding.
I don't have a lot of experience
with vampires, but I have hunted
werewolves. I shot one once.
But by the time I got to it,
it had turned back into my
neighbor's dog.
Extraordinary events
call for extraordinary actions.
Will you form an allegiance
to use sudden violence?
Okay.
Do you have the tools to turn a wooden mop
handle into a steak?
Which size?
What do you say to a customer who wants to leave you
for the convenience and savings of a nationwide
chain? I say you will
miss our service, and I
absolutely guarantee you'll come back.
Has anyone ever come back?
We don't want them back.
They're stupid. How far has your Herfindahl
index declined since the merger?
Nice try. How's your Pollux's one index?
What? Thanks, Kowalski.
Can we get back on track here?
By your own employee's calculation,
you'll be obsolete in the next five to ten
years.
Wait, Ryan said that?
What are you doing?
You better not hurt that little bat.
Animals can't feel pain.
Don't hurt that bat, Creed. It's a living thing
with feelings and a family.
Flush him towards the door. On my go.
Now!
Kill it!
I am a
hero.
Yeah, sure. You know business. Sitting up here
in your ivory tower
and your ebony tower.
But you know what?
I'll tell you one thing. Dunder Mifflin is here
to stay. But how can you
compete against a company with the resources of a
nationwide chain? David will always beat
Goliath. But there's five
Goliaths. There's Staples,
Office, Mines. Yeah, yeah. You know what else
is facing five Goliaths?
America.
Al-Qaeda,
global warming,
sex predators,
mercury poisoning.
So do we just give up?
Is that what we're learning in business school?
But in the big picture... Dunder Mifflin
is the big picture. Can't you
understand that? No. You can't.
You're too young.
Ryan
has never made
a sale.
And he started a fire
trying to make a cheesy
pita.
And everybody thinks he's a tease.
Well, you know what?
He doesn't know anything
and neither do you.
So suck on that!
I really want to come out.