I have left Dunder Mifflin after many record-breaking years,
and I am officially on the job market,
and it's very exciting.
For your convenience, I've broken it down into three parts.
Professional resume, athletic and special skills resume,
and Dwight Shroop trivia.
I am ready to face any challenges
that might be foolish enough to face me.
How would I describe myself?
Three words.
Hard-working, alpha male, jackhammer.
Merciless.
Insatiable.
There's nothing on my horizon except everything.
Everything is on my horizon.
I got this job to make some money
while I continue my employment search.
And, uh, it's fine for the time being.
Oops.
Breaks over.
Big turkey.
Twiddly-diddly-dip, twiddly-diddly-dip, twiddly-diddly-dip.
Twiddly-diddly-dip, rocks in the deep,
so I'll hold it long.
Here I've been and I'm bumping and I'm singing the song.
All my little birds...
Is that you singing?
All four parts.
Recorded on my computer.
Wow.
Took me forever.
Nice job.
Thank you much, Lee.
Rock, hit or rock, boy, you're really gonna rock tonight.
Every little thwop...
You gonna answer it?
Mm-hmm.
I call that myself.
Just let you get a kick out of the new ring.
Yikes.
Side note, just like to say I'm thrilled
to be working directly beneath you.
I feel I have a lot to learn from you.
Even though you're younger and have less experience.
So here's to the future.
Andy and the Tuna.
E-e-e-Andy and the Tuna.
Oh, butter, dough, and a magical
E-e-E-Andy and the Tuna.
I miss Dwight.
Congratulations, Universe.
You win.
Yeah, top one go up.
Oh hey hey look who's here. Hello hello. Hi Michael. Welcome back. Good to see you.
As you know Oscar is a gay man who is also my friend and he has been on a
little bit of a sabbatical recently seeing the world finding himself having
lots of fun no doubt. What does that mean? Oh check out the new car German engineering nice.
How many pesos does that set you back? It's a company lease from the settlement after you
kissed me. Well that's how this company takes care of our employees when we
settle we settle high. I have an idea rainbow stickers all over the back
windshield. Shout it from the mountaintops my friend. Part of me wants
the people in this office to have learned their lesson and just shut the
hell up and part of me thinks you know what keep talking I'd really love a home
theater. Yes Dwight Schrute has left the company more personnel turnover. Cost of
doing business. Yeah well it is a big loss Dwight was the top salesman. Was the
top salesman. I said was. Addition by subtraction. What does that even mean?
That is impossible. Yeah you're right. But there is some good news Oscar is back
addition by addition so we are going to have a big party today to welcome him
back and hopefully that'll lift everyone's spirits. Hey Oscar good to
have you back. Good to be back. Hey Oscar. Hey everyone. Oh hello Oscar. How was your
vacation? That's very funny. Yeah I thought of that like two seconds after
you left. Hi Angela. Oscar. Hey boss. Hey what's up?
Mmm. DGI Wednesday. Am I right? Yep. Gonna go home get my beer on get my lost on.
What are you doing later you want to hang out? Oh I don't know maybe. Well I'll take
that as a maybe. We're going. Bathroom. No I'm going to the kitchen I'll walk with you.
Things are going pretty good. Getting a lot of face time with the boss.
Oscar I have a question. Would you like to join the party planning committee? The
committee with all the women? Yeah. Because I'm gay. No no certain events
have transpired and I've thought about certain things and I'm sorry for the way
those certain events transpired and I would just like to make some changes
about certain things and certain situations. Okay okay. All right all right I'll join. I'd love to.
That's thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Can I join too? Never. You sell those two printers this
morning. Nice work. Child's play give me something hard to sell. Hey Oscar how was Europe? It was
great. Yeah a lot of pictures. Oh great. You? Well my daughter turned seven so yeah big party lots
pictures. Nice. Yeah that's nice. Thanks. So should we email the pictures to each other or?
Or? I don't think we have to do that. Okay.
Hey where's Dwight? You didn't hear? Decapitated. Whole big thing. We had a funeral for a bird.
I'm pretty sure none of that's real. You're not real man. Wow what is wrong with this thing?
Looks terrible. Do you want me to ask the night cleaning crew if they stopped watering it? Yeah.
Oh you know what ask them about the toys on my desk too. They always used to arrange the toys
on my desk in a very pleasing way. Used to brighten my morning. Oh that wasn't the night
cleaning crew that was Dwight. Really? That was very nice of him. We need more attitude like that
around this office. Feel you dog. Yeah do you? Absolutely. What did I say? You said