Oh, wait.
He's dead.
Why?
What?
I accidentally ran over it.
It's a Christmas miracle.
Well, get it out of here.
Relax, okay?
And because this is Christmas, I am going to roast this goose and prepare it with a wild
rice dressing.
Do we have any cayenne pepper in the kitchen?
No.
No?
Okay.
Merry Christmas, Dwight.
Jim.
Wow.
What do we got here?
What does it look like?
Dead goose.
And circle gets the square.
All right.
So can you watch this?
I'm going to get my carving knife out of the trunk.
Dwight, we talked about this.
No, Toby.
This is different.
He's already dead.
Once I brought in a duck to prepare for lunch, and people got upset.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
People got upset.
Apparently they got attached to the duck and didn't want to see it killed.
He was already dead, and we shrewts use every part of the goose.
The meat has a delicious, smoky, rich flavor.
Plus you can use the molten goose grease and save it in the refrigerator, thus saving you
a trip to the store for a can of expensive goose grease.
Wow.
Win-win.
Exactly.
Thank you, Jim.
I like goose.
It's already dead.
Is it so crazy if we eat it?
That's crazy.
It's crazy.
Dwight, you cannot keep that here.
Okay, that is ridiculous and totally against the spirit of Christmas.
Come on, Dwight.
We went over this like for half an hour.
It's Christmas, Toby.
It's a dead animal in an office, you can't...
Toby.
I'm sorry.
Please.
Clean it in your car.
I would like it off my desk.
No, pay him.
Take a chill pill.
Dick the halls with vows of holly.
Fa la la la la la la la la.
Hey, I would like a nice slice of Christmas Pam.
Cider candy Pams.
And perhaps some Pam chops.
Can I help you, Michael?
With mint.
I'm looking for the toy drive box.
It's behind you.
Okay.
Well, I need to put this bike in there.
I hope it will fit with all these little knickknacks.
Wow.
What kind of bike is that?
I don't know.
Average kind.
The tires look pretty worn.
Well, that is probably from the test drive.
But the paint's chipping.
Is that your old bike, Michael?
No.
You, Michael.
Sweet ride, Mike.
Oh, thanks.
Michael?
Yes?
Oh, Pam.
That is so sweet.
You didn't have to do that.
I didn't.
It's from corporate.
Oh, okay.
Did everybody get one of these?
Yep.
Terrific.
Good.
This is going to be the best Christmas ever.
My girlfriend, Carol, is coming to our party tonight.
And I have a little surprise for her.
I've got two tickets to paradise.
Pack your bags.
We're leaving after tomorrow.
Taking her to Sandals, Jamaica.
All inclusive.
You know what time marriage.
Right?
Right.
Oh.
I think you're supposed to put a toy in the box.
You're supposed to put a toy in the box.
I'm sorry.
I think you're supposed to put a toy in the box, Greg.
And a happy holiday to you.
Carol.
Hi.
Is Michael around here?
There she is.
A Christmas Carol.
Hello.
You're about five hours early to the party.
Boy, you're such a blonde.
Michael.
Hey, everybody.
I don't know who you haven't met yet,
but I think this is one of them.