Hey Ryan, can I get you a pencil from the warehouse?
Uh, no thanks, I'm good.
Well that's okay, I'm going down.
Um, yeah, absolutely.
Alright, I'll be right back.
Woo! Awesome!
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Can you get me a pen from down in the warehouse?
Don't mind if I do.
See you in a minute.
Okay.
Woo!
There you go, fresh from the warehouse.
Hey Michael, would you get me some coffee from the warehouse?
There's coffee in the kitchen, Pam.
But the warehouse coffee tastes so much better.
Yes, it's better.
Alright.
Okay.
I'm like Bette Midler in For the Boys.
I'm going to keep the troops entertained.
With cream and sugar?
Okay.
Alright.
So I wanted to let you know that we lost Ed Truck.
Okay, let me see if I have his cell.
Is this the only reason you are calling, Jan?
Or does somebody miss me?
Michael, Ed died over the weekend.
Oh wow.
Yeah, and I know you with your boss, so I thought you should know.
Does his family know?
No, they don't.
I thought you should know.
Does his family know?
Yes, they know, Michael.
But I'm the first in the office.
I guess, yes.
I think it would be appropriate for you to make an announcement to your team in case they want to pay their respects.
Okay, yes, sure, I will do that.
As I am the first to find out, nobody else knows, and it is my responsibility to tell them.
Good.
How are you holding up?
Want me to come over?
Ed Truck died.
And it blows.
They say that with grief, time makes it worse.
Which is bad for me because I found out before anybody, so I've had more time to be sad.
Attention everybody.
I just received a call from corporate with some news that they felt that I should know first.
My old boss, Ed Truck, has died.
Oh, Michael, that's such terrible news.
You must feel so sad.
Yes, I am.
It's very sad.
Because he was my boss.
Well, that's a shame.
Ed was a good guy.
That's right.
You worked with him.
So did Creed.
Well, I'll be in my office in case anybody wants to drop by.
Cheer me up.
So did you hear the news?
The news that you just announced?
That Ed died?
Yeah.
Is there anything I can do?
Oh, gosh, what can anybody do?
Really?
He was almost 70.
Circle of life.
Yeah.
Oh, okay.
Okay.
Hey, Jimmy, want to see some pictures of my baby?
Sure.
Here he is.
Oh, he's so cute.
And here's his first bath.
Warning contains nudity.
That's okay.
Oh, no, it's not.
I'm sorry.
Is that your husband in the tub with him?
You think we should have left our baby in the tub alone?
Talk to me when you have kids.
Sounds good.
What's going on with Fairfield County Schools?
Karen, did you generate that price list?
Shoot.
I don't know.
Okay, just get it done.
Jim, will you make sure?
Oh, yeah, definitely.
Suck up.
Josh, did you hear what I said?
Thank you, everyone.
Damn it.
What's up?
Nothing.
I'm just out of her...
Oh.
But don't worry about it.
My snack food doesn't fall under the umbrella of your authority.
That's where you're wrong.
I'm your project supervisor today.
And I have just decided that we're not doing anything
until you get the chips that you require.
So I think we should go get some.
Now, please.
Attention, everyone.
As you know, Ed Truck is dead.
If you have any contact information,
unroll the DEX files,
or in Microsoft Outlook, remove it now.
Also, if you have any photographs,
Pam will make her shredder available during lunch.
That is all.
It's a real shame about it, huh?
Yeah.
Must really have you thinking.
About what?
The older you get, the bigger the chances of you getting
a job.
I'm not sure.
About what?
The older you get, the bigger the chances you're gonna die.
You knew that.
Ed was decapitated.
What?
Really?
He was drunk as a skunk.
He was flying down Route 6.
He slides under an 18-wheeler, pop, it snaps right off.
Oh, my God.
That is the way to go.
Instant death.
Very smart.
You know, a human can go on living for several hours
after being decapitated.
You're thinking of a chicken.
What did I say?
That is just not the way a Dunder Mifflin manager should go.
I'm sorry.
Alone, out of the blue.
He might even have his own head to comfort him.
So I'm not exactly sure how to say this.
Ed was decapitated.
What are you doing?
You said you didn't know how to say it.
I didn't.
He was driving on the road, and he went under a truck.
And that's when his head...