Brain teaser. I have two coins totaling 15 cents.
One of them is not a nickel. What are they?
A dime and a nickel.
No, I said one of them is not a nickel.
But the other one is. I've heard that before.
Okay. A man and his son get into a car accident.
They are rushed to the hospital.
The doctor says,
There's no way I can operate on this boy because...
Because he's my son.
The doctor is the boy's mother.
A man is found hanging from the ceiling.
He stepped on a block of wood.
He's found hanging from the ceiling.
He stepped on a block of ice, hung himself, and the ice melted.
Hunter.
It's a polar bear because you're at the North Pole.
Tell me what you did yesterday.
Uh... Nothing.
Nothing?
No, nothing. How was your day?
I don't care how your day was, Michael.
Wow. Well, okay.
I don't care how your day was either, Jan.
I was just asking you because you asked me.
Tell me what you did yesterday.
Why did you set me up like that?
I'm sure you're not just a boy.
I'm not just a boy.
You're a guy.
because you asked me.
Why did you set me up like that?
I worked.
And then I went home to my condo and Carol came over
and we had sex.
That what you wanna hear?
Never, ever, ever sleep with your boss.
I'm so lucky that Jan and I only got to second base.
What I want, Michael, is an hour by hour log
of how you spend your work time.
Well, that's really not the way I roll
because sometimes I'm in the zone
and sometimes I'm in the zoning out.
Zoning out?
Do you want me to go on Amazon
and order you a slang dictionary?
Because I'll do it.
If you can account for your time,
then maybe corporate can justify your salary.
A woman spurned.
It's like mommy and daddy are fighting.
Except mommy outranks daddy.
And mommy is way scarier.
Hi, Pam.
Hi.
I'm great.
So, Pam, I'd like you to keep a log
of everything Michael does hour by hour
so that we can analyze it at corporate, okay?
Oh, I don't know, Pam. Thanks, Pam.
It's weird.
Jan used to treat Michael like he was a 10-year-old,
but lately it's like he's five.
So you excited?
Yeah.
Very excited?
Yes.
I'm very excited.
Extremely excited?
Just very? That's cool.
Take a good look at this boy.
I always do.
Because you are never going to see him again.
If you lay a finger on him.
Today is Ryan's first sales call
and I am bringing this boy home, a full-grown man.
Oh, would you look at that?
Ah!
Ha ha ha!
Damn it, Dwight. Come on.
Dwight is taking Ryan on a sales call today.
So if we find Ryan's body in a heavily wooded area tomorrow,
I owe Jim $30.
It's an old bet, but deal's a deal.
I have spent a year here
and I have to commit or get out.
So Dwight's the top salesman in the company
and he's taking me on my first sales call today.
And I'm excited.
I am very excited.
Ryan hasn't made a sale yet,
but more importantly, he hasn't made an ally yet.
Is he going to be a slacker, loser, wise ass like Jim was?
Or is he going to join the Dwight Army of Champions?
Get in the car.
I don't have a key.
Don't you realize the key is inside you?
He's the top salesman at the company.
Today's going to be great.
No, but seriously, your ears are the key.
90% of a good sales call is listening.
Only 10% is talking.
Huh.
Get in the car.
So what if they're not talking much?
Then does it make sense to kind of lead the conversation?
You know, just till it gets to a point
where they are asking questions?
So where's the sales office?
When you are ready to see the sales office,
the sales office will present itself to you.
Your journey begins now.
Hey.
What?
My chair's squeaking.
Is it?
You took my chair.
No, I didn't.
I took back the chair that you took from me,
but I didn't take your chair.
When you get up, I'm just gonna take it back anyway, so.
So I guess I can't get up.