Oh, yes.
Okay, where does it hurt?
Just all over.
I don't want to do anything dying.
No, that's not how it works.
You have to point to a specific part of the body.
Right there.
Abdomen.
Mencies.
Maybe.
The uterus contracts after your egg passes through it.
No, I don't have eggs.
So when did this start?
About 10 minutes ago.
When I came in with the paperwork?
Mm-hmm.
About 40 times a year, Michael gets really sick
but has no symptoms.
Dwight is always gravely concerned.
Oh, is it possible you ate food that contained animal waste?
It's possible.
Michael?
David Wallace is online.
CFO?
Oh.
All right, everybody out.
Out, out, out.
Okay.
To what do I owe this great honor, David Wallace?
Michael, I am calling...
Abramit?
Jan?
Is Jan there?
Jan is out of town right now.
Oh, you sigh like Jan.
I broke Jan's heart, David, and I feel awful.
It was...
It was never my intention to ruin a life.
But you know what?
Sometimes...
Michael?
You just gots to get your freak on.
Yeah.
Michael?
Hmm.
I am calling to see if you would come down
and interview for a job.
We have opening up in corporate.
Really?
A week from today.
Bring your first quarter stats and your recommendation
for who would take over this grand branch.
Wow.
I wish I had prepared something to say.
That's not necessary.
May God guide you in your quest.
Yes.
Okay.
Everybody have their towels and swimsuits.
We have about an hour and a half.
I suggest that you all go potty now,
and then we will be congregating on the partay bus.
Fun on wheels.
Only way to travel.
Besides a monorail.
Well, Bob was going to just drive me.
No.
No, no, no.
No guests today.
Classic gang only.
Just us good friends.
And Karen and Andy.
Sometimes Michael gets nostalgic,
and he talks about the classic gang.
That's Michael, me, Jim, Dwight, Angela, Kevin, Oscar, Stanley,
Phyllis, Creed, Meredith, Kelly, and Ryan.
We're a regular Oceans 11.
Jim?
David Wallace is calling for you.
Oh.
Okay.
Hello?
Hey, David.
Sure.
Oscar, you brought your Speedo, I assume?
I don't wear a Speedo.
Well, you can't swim in leather pants.
I'm just yanking your chain.
Not literally.
Oh, I'm excited.
Today is beach day.
Michael is taking the whole office to the beach.
So I'm wearing my bathing suit underneath my shirt.
Oh, yeah.
I packed it in my purse.
Anybody need sunblock?
Got SPF 30.
Oh, you know what?
You're not going.
It's beach day.
Yeah, I know.
I'm sorry, Toby.
We, um, somebody has to stay here.
I want today to be a beautiful memory that the staff and I
share after I have passed on to New York.
And if Toby is a part of it, then it'll suck.
Hey.
Want my sunscreen?
Oh, great.
I forgot mine, and I'm wearing a two-piece.
Uh-huh.
Thanks, Toby.
Hey, Pam.
You broke up with your boyfriend
and then kept working together.
How did that work out?
You remember?
You fired Roy for attacking Jim,
and I don't talk to him anymore, really.
Acrimonious.
I have a very important job for you today.
I thought we were just having fun at the beach.
We are.
But I would like you to take notes,
and I want you to find out about people's character.
You know, not their hotness, per se,
but their humor and their charisma
and the indefinable quality that makes
you all glad to follow me.
What happens to a company if somebody takes a boss away?
I will answer your question with a question.
It's like what happens to a chicken.
When you take its head away, it dies.
Unless you find a new head.
I need to see which one of these people
have the skills to be a chicken head.
You want me to write down people's indefinable qualities?
I want you to write down everything
that people are doing all day and then type it up
in a way that is helpful.
Right?
I have the most boring job in the office,
so why wouldn't I have the most boring job on beach day?
This way to the pate, Buzz.
I just want to lie on the beach and eat hot dogs.
That's all I've ever wanted.
Um, what the hell?
It's a bus that takes you to a party.
Here we go.
Um, I forgot my sluggle.
Here we go. Come on.
Okay, everybody here?
Yeah!
Then, Mr. Driver, we are off like a herd of turtles.
Johnny Carson.
Seat belts fasten, folks.
Safety first.
Hey, what is all this?
Nothing.
If I guess, will you tell me?
No.
Please?
Is that a sumo show?
No, no.
I know.
We're putting on a play for Japanese investors.
No, we are not.
Please tell me.
You are really annoying me.
If you don't knock it off, I'm never going to tell you anything ever again.
Stop it.
Can we please pull over at the next rest stop?
No.
We're only ten minutes from the lake.
Pull over.