So the figure's showing improvement right there, Michael.
And again...
I'll call back.
You never call back.
Every time Michael's in a meeting, he makes me come in and give him a post-it note telling him who's on the phone.
I did it once and he freaked out. He loved it so much.
The thing is, he doesn't get that many calls.
So he has me make them up every ten minutes.
Tell him I'll call him back.
You can't just work 200 days a day.
Oh, no, no, no. I don't have time for this.
Tell him I'm in a meeting.
So?
You have to know how to work this. There's no excuse for this.
Yep.
I can get you a tutor if you need.
Oh.
Ah, this is a very important client.
But I have the most important client sitting right in front of me, my boss.
So I will call him back later.
Oh, no, no, no.
Customer service is obviously a priority one. You can take the call.
No. Money isn't everything, Ryan, and you're my friend, and I don't want to be rude.
Take the call, friend.
I refuse. No. My house, my rules. I insist.
I insist you take your work calls.
Okay. All right, Pam, would you put the call through?
Bye, buddy.
I don't know. I just... I never felt welcome there, you know?
That's, uh...
This is such a boys club.
Yeah, I hate that.
Good.
So here's the deal. I am on my way to New York to be deposed as part of Jan's wrongful termination lawsuit.
The company fired her for having the courage to augment her boobs.
And they displayed a pattern of disrespect and inappropriate behaviors.
Yes. Yes. Pattern. Pattern. My friend Pat took a turn. That's how I remember that.
Could we pull over and put down the top? My... I feel a little queasy.
I want it up. My hair.
Well...
Remember, it's not just a pattern. It's a pattern of disrespect and inappropriate behaviors.
Dis-ray. My friend Dis-ray got new specs. Dis-ray speck. My friend In-apro drives a Prius with his behind neighbor.
Does this work for you?
Yep. Tell him how much you're going to get if you win.
Oh, come on, Michael. That's tacky.
Million dollars.
Four million.
Four million dollars! Man! That is a lot of guacamole. A lot of the green. A lot of green.
That is why I have memorized Jan's answers. And I've also thrown in some errs and ahs just to make it seem like it's not memorized.
Perfect crime.
Stop saying ridiculous things. He's just going to tell the truth. The truth is very, you know, complicated.
So we went over it carefully and just so that we wouldn't leave anything up to chance or Michael's judgment.
Could we please pull over and pull down the top? I do not feel good.
Michael, I told you I'm not putting the top down.
I'm getting corn sick.
I'm going to puke. I think I'm going to throw up.
Alright, fine. Just a second. Hold on.
Thank you.
So both my lover and my company are very concerned about what I have to say. But I think I can strike a balance between the two.
As long as there is no acrimony. Jan's lawyer said the trial would be very civil. So I am not worried.
However, just in case, world sales trick. Feminine lady pads. You stick these under your armpits. They're very absorbent.
Made for a woman, but strong enough for a man.
Hey, Schneider, real quick. What do you call a buttload of lawyers driving off the cliff?
A good start. And I think it's busload.
Yeah, a bunch of rich lawyers took the bus. Where'd you find this guy?
Hey, there he is.
Hey, Michael.
Hey, Jan. I'm glad you're here. I actually need to talk to you for a second.
Can we talk off the record as friends?
I would love that.
Jan has put the company in a very tough position here. Now, you've been with us for a long time. Over ten years, right?
We just want to be sure that you won't do anything to hurt us with your testimony. Do you understand?
Absolutely, yeah. I'll do anything for the company.
Good. That is great to hear.
It is.
Gage, son. All right, let's run it back.
The warehouse got a ping pong table last week. Now Jim comes down and plays with Darryl. Sometimes I bring him juice. My boyfriend is 12.
What has two skinny chicken legs and sucks at ping pong?
Hi, Kelly.
Guess whose boyfriend it is?
I don't want to guess.
I'll give you a hint. It's not my boyfriend. I think it's a guy over here.
White people trash talk like, Kelly, you are not allowed to sleep at your desk. That is irresponsible.
But black people, they're like, Kelly, you got a salamin' body, girl. You got it going on.
Jim, can I see you for a second?
Sure.
Wow.
Okay, it's not regulation size, but it'll do. You have to practice. You have to get really good and beat Darryl.
I can't beat Darryl.
Please? Kelly's trash talking me because Darryl's beating you.
What? Seriously, what is she saying?
Your boyfriend is so weak he needs Darryl as just to watch baseball. Jim couldn't hit a ping pong ball if it was the size of the moon. Were Jim's parents first cousins that were also bad at ping pong?
So you're asking me to defend your honor against Kelly?
Sorta, yes.
Bring me a player.
Okay.
Hi, everyone. Diane Kelly. I'm the company's chief legal counsel.
Hi. No, no. Absolutely not. What is he doing here?
Are you renewing your divorce vows before my deposition?
Michael, I'm your H.I. rep. I'm on your side.
Never. I want him gone. I don't talk until he leaves.
Michael, just relax, okay?
You know what, I think they're ready for us now, so.
Okay. All right.
Michael is going to be cross-examined today, which will be very, very risky for me. It's not an easy decision to make, but it's a deposition. It's not going to be in front of a judge, and it's $4 million.
I have some experience. I once had to testify in a traffic accident case.
Then you're an old hand at this.
Yes. My testimony was actually very important because the accident was my fault.
It's not merit of this another time.
Before we continue, I would like to make an opening statement.
Fine. Please be brief.
Ladies and gentlemen of the table, I would just like to say what a joy it is for me to be here today. But frankly, at my age, it's a joy to be anywhere.
I'm only 44, so I'm not old, and I guess that doesn't really play.
But the point is I have a sense of humor, and I implore you all to have a sense of humor as well.
Jan, David, my wonderful girlfriend, my gorgeous company.
What a joy it is to be here today.