Hey. Ready?
Come on. Show me excited.
Yes. Yeah.
I'm pretty excited, too.
Today, I'm headed over to the job fair
at Valley View High School to find some new interns.
Want to get some fresh blood?
Um, euthanize this place.
Hey, we doing this thing? Yeah.
Oh, my God, Daryl.
You look like Barack Obama.
Everybody have a date of Barack Obama.
Why are you dressed like that? Like what?
Like you're applying for a loan.
Maybe he's going to church or a court.
Figured I'd look presentable. Yeah.
You went a different way.
I think you look nice. Thank you.
Okay, here's what we're going to do.
I am going to instruct the kids about management and sales.
Oscar will be in charge of accounting.
Pam will be eye candy.
No, and also because that is your alma mater.
Uh, Daryl will hire some kids for the warehouse.
We don't have to worry about internships with them
because they definitely ain't going to college.
What college did you go to, Mike?
Let's go!
Today I am meeting a potential client on the golf course
because Ryan put me on probation.
You remember Ryan? He was the temp here.
Yeah, and it is not a good time for me to lose my job
since I have some pretty big long-term plans.
My personal life with Pam that I'd like her parents to be psyched about.
So I am about to do something that I'm not going to do
because I'm going to be a little bit of a pain in the ass.
I'm going to be the temp that I'd like her parents to be psyched about.
So I am about to do something very bold at this job
that I've never done before.
Try.
Whoa! Mr. McGuire.
It's been a couple of years.
Hey, Jim, how are you? Nice to see you, man.
Oh, no. No, no, no, no.
My grandfather would be spinning in his urn
if he knew that I was out here with a Dartmouth boy.
You take that shirt off right now, or I will take it off for you, sir.
I am totally and completely kidding.
Andrew Bernard, Cornell, 95.
The McGuire Dartmouth, 74.
Got some blisties. Yeah, you do.
Hit about 1,200 balls last night in preparation for today,
so hands are a little tender.
It's actually not funny at all. It's incredibly painful.
Hey, let's make it interesting. Say, uh, 10 bucks a hole?
Great. What are we talking? Skins? AC Doocy? Bingo, bingo, bongo?
Sandies? Barkies? Arnie's? Wolf? What?
I'm going to take this petty cash that I got from Oscar
and turn it into next month's rent.
So many memories in this old gym.
Pretending to have PMS so I didn't have to play volleyball,
pretending to have PMS so I didn't have to play basketball.
Those were the days.
A little over the top, don't you think?
Show them what you brought, Mike.
Um, that's all we brought.
This is all we need? We'll see.
Yes, we will see, Oscar.
We will see because a blank sheet of paper
equals endless possibilities. Conceptual.
All right.
We are open for business.
Hello?
What up?
Sup?
Hello?
Blank sheet of paper. Blank sheet of paper.
Well, kids today have a very short attention span.
They are into texting and video games and sex and...