I'm going to do the math.
I'm going to make a
Hello, this is Dwight Schrute.
Hello?
Hello, this is Dwight.
Yes, we do have that.
Hold on one second.
Jim, what are you doing?
And how many would you like?
Hang that up right now.
Absolutely, I can get that out to you immediately.
This man is an impostor.
Do not do business with him.
This is not Dwight Schrute.
Dwight left his cell phone on his desk, so naturally, I paired it to my headset.
Okay, fine.
I'll just let it go to voicemail.
Hello, this is Dwight.
Hey, is this Dwight?
Yes, it is.
Oh my goodness, you sound sexy.
Oh, thank you.
I've been working out.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Pam, Pam, you are not talking to Dwight right now.
You are talking to Jim.
Dwight?
No.
Pam, I'm over here.
I'm confused.
Disconnect that right now.
You give me your earpiece.
I can't do that.
I'm sanitary.
Okay, you know what?
I'm going to go to the bathroom.
Fine.
I will reprogram my phone to go to my office phone.
Done.
This is Dwight.
Oh, and I forwarded his desk phone to mine.
Oh, hello, mutter.
Good news.
I've married.
Tell father.
Such a nice woman.
Forget it.
Let's go.
Did we just kiss?
Yes.
Today is Toby Flenderson's last day.
I couldn't sleep last night.
I came in extra early.
So much energy.
There's certain days that you know you will remember
for the rest of your life.
And I just have a feeling that today is one of those days.
Morning.
So here we go.
Just a matter of hours now
until his horribleness has left the building.
I'm going to set my watch alarm.
And...
Morning, Kelly.
I can't believe this is your last day.
How do you feel?
Fine. Good.
I feel weird.
This is a picture I've been carrying around on my wall
for about six years.
It's this unspoiled beach in Costa Rica, Playa Grande.
God, I take it out when I get stressed or depressed.
It would really calm me down.
Never thought I'd get to live here.
But it turns out they built these great new condos there.
So this could be me right around where the trees used to be.
First thing on the agenda, actually,
the only thing on the agenda
is the status of Toby's going away party.
We have a buttercream cake and a slideshow of Toby.
But so far we only have two pictures of him.
Okay. Well, this will not do.
Toby is going away forever.
And we need to do something very, very special.
In some cultures, when somebody leaves,
like New Orleans culture, they have a parade
and they have a band and people party in the streets.
Do you mean leaves as in dies?
You want us to throw Toby a New Orleans funeral?
If the devil were to explode and evil were gone forever,
what sort of party would you have?
Michael.
Like a beach blowout or a toga?
No, you know, no.
Oh, God.
You always do this.
We have a nice modest party planned
and then you come in and demand the world.
Let me be clear.
There is simply no money for anything other than a cake
and to develop a few more slides.
Although Toby won't be in them.
I thought that you might say that.
Hmm.
Every year, my sweet, sweet grandmother sends me a check
on my birthday for $50.
And lately...