And the same thing goes for quarterly reports.
They are unreadable.
They're just numbers and boring and blech.
So what I was thinking is that maybe we should have
some sort of graphic, like if we have a bad quarter
put in a storm cloud.
And when we have a good quarter, fireworks or a race car.
Doesn't have to be a race car.
Use your imagination.
There's this cube on the screen.
It bounces around all day.
And sometimes it looks like it's heading right into the corner
of the screen and at the last minute it hits a wall
and bounces away.
We are all just dying to see it go right into the corner.
Pam claims that she saw it one day when she was alone
in the conference room.
Okay.
I believe she thinks she saw it.
I saw it.
I saw it and it was amazing.
Who said I didn't see it?
Did Jim say that I didn't see it?
I saw it.
We have a lot of colored paper here.
Why oh why do we keep printing this on white?
No, come on.
Yeah.
I know.
I know, it's bland.
It's never going to happen.
Dude, you've got to believe.
Maybe we could have some sort of riddle.
Wait for it.
Like something that you have to look for.
Sort of a where's Waldo.
Oh.
Yeah.
Pretty close.
All right.
All right, let's quit while we're ahead.
That was so awesome.
That was awesome.
Thank you.
Some days I am just on fire.
Why can't I say?
What?
Well, it's just that you had no hair on Friday.
It's called being a man.
You should try it sometime.
How long have you been a man?
I was born a man.
I'm not a man.
I'm a man.
How long have you been a man?
I was born a man, Halpert.
That must have been extremely uncomfortable for your mom.
I stopped shaving because my girlfriend broke up with me.
Am I in pain?
Hell yeah.
But I'll tell you something.
I thrive in pain.
I love pain.
To me, pain is not pain at all.
No.
It is pure pleasure.
And I hate pleasure.
Almost as much as I love pain.
So, yeah.