Dunder Mifflin, this is Rolando.
Oh, yeah, she's been expecting your call.
Yeah?
Karen? He's on line one.
Thanks, Rick.
Hey, we finally connected. How's Scranton?
I am the regional manager of Dunder Mifflin Utica branch.
Turns out it's a pretty easy gig when your boss isn't an idiot
and your boyfriend's not in love with somebody else.
Yes. Look, all I'm saying is it would be a great opportunity
and we'd love to have you come aboard.
So think about it, okay?
Okay, bye.
Look, for the record,
a certain Scranton salesman approached me, okay?
Wow. This is perfect.
He looks like your twin.
This is a dummy a la Ferris Bueller's day off.
We have tied a string to the wrist which goes to the door.
When somebody opens the door, the hand goes down, hits the remote,
turns on the tape recorder, which is me snoring.
Now nobody knows whether I am here or whether I am gone.
I will know.
But you will not tell anyone.
We'll need to because we'll be together playing hooky.
We will.
Sometimes, most of the time, I will be with Ryan or Daryl.
Yes. Oh, good, good. Stanley, first victim.
This is what I want you to do. Go out, come back in.
We're going to hide. I want you to tell me if this looks like me, okay?
I don't understand why sleeping at your desk is better than you not being here.
Just go out and come back in.
I got an offer from Utica for more money, and I'm going to take it.
What?
Hi, everyone. Can I have your attention, please?
I just thought you all should know that Stanley Hudson is planning on leaving us
because our old friend Karen from Utica is going to give him more money to work there.
Okay.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm sorry.
You completely misinterpreted my tone.
This is a horrible thing.
Clearly, Karen is trying to get back at us because Jim dumped her.
Oh, I don't think that's what's happening.
Okay, well, smarty pants, then why?
Why is she trying to take Stanley from us?
I think it's because of my sales record.
That could not possibly be it.
I will go to Utica if they have more pretzel days in Utica.
If they do not have more pretzel days in Utica, I do not know what I will do.
Are you gleeful over this?
Is this working out for you, Jim?
It's completely unrelated, so.
Was it worth it?