It is moving day.
I have spent the last month here at Dwight's lovely farm
taking a little bit of a vacation, clearing my head
after Jan and I, um...
No, I did not kill her.
We were just at different places in our lives,
so I thought I'd be the bigger man
and allow her to stay at the condo.
She has since moved on.
She is staying with her sister in Scottsdale.
Fresh outlook, and it's all good.
Okay, so look that over. Make sure it's accurate.
What is this?
Your bill, minus the 10% Dunder Meflin corporate discount.
You're charging me? I'm your friend.
You occupied the America Room for six weeks.
That's our most popular room.
There was no other guest the entire time I was here.
Right, because you were in the America Room
in an election year.
Okay.
All right, Dwight, take my money. Go ahead.
Keep in mind that this whole thing
was just a business transaction.
The late nights, the talks, slumber parties,
the crying jags, that was all business.
It had nothing to do with friendship
and being friends.
You can ring me up.
Go ahead.
Thank you, Dwight.
We don't take debit cards anyway.
Dwight, a little help with the bags, please?
WB Jones is renovating their offices,
and their construction crews are taking up
some of the parking spaces we used to get.
So we had to park at a satellite parking lot over there.
Which just means we get to see more of our lovely street.
Tell them what we saw today, Jim.
Oh, today we saw a junkyard dog attacking the bones
of a rotisserie dog.
That's a good one.
I'm glad you're here.
A junkyard dog attacking the bones of a rotisserie chicken.
Nature.
I've been here nine years now.
All of a sudden I'm supposed to park half a mile away.
I lost a penny out of my lopers, Oscar.
I will quit.
As God is my witness, I will quit if this is not fixed.
Some of us like the walk more than others.
It looks like hell.
Hey, Stanley.
Ugh.
Did you pick a new chair? It's been a while.
Pam, when I first opened this catalog,
I thought I was just going to be picking out a chair.
But instead you found something to distract you
from ever picking out a chair.
Michael started the process of selecting a new chair
about three weeks ago.
And normally I wouldn't care, but he promised me his old one.
It's way better. It's one of these.
Shh.
I really want it.
Have you ever seen this woman?
Her? The one in the really great
mesh black high-backed swivel chair?
Look at her smile.