What do you think of my cool new ride?
Pretty sweet.
It's just for rental.
My C-bring's in the body shop.
Got some work done.
Had to have the dent taken out of the hood where I hit Meredith.
Destination is ahead.
Thank you, invisible driving companion.
It's not an invisible companion.
It's a GPS machine.
The thing is so amazing.
This is like having a computerized map in your car.
Destination is on the right.
Why, thank you.
Love that voice.
I know.
Something so soothing about it, like taking a warm bath.
Oh, oh, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on.
Ah, it is my lady love.
Smell-o.
Where the f*** are my grapenuts?
I don't...
I just want to know, did you eat my grapenuts?
Ah, no, I hate those things.
Grow up, Michael.
I love...
Not a morning person.
Sorry, I don't understand that command.
Hey.
I got you one.
Oh, wow, great.
Oh, thank you.
Yeah.
I'm just gonna grab some chips.
You want some?
No, thanks.
We're still having lunch today, right?
I guess.
How dare you?
Hey, Toby.
What's this?
Huh?
I just want to remind everyone about the company rules
involving PDA, or public displays of affection.
Yes, some people in the office have complained.
Oh, really?
About some other people engaging in PDA.
You know, just want to remind,
it's not appropriate to do that.
This is about me and Jan in my office,
because I will have you know that that was consensual.
What we did has nothing to do with you or anyone here.
I don't think anyone heard anything.
We were very discreet,
and most people had left by that point.
So I don't think it's any of your business.
So what I think you should do is roll up the memo real tight.
Okay, look, the memo is not about you.
For the record, I have never been involved
with anyone at work in any capacity.
All right, everyone, look.
The complaint was about Jim and Pam.
No way.
You guys are together?
Yep.
Yes, we are.
Whoa, wow.
Tudor?
Awesome.
I knew it.
To the two of you.
Yes, yes.
Toby, was this your fun little way of congratulating us?
Yes.
Okay, mind is exploding.
Get over here, come on.
Come here.
Okay, okay, stand up.
Okay, here we go.
Everyone, this is a day that will live in infamy
because today is the day that Jim and Pam become one.
Actually, I've been dating for a couple months.
I love you guys so much.
Oh.
Phone's ringing.
No, no, no, Pam, let them ring.
Let the bells of Dunder Mifflin chime out your name.
Dunder Mifflin chime out your love
because this is really good.
This is really good.
My heart soars.