Everybody, everybody, listen up.
I need your ideas now.
Ideas, please, right now.
Go, go. Come on.
Michael, we don't know what you're talking about.
Wet cement outside. It's drying fast.
Come on. This is a lifelong dream.
What do I write? What do I write?
Michael, you could put your initials in it.
MGS? No.
It's some idiot named Mark Greg Sputnik
who will claim credit for it.
It wasn't a lifetime opportunity, people.
Come on. Here we go.
Here we go.
Yes?
When I was a little girl...
Okay.
Okay. Come on. Great. Let's hear it.
We found some wet cement in the park in our neighborhood.
It's drying. It's drying.
All right. Come on.
I want to see it right.
Oh, come on.
Here it is. You draw a picture.
No.
Because that says so much more than words.
No. Come on. Give me something good.
I was watching E! and I saw Will Smith
outside the Chinese theater.
Oh my God. He looks so good.
Hey, I'm translated.
She's talking about the hand prints
that celebrities make in the summit.
I love it.
If you were a real star, you'd put your face in it.
I love it more.
Michael, that doesn't seem safe.
I love it.
Come on. Let's go.
We are here today not to immortalize a man,
but an idea.
Maybe the idea of a man.
Hurry, please.
Greatness is only skin deep, some people say.
Can you breathe?
That's not true. Other people believe it's deep down inside.
Hold your breath. Ready?
That's also not true.
Go.
Force it in as deep as you can.
That's what she said.
Today is a very special day for me.
And it's really not about me.
It's about my grandkids.
It's about my great grandkids.
I can come back here when I'm 100
and I can find that piece of cement and say,
that's me.
Look, kids, your daddy left that face hole.
I don't know.
It's a good feeling.
Music
Okay. Adjective.
Um, tall.
No, no. Nice.
Good one.
Okay. You ready?
The tall man entered the nice building
to visit a very nice man.
Sit down, Mr. Smith.
Could I interest you in any good cat food?
The man eating cat food.
What about a cat eating man food?
Andy and Angela seem very happy.
I hope nothing horrible ever happens to them.
Um, yeah, I slept over at a friend's house
and I forgot my contact solution,
so I had to wear my backup glasses.
Shut up.
All right, everybody.
Oh, my God, Pam.
Those make you look so ugly.
Pam, in order to get hotter, you take glasses off.
You're moving in the wrong direction.
I don't have my contacts.
I can't even hear you.
It's just noise coming out of an ugly scientist.
Everybody, we're going to have a little brainstorming session
in the conference room.
Energize.
You know what would energize me?
If you, Pamela Morgan Beasley,
Don't you dare.
If you propose to me during a Michael meeting, I will say no.
Well, it's too late because I'm proposing
that you get me a cup of coffee,
which would energize me greatly
and make me the happiest man in the world.
Everybody, so how are we going to energize our office?
I mean, I haven't done anything since Christmas.
Pam clearly has just given up trying.
Pam, stand up.
Hi, everyone.
My name is Pam and I wear glasses.
Hi, Pam.
Pretty disgusting.
So what we need to do is we need to get things going.
We need to get percolating a little bit.
Anybody have any ideas what we could do?
Any suggestions?
Yes, Andy.
What if we changed our outgoing answering machine message
so it just had a little more zing and a little more pep?
Zing and pep.
See, those are the kind of words we're looking for.
Yes, Jim.
What about if we did an even newer voicemail message
that had even more zing and pep?
Now we're cooking.
I like this.
Maybe a whole theme, like a rap,
a rap rhyme.
An urban thing.
An urban, yeah.
Stanley, you want to help us out with that?
Stanley, Earth to Stanley.
Not me.
Yes, you.
Come on, Stanley.
Put your little game down and join the group.
No.
Stanley, we're having a little brain...
Leave me alone, damn it.
We're having a brainstorm session.
Did I stutter?
Good. This is good.
I'm going to grab a glass of water.
I have told Michael on numerous occasions,
do not test me, and today he took it too far.
So f*** him.
Stanley's usually pretty grumpy,
but that was way past the line.
I blame gangster rap.
By talking back to me, Stanley was really saying,
you're not paying attention to me, Dad.
I want to act out.
I understand this because that's exactly what I did
when I was a kid.
Did it make my dad leave?
Maybe.
But Stanley can never make me leave
because I have a contract.
Can I talk to you a second?
Oh, what?
I really think that you need to address
what happened with Stanley this morning.
What are you blabbering about?
Nothing happened.
Well, you know, Stanley was openly insubordinate.
That, in the conference room?
Yeah.
We were joshing around, the two of us,
and he said, did I stutter?
And I said, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, dog.
I was joking, Toby, all right?
It didn't seem like he was joking.
Well, you don't get it, because Stanley is a beautiful,
sassy, powerful black man, and you're you.
If you had any friends, you would understand.
Friends joke with one another.
Hey, you're poor.
Well, hey, you're poor.
You're poor.
Well, hey, your mama's dead.
That's what friends do.
It's...you're so white.
All right.
Well, if you really believe that Stanley was joking,
why don't we go ask him now?
Okay, I will.
I'm not feeling very well right now, though.
My stomach hurts, so I may be going home early today.
You know, Michael, sometimes my daughter's stomach hurts
when there's a mean girl at school.
Well, sometimes my stomach hurts when you come into my office,
so it's probably psychological.
I like your frames.
Thanks, Phyllis. Yours, too.
Oh, I'm already married.
Boys don't make passes at girls who wear glasses.
Sorry.
Ignore her. Those glasses are so cool.
Really?
Yeah, you look like Lisa Lowe or Tina Fey or someone.
You should definitely wear them all the time.
Huh, maybe I will.
Guess who just became the cutest girl in the office?
Stanley is one of my oldest friends in this office.
He outweighs me by 100 pounds.
He's a type of friend that I could not see for 50 years,
and the second I saw him, I could make an insult about his mama,
and he would laugh, and I would laugh, and I'd...