Uh-huh. Nice. All done.
What's wrong, Michael?
I got gum in my hair.
You do?
This just stinks. Don't touch it. Please don't touch it!
You got a ton of dandruff.
Okay, let me be.
How'd you get gum in your hair?
I was walking in and I noticed something shiny under Stanley's car and I got under to see what it was and I messed up my hair.
All for a stupid piece of tin foil.
But best case scenario, you thought it was a quarter.
Kill me! Right now!
We have peanut butter in the kitchen.
I don't feel like peanut butter.
Get me an ice cream sandwich.
Nope, not for you. It's for your hair and it is 9am.
No, Dwight, not the good peanut butter. People are gonna get mad.
Hey, hey, hey. This is my hair we're talking about.
Smells good.
Tastes good too.
Oh, Donald, that's disgusting.
Wow, a lot of calories.
Well, just don't leave it on too long.
Keep massaging, please.
Oh, yeah, that's nice.
Hey, Michael, how was your date last night?
I will be honest, the dating has not been going well.
Look, men are visual creatures.
We crave beauty like a piece of fine art by any number of renowned artists
or an arty photograph of Cindy Crawford nude.
That, but the women I'm getting fixed up with are...
Not that they aren't nice or that have great personalities.
They just lack a certain Crawford-ness.
I am livid, absolutely livid.
It's ridiculous.
Yes, I'm having this grand brunch coming on one Saturday.
Oh, I have to work on one Saturday. I'm so distressed.
You know what, my Wall Street buddies, they work 100 hours a week.
God, those guys are rich.
How successful is Dunder Mifflin Infinity?
Well, tomorrow, Saturday morning, we all have to come in and re-enter sales
we already made in order to pretend that the website did it.
So, how successful does that sound?
So it's definite?
Looks like it.
Shoot, Jim and I were going to go to the Cherry Blossom Festival this weekend.
I'm sorry, your voice over my head like that?
Sorry.
Morning, Pam.
Hey, Ryan.
Wow, so refreshing to hear my name like that.
In New York, all the receptionists call me Mr. Howard.
It's so weird.
Do you want me to start calling you Mr. Howard?
No, no, we go way back. You keep calling me Ryan.
Okay, I will.
All right.
I presume you're here because of the website problem.
Stanley, give it up.
Yeah.
We still do it old school, right?
Even though I'm your boss's boss's boss.
Hey, Ryan.
Michael.
If you're wondering at all why I'm not giving you a more excited welcome,
I have been depressed.
That's okay.
You want to know why?
If it's private, it's private.
I can't not hug you.
Can't do it. Come here.
Come here.
What is that, linen?
Feels nice on my face.
Do do do do do do do do do.
The boss man cometh.
Mandy.
By the way, I am not mad at you, unlike some other people in this office.
My favorite branch.
Hey, man, you mind if I run something by you?
Love it. Go.
Well, I kind of feel like what we have going for us is our customer service.
And no matter how much we change this up,
I don't know that a website's going to be able to replace that.
I can tell you've thought about this a lot. I appreciate that.
Thanks.
David Wallace does, too.
You told him all about this at the Christmas party, right?
I, uh...
You did. Yeah.
Watch your back, Jim.
I'm just kidding.
Ladies and gentlemen, may I have your attention, please?
I know that a lot of you are very angry with Ryan
because he is the reason we all have to come in tomorrow.
However, I swear to God,
if any of you hurts him in any way emotionally or taunts him
or makes fun of his height or his half beard...
Okay. He...
Thanks, Michael.
Yeah.
I'm here today to do some creative problem solving
about Dunder Mifflin Infinity and field your questions.
Question.
Dwight.
Why am I being forced to come in tomorrow
and pretend that a website made sales that I made?
This is a temporary measure to increase the legitimacy of the site.
I don't like when my clients call me to help them use the website.
I'm not seeing commissions on that.
I hear you, Stanley. That is a great observation.
Problems like that will not happen
when we launch Dunder Mifflin Infinity 2.0.
When will that be?
TBD. Phyllis.
Did the police solve the problem with the...
Yes. Yes, they did. Yes, they did.
Yes. The social networking feature
of the Dunder Mifflin Infinity website
was infiltrated by sexual predators.
I don't understand why our website needs to have social networking at all.
Yeah, I actually have to agree with Dwight on that one.
It's all about creating a one-stop consumer experience, all right?
You're chatting with your friends.
You're talking about the latest music, about the election.
All of it is happening in our virtual paper store.
And then an older gentleman asks you boxers or briefs.
I don't get the big fuss here. I like the site.
If I had created a website with this many problems, I'd kill myself.
Do you have a question, Kelly?
Yeah, I have a lot of questions. Number one, how dare you?
Ryan has done a very good job, and I am not applauding sarcastically.
Think about it.
A month ago, nobody would go on this site
because we were worried about getting molested
or losing our identity, having it stolen.
But now, at a time, TDB, all of these problems will be in the past.
You're doing good, kid. You're doing good.
Well, it has been nice seeing you again, my friend.
You, too.
Oh, Ryan, I need a girlfriend so bad.
Michael, let me go. Let me go, Michael.
All right.
Do you know any girls in New York you might want to hook me up with
and might be interested in a guy like me?
No.
No. Sorry, man.
I'm sorry.
No.
Sorry, man.
Well, you tried.
But seriously, you should see the girls I meet at clubs in the city.
No. Unreal.
They sound great.
Bye, everyone.
Stay real, Scranton, all right?
Peace.
Would you have sex with Meredith?
What?
Do you think she'd keep it quiet?
I'm gonna go to my desk.
Jim, it's not the horniness, okay?
It's the loneliness. That's...
I know.
Let's go to New York.
We'll go clubbing with Ryan.
I can't.
Yes, you can. You're single. I'm single. It'll be awesome.
I'm not single.
Who are you dating?
Pam.
That's still going on?
Okay, Dwight, grab your stuff.
We're going to New York to party with Ryan and to meet girls.