Okay, well, I did not get the job in New York, but I got the real prize, domestic bliss.
Jan made me breakfast this morning.
Well, she bought the milk.
It's soy.
This is why I do it.
That's what I have to come home to.
She probably won't be up for a few hours.
This is going to be a very good year.
Very good.
Jan is at home.
Jim is back.
My protege, Ryan, is at corporate.
Good stuff.
Andy and Dwight are rocking the sales team.
I feel very blessed.
You know, generally it's not a good idea to click on any internet offers that you haven't
requested.
What was the exact offer?
It was for a video.
Yeah, what kind of video?
A celebrity sex tape.
Really?
What kind of celebrity?
It's not relevant.
How much did you pay for it?
Not relevant.
You paid for it?
It all happened so fast.
I broke up with Karen after the job interview.
And it was a little awkward when she came back from the city.
She told me very clearly that just because we were broken up didn't mean that she was
going anywhere because she had worked really hard for her career, but the next day her
desk was empty.
And as for me and my current romantic life, I'm single now and looking.
So if you know anybody.
Jim and I went to dinner a few times when he got back from New York.
I talked him through his breakup.
It's really nice to be good friends again.
Are you kidding me?
Pam and Jim are totally hooking up.
All they do is smile.
They're just keeping it a secret, right?
I don't know.
There is no evidence of intimacy.
They've been in remarkably good moods.
Could be other things.
Are you kidding me?
And Sunday I'm thinking of going to that flea market at the drive-in.
Well that sounds fun.
I'm mountain biking on Sunday and Montage Mountain.
Cool.
Yeah.
Well have fun with that.
Ladies and gentlemen, I have some bad news.
Meredith was hit by a car.
What?
Oh man.
It happened this morning in the parking lot.
I took her to the hospital and the doctors tried to save her life.
They did the best that they could and she is going to be okay.
What is wrong with you?
Why did you have to phrase it like that?
So she's really going to be fine?
Yes.
She has a slight pelvic fracture but people have survived far worse.
Thank god you were there.
Yeah.
Did you see who did it?
No need.
We can just check the security tapes.
Kind of a good news, bad news there.
I was able to be on the scene so quickly because I was in the car that hit her.
Who was driving?
Oh Michael.
One day Michael came in complaining about a speed bump on the highway.
I wonder who he ran over then.
You ran over Meredith this morning in the parking lot.
And saved her life, yes, by taking her to the hospital.
They cut back the Christmas gift.
Then no personal calls from work.
Now we get a run over.
I did get 25 points though for hitting Meredith.
Like in that movie, Death Race 2000.
I didn't get points for hitting people.
Do we need to do any clean up?
No.
I've been playing this game for a long time.
Let me tell you something.
Meredith ain't worth no 25 points.
Maybe she hit me.
You ever think of that?
She hit me?
I don't know whose fault it was.
I wasn't exactly looking at the road.
It's only Meredith.
Yeah, it's only Meredith, thank God.
But did you see the way they looked at me?
Like I was a murderer or something.
Hey.
Why did you do it?
It was an accident.
Was she talking back?
No.
She got sick of that face.
Did she owe you money?
Uh oh.
Is this downsizing?
Did she spurn your advances?
We should all go visit.
Yes, I guess we should.
Why is that?
I barely know the woman.
She sits all the way over there.
I have to visit Phyllis.
No, we should go visit and get her a gift.
If everyone puts in $5, we can get a nice bouquet.
That's a good idea.
I will put in $10 because I make more.
And you hit her with your car.
Maybe you should put in your whole damn salary.
Michael only hit her because she was late.
Show up on time and you've got nothing to fear.
That is not true.
It was a horrible accident.
She should sue you for a million dollars.
Okay, a million dollars.
What was she going to do with that pelvis?
Cure cancer?
What is he doing here?
The receptionist's porno crashed some hard drives.
It's okay, Pam.
We all do it.
Hey guys, we're all going to visit Meredith at lunch.
And we're kicking in $5 for flowers.
Who's we? You and Jim?
No, me and Stanley and Phyllis so far.
Oh, I bet Jim goes too.
Yeah, I haven't asked him yet.
Oh, I bet you ask.
I was planning on it.
I bet you were.
Angela?
Are you coming?
I can't.
Sprinkles is sick.
She's been sick for some time.
Thank you for asking.
No one asks about Sprinkles.
I have to give her her meds.
I have to pet her.
And who will she eat lunch with?
Can't your other cats keep her company?
There's bad blood, jealousies, clicks.
Angela, you are the chairman of the party planning committee.
I shouldn't even be planning this.
It's your job.
All right.
I've had Sprinkles for 16 years.
I adopted her when I graduated from accounting school.
I knew the kind of life I wanted,
one with the companionship and unpredictable good times only a cat offers.
Don't worry, Angela.
You can eat lunch alone with Sprinkles tomorrow.
Sometimes I curse the fact that I was gifted with the ability to party plan.
I mean, why couldn't I be a good-for-nothing fatso like the rest of this office?
Hello, Hunter. It's Michael.
Yes, Jan is fine. Awesome, fantastic.
Thank you for asking.
Is the man in?
So Ryan got promoted to corporate, where he is a little fish in a big pond.
Whereas back here in Scranton, I am still top dog in a fairly large pond.
So who is the real boss?
The dog or a fish?
Yes, Michael Scott.
Things might be different for him this year.
He can no longer protect himself by starting a sexual relationship with his boss.
Is Ryan my boss?
I don't know.
He is called the boss.
He has the power over me that a boss has.
So no, we are equals.
So I need a little treat for the gang.
Something to win their affections back.
Back? Why is that, Michael?
Well, I ran down Meredith in my car.
Oh, did you do this on purpose?
No, I was being negligent.
But she's in the hospital. She's fine, recovering nicely.
Tiny little crack in her pelvis.
Did this happen on company property?
Yes. It was on company property with company property.
So double jeopardy. We are fine.
I don't think you understand how jeopardy works.
Oh, right. I'm sorry.
What is we're fine?
People keep calling me a wonderkid.
I don't even know what that means.
I mean, I know what it means.
It means very successful for your age.
So I guess it makes sense.
That's a weird word.
Look, I'm not going to give you a prize for running over an employee.
Well, how does it benefit me for you to be in corporate if you don't call me some slack?
Oh, it's not going to benefit you to have me in corporate, Michael.
Well, then call me some slack.
I mean, come on. You rub my back, I'll rub yours.
Goodbye, Michael.
See ya.
Never made a sound.
I do not know what they were thinking.
Hey, Dee.
Hey, monkey. What's up?
Can you do me a little favor?
Go to my place at lunch and give Sprinkles her medicine.
Sure.
I have to visit the alky.
Check to see if she's faking.
If a car hit me, it wouldn't crack my pelvis.
You know what?
I bet you cracked it at home.
Jumped in front of the car to get some workers' comp.
I wouldn't put it past her.
My girlfriend, who you have never met, your loss,
is the only person I can ever imagine being with.
We go together like topsoil and manure,
like a tractor and a dozer blade,
like mulch and manure.
So what do you need me to do?
I wrote it out.
There's a diabetes shot.
Roll the insulin in your hands.
Don't shake it.
She gets an ACE inhibitor with her meal.
If you have to put her right in front of the dish,
or she won't see it because of the cataracts.
Mix one capsule of omega fatty acid in with her kidney medicine.
And you want to give that to her 15 minutes after she's eaten.
And, oh, there's a fungal cream
because she has this infection under her tail.
So you're going to have to lift her tail
and put the cream right at the base of her tail.
Hey, Toby.
Kelly, we're going to visit Meredith at lunch.
Kelly?
Well, Kelly's been so upset about Ryan dumping her
that she can't even talk.
I don't want to talk to anybody about Ryan.
Please, go away.
Okay, I have an announcement.
You pushed Darryl out the window.
No.
You shot Dwight.
No, no.
That is not funny.
I love my employees,
even though I hit one of you with my car,
for which I take full responsibility.
Look, I'm just trying to take everybody's mind
off of this unavoidable,
you know,
I'm trying to take everybody's mind off of this unavoidable,
tragedy,
and onto more positive things.
So I thought we should plant a tree.
Oh, good.
At least we don't have to work.
Okay, we're leaving for the hospital at one.
So, like a freedom tree.
I can take three people.
I can also take three people.
Separate cars.
Pam?
All right, we'll get a card at the hospital
and we'll sign it outside her room.
Pam.
Salespeople can go later in the day.
Hourly workers can go at lunch.
Okay, good, good.
So we'll just all go down there together at lunch.
Excellent.
I was thinking that we would...
Good work, Pam.
But if we...
Yay!
I think it would be kind of a lot.
Pam!
All right, since I am the boss,
I will drive as well.
Who wants shotgun?
You can't be serious.
You ran a woman over this morning.
Everyone inside the car was fine, Stanley.
Guess what?
I have flaws.
What are they?
Oh, I don't know.
I sing in the shower.
Sometimes I spend too much time volunteering.
Occasionally I'll hit someone with a car.
I'm not a good singer.
Occasionally I'll hit somebody with my car.
So sue me.
No.
Don't sue me.
That's the opposite of the point that I am trying to make.
Did you ever think of this?
Would a sober person walk in front of a car?
Hey-o!
I'm sorry, are you saying that Meredith was drunk at 9 a.m.?
Well, it's despicable.
That's not cool.
There's no proof of that.
That's not...
That seems early, even for her.
That's not what...
No, I'm not saying that.
That's disgusting.
Drunk?
No.
You can't get drunk off Kahlua.
It's just a kind of coffee.
Then what are you saying?
I am saying that maybe I was drunk.
Did you ever think of that?
Definitely not.
W-D-U-I.
That's...
Okay.
I am not a bad guy.
I am a good guy who runs over women with his car.
Why am I having such a hard time getting my message across?
Oh, I hate hospitals.
In my mind, they are associated with sickness.
Oh.
She looks like an angel.
She looks awful.
No, okay.
She always looks like that.
It was not my fault.
They don't have this kind of technology at the vet.
It's not fair.
It's fair.
You know what?
Why don't we go around the room and save one memory of Meredith?
I'll start.
I liked her jumpers.
They reminded me of kindergarten.
Jim?
I'll always remember Meredith's back.
That's all I can see from my desk.
All that red hair over a nice strong back.
Sometimes I pretend it's Carrot Top and he's going to turn around and tell a joke.
She was fun loving?
Okay.
No.
I said Jim.
I think she's awake.
No.
She's in a coma.
Okay.
Meredith.
I found all your friends from the office, dear.
At the same time.
Hello, Meredith.
This is weird.
Brought you some balloons.
Why don't we...
Here we go.
Tie these up.
Cheer up your tubes.
Oh, shh.
Oh, for God's sake.
Nurse?
No, don't bother the nurse.
Just put it back in.
I am going to be sick.
I am going to puke.
I was going to puke.
What are you doing?
Just give me that.
Thanks.
Does it hurt terribly?
No, that's not too bad.
They have me on a lot of pain killers.
Oh, really?
What kind?
Coding, Vicodin, Percocet, Fentanyl, Oxycontin, Paladone.
I have no idea.
It was really great of all of you to come and visit me at the same time.
I'll see you guys at the office.
Okay.
Wait up.
Guys, guys, guys.
Hold on a second.
You know what I was thinking might be sort of fun?
Is if you forgave me in front of everybody.
Michael, I'm not going to do that.
Because you know what they say in the Bible about forgiveness?
Forgiveness is next to godliness.
That's not a godliness.
Well, just shh.
You cracked my pelvis.
Look, I didn't crack your pelvis.
My car cracked your pelvis.
Okay, your car cracked my pelvis.
Look, I just.
You are not forgiven.
Apart from hitting her with my car, I have been so kind to that woman.
I have treated her like my grandmother.
Grancy, not Nana.
Meredith is no Nana.
So have you read about Iran in the newspaper?
Nope.
Please, spoiler alert.
I'm only up until last Monday.
So don't tell me anything about Iran or Iraq.
I want to be surprised.
So how's the view, old girl?
Oh, there's a cemetery.
You think that's affiliated with the hospital or is it like a separate picture?
Okay, okay, okay.
The nurse is here.
You guys, there's far too many people in this room.
That's what Pam was saying.
Bye.
Meredith, I came.
I want you to remember that.
Hey.
Is there any way that she received this injury due to a part of her anatomy that was just weak from birth?
It was probably more due to the 3,000 pound car knocking her down.
Okay.
You heard the doctor.
Probably.
So not for certain.
Jury is still out.
Thank you very much, doctor.
See you, mayor.
Water, my pills.
There you go.
There's nothing in here.
Hey.
Hey, monkey.
Any problems?
Well, you left the TV on and your cat is dead.
What?
Sparkles, the white one, is dead.
Sparkles.
That was the sick one, right?
Uh-huh.
I thought she had more time.
No.
Did she, look, when you saw her, how was she looking?
Really dead.
Like a, just a dead cat.
So, hey, come on.
Don't be sad.
Just, okay?
She's in a better place.
All right.
Actually, the place that she's in is the freezer.
Because of the odor.
It's going to be okay.
Okay, you know what?
Everybody, let's just get over the whole Meredith thing.
She cracked her pelvis, a tiny little crack, and she's going to be fine.
So let's just...
Michael, Angela's cat died.
Sprinkles?
Oh, shit.
I'm sorry, Angela.
Man, what a day, huh?
How could it get any worse?
The computer crashes with the porn and then Meredith with the accident
and then...
Prinkles?
God.
That's three things I'll tell you what's going on.
This office is cursed.
And we need to do something about it.
Why am I taking responsibility?
And it is up to me to get rid of the curse that hit Meredith with my car.
I'm not superstitious, but I am a little stitious.
Did anyone do anything involving an Indian burial ground?
Like what?
Like park on it or dig up a body.
Toby, do you have anything you want to tell us?
No, I did not violate an Indian burial ground.
In fact, I had some good luck recently.
Alfredo's Pizza picked my business card out of the basket, so I got a week of free pies.
That's cool.
Yeah.
Perfect.
So our tragedy is your good luck.
Satan.
Question, has anyone recently offended a gypsy?
We have to have done something wrong.
You ran over an employee.
That was the curse, Stan Lee, and we are trying to find the cause of the curse.
Sprinkles never hurt a soul.
God, in your infinite wisdom, how can you do this?
She wasn't ready. She had so much left to accomplish.
It is only a cat.
You never... you don't like them.
Cats do not provide milk or wool or meat.
Dwight, you haven't seen Meredith yet, have you?
No, I have not.
Well, I think you should go to the hospital and pay your respects.
I do not respect her, but I will go.
All right.
My cousin, Moses' best friend, was a dog.
One day, he was foaming at the mouth, so I had to shoot him dead.
Turns out he had only eaten one of Moses' cream pies.
Did I feel bad for killing him?
No. That's how you deal with a thief.
I would now like to talk about each of your individual religious beliefs.
Oh, Michael, you can't ask about religious beliefs.
Satan is a master of lies. Everything he says is the opposite.
All right, well, then you can ask about religious beliefs.
Thank you for the permission.
Psych!
All right, let's just go around the room.