I really didn't think I was gonna have a good time, but I did. I totally did.
I love camping.
Anything can happen.
Aw, it wasn't camping. It was more of a wilderness retreat.
Morning.
Michael.
Ryan invited some of the branch managers and Toby into the woods for a get-to-know-you weekend.
Michael wasn't invited.
Apparently they already knew everything they needed to know about him.
I thought it'd be a good idea to have a retreat with some guys that I like, but no one wanted to fund it.
Fix it, Ryan. Find a solution, Ryan.
Fine, guys. Did I mention it's a green retreat?
What happens next? Corporate funds your camping trip and all the cute secretaries are like, huh, check it out.
That new wunderkind guy is kind of a do-gooder.
I'll let you in on a little secret. No one ever does anything for the environment just to help the environment.
If someone tells you they have a green initiative, it's a scam.
Do I feel guilty? Please. I went surfing last weekend. The ocean's still there. Unseasonably warm, actually. It was gorgeous.
Did you sleep in cabins?
Under the stars. It was really beautiful. You should have come.
Bob and I took rock climbing lessons once.
Michael wasn't invited on Ryan's camping trip. Toby went, but Michael didn't go. He wasn't invited.
Who went?
Me, Dan from Buffalo, Mark Chisholm, Jeff from Albany, and Ryan, obviously.
We had so many s'mores I finally had to say. No more s'mores. No more s'mores.
Ryan invited me to go on his wilderness adventure retreat. It was this amazing, beautiful experience.
Hey, nobody cares. Nobody cares. I need that room at some point, so just wrap it up.
Michael wasn't invited.
Music
Knock, knock. Come in.
Oh, it's Creed's birthday today. Should we get him an ice cream cake, mint chocolate chip?
Pam, are you my friend?
Oh, no.
We have been friends forever, right?
Yes, I have been working with you forever.
Hypothetically, would you go camping with me if I were to ask you? And bear in mind that I would never actually ask you to go camping.
The gym is also a friend of mine, and I would rather die than make any sort of improper ovation toward you.
I don't think so.
Here's the thing. When Michael invents a hypothetical situation, he eventually turns it into an actual situation.
Do you understand that Jim is like a brother to me, and I would never do anything inappropriate?
I do.
So, as friends, would you go with me on a camping trip?
No.
Thank you for your honesty.
You're welcome. Open or closed?
Split the difference.
Hey, mint chocolate chip, please? Is Jim out there?
No.
Can you send Dwight in here?
Yeah. Dwight, Michael wants to see you in his office.
You want him to see me?
Mm-hmm. I have something very personal I would like to discuss.
Would you go find Jim and send him in here, please?
I'm on it.
Michael has employed Dwight to track you down.
How much time do we have?
Jim, Michael's office.
A couple minutes, give or take.
Now, Jim.
Hypothetically, if I were to ask you to go camping, and you know what hypothetical means, not real.
Got it.
So, if I were to hypothetically ask you to go camping with me, would you go?
Absolutely, yes.
When Michael plays the hypothetical game, I always say yes.