This is ridiculous.
I had tickets to see Tom Petty.
Well Friday nights are the nights that I pick up my outfits are Saturday nights.
Well I had to give the tickets to my ex-wife.
Or boyfriend.
Took a big loss.
Not that anybody cares.
There's a perception out there that working in the paper industry is glamorous.
But here's what the media doesn't show you.
Sometimes we have to stay late on a Friday night.
Did I just blow your mind?
Do you have any idea what time we'll get out of here?
Nobody likes to work late.
At least of all me.
Do you have plans tonight?
No I don't.
Remember when you told us not to make plans because we were working?
Yes I remember.
Mmm this is BS.
This is BS. Why are we here?
I am going to call corporate.
Enough is enough.
I'm Scott. I'm so mad.
This is Michael Scott.
Well we don't want to work.
No we don't.
It's not fair to these people.
These people are my friends and I care about them.
We're not going to do it.
Everybody I just got off the horn with corporate.
And basically I told them where they could stick their little overtime assignment.
Go enjoy your Friday.
Thank you Michael.
Well I think we dodged a bullet there.
I think we should celebrate.
You, Pam, me, Casa, little dinner dancing drinks.
You said you didn't have plans.
That's what you said.
Michael has asked Pam and me to dinner at least nine times.
And every time we've been able to get out of it.
But I got to give him credit.
He got me.
Because I'm starting to suspect that there was no assignment from corporate.
Michael, what time should I be arriving?
Dwight is couples only.
And besides I only have six wine glasses.
So it will be me and Jan and Pam and Jim.
And Angela and Andy.
Heyo!
Does it bother me that I wasn't invited to Michael's dinner party?
My ideal dinner party. Easy.
Jim Pam, Ryan, the mayor, Barack Obama, Shiloh Jolie Pitt,
because at the end of the night Brad or Angelina would have to come and pick him up.
And I would get to meet them.
Shiloh Beef, because of Disturbia.
All of the children of the world.
Val Kilmer, but he probably wouldn't come.
Too famous.
Obviously George Clooney.
And Jan, definitely.
If there was room.
It is really hard when you mess with this schedule like that.
I hate to see Tom Petty.
Well I'm sure the heartbreakers will be heartbroken.
No one even heard me.
I'll tell you about my ideal dinner party.
John Wilkes Booth, Lee Harvey Oswald, Osama Bin Laden, John Wayne Gacy, and Jeffrey Lionel Dahmer.
Oh, hey guys, welcome to my home.
Oh, here comes the waiter with the soup.
Hope you guys are hungry.
Meanwhile, the waiter subtly nods at me.
But I don't acknowledge him.
But I know he's an assassin, because I trained him.
Boom, two minutes later, five dead psychopaths at my dining room table.
All that's left to do is dispose of the bodies and collect the reward.
It's almost too easy.
A few hours later.
We can turn back, it's not too late.
We eat and we're out.
We have to wake up early tomorrow.
Yes, because it is Saturday.
Hi!
Hello! How are you?
Come on in. Good to see you.
I'm so glad we finally got to do this with you guys.
You want to take their coats, baby?
Yes, I would.
So, what have you been doing?
Let's see, since I saw you an hour ago?
Yeah, I have been getting ready.
And then driving over here.
Well, we've been doing pretty much the same thing.
Except driving.
We got you this.
Oh, well Pam, thank you.
This will be great to cook with.
We'll have a seat, or come on in, or I don't know.
Make yourself to home.
This is our casa.
Really nice.
So what do you guys think? Should we do the tour first?
Do we have appetizers first?
Tour. Let's do the tour first.
You have preference, babe? Upstairs first?
Totally your call, babe.
Alright, well, let's go then. I'd sneak upstairs.
Oh.
You guys doing a little construction?
Oh, just redoing the sliding glass door.
Yeah, so sorry about this god awful carpet.
We are still a work in progress here.