Yeah, everything! It's all good, it's all good.
Fill us.
Dancing babies.
Dancing babies. I love it, I love it.
We are making a commercial for Dunder Mifflin today.
Our first ad ever.
Corporate purchased some airtime in local markets
to spread the word about Dunder Mifflin Infinity
and they are even sending up a professional ad company
to help us make it later.
So, it's not too shabby.
Best ad ever.
Give me a break, give me a break.
Break me off a piece of that.
I am totally blocking.
What is the thing?
Nobody tell him.
What? No, why?
You got it, you're so close.
Break me off a piece of that.
Break me off a piece of that applesauce.
Piece of that Chrysler car.
Nope.
Football cream.
Okay, it's football cream.
It's football cream.
Alright, so, anybody else?
No bad ideas.
Everybody?
Let's keep them coming.
Okay, Toby.
Well, you know how everyone fast-forward
to ads these days?
Well, what about an ad in slow motion?
You know, if they fast-forward through it,
it'll just seem normal and it'll catch your eye.
Plus, the slogan could be,
Dunder Mifflin, we adapt to the pace of your business.
There are no bad ideas,
but for an idea that was really, really bad.
I spent three years in advertising before I came here.
And that is probably why most ads suck.
I'm taking a computer animation class
so I could try to do a logo.
Look at that.
Even the receptionist is getting in on the creativity.
Very good.
Oh, that's them.
Those are the ad guys.
Right there.
Alright, my very fortunate and creative group,
go back to your desk and I will let you know
when it is time to film.
Pam, Pam.
Here, sir.
Did you get the memo about dressing your best?
Yeah.
About dressing your best today?
Yeah, I distribute so I get all the memos.
Cool.
I just wanted to make sure you got it.
Yeah, I get all the memos.
Okay, good.
Good.
Hello, hello.
Hey, how you doing?
Michael Scott, your usual manager.
Hi, Michael.
Nice to meet you.
Excited to talk ideas.
Us too, man.
You know what?
I want this to be cutting edge.
I want it to be fast, quick cuts, you know,
youthful sort of MTV on crack kind of thing.
That sounds great.
Alright, good.
Well, this is what we have to work with.
This is Pam Beasley representing our Girl Next Door team.
She's our Girl Next Door.
Pretty, but nothing special.
You know, but she sort of keeps it real.
What you might want to do is if you could zoom in,
like really quick zooms on her.
Might be good.
These are our accountants.
And as you can see, they are very different sizes.
What you might want to do is kind of a Papa Bear,
Mama Bear, Baby Bear thing.
That might be kind of fun.
Mama Bear.
Creed is the old guy over there.
Don't look at him.
You might want to use him to sort of get that Orville Redenbacher
dynamic going.
Sure.
And if not, you know, we just make him disappear.
This is Jim Halpert.
Jim has a very expressive face, don't you, Jim?
He is like our Mr. Bean.
So do, do sad, do the sad face.
I don't know.
Skeptical.
Do sad.
That's a pence of pirate.
That's annoyed.
Well, he doesn't do very well under pressure.
You know.
I would like you to meet Andrew Bernard, the Nard Dog.
Ooh, let the Nard Dog out.
He gives the best back rubs in the office.
That's true.
I give him mean back rub.
I also do good aromatherapy.
You just got Nard Dogged.
Now this gentleman right here is the key to our urban vibe.
Urban?
I grew up in a small town.
What about me seems urban to you?
Stanley is hilarious.
Phyllis is like our Mrs. Butterworth.
Kind of a less urban Aunt Jemima.
And anybody else?
We can just hire an actor to replace.
Follow me.
Let's get this moving.
I think it's great that the company's making a commercial.
Because not very many people have heard of us.
I mean, when I tell people that I work at Dunder Mifflin,
they think that we sell mufflers or muffins or mittens or...
And frankly, all of those sound better than paper, so I let it slide.
Damn it!
I'm taking a computer animation class.
And I can draw right into the program using this tablet,
but whenever I plug it in, the computer crashes.
It's like the company knows I'm doing something to expand myself.
Playing that game again?
Second Life is not a game.
It is a multi-user virtual environment.
It doesn't have points or scores.
It doesn't have winners or losers.
Oh, it has losers.
I signed up for Second Life about a year ago.
Back then, my life was so great that I literally wanted a second one.
In my second life, I was also a paper salesman,
and I was also named White.
Absolutely everything was the same, except I could fly.
Little girl in a field holding a flower.
We zoom back to find that she's in the desert, and the field is an oasis.
We zoom back further.
The desert is a sandbox in the world's largest resort hotel.
Zoom back further.
The hotel is actually the playground of the world's largest prison.
But we zoom back further.
I can tell that your time is valuable.
Actually, I don't get paid by the hour anymore, but thank you.
I get paid by the year.
That all sounds really, really ambitious.
Yeah, I know.
Why don't we show you what we did with the Nashville branch?
Mmm. Okay.