What is this?
Happy holidays Dwight.
But do not open it till Christmas.
You're so pathetic.
How long did this take you?
Three hours?
Five minutes actually.
I am a black belt in gift wrapping.
Yeah, no such thing.
They don't give out black belts for things that are stupid.
Well, I hope it was worth it, because I'm going to take it apart in about five minutes.
I think it'll take you a little bit longer than that.
Really?
If I can skin a mule deer in less than ten minutes, I ought to be able to cut my...
I'm sorry, it's the largest one I have.
I will not be the big guy in the tiny hat.
This is the first Christmas party I'm throwing as head of the party planning committee.
The theme is night in Morocco.
This isn't your grandmother's Christmas party.
Unless of course she's from Morocco, in which case it's very accurate.
Hey Phyllis, do I need this invite to get into the party?
Yes.
Awesome.
I think this is going to be the best Christmas party ever.
Angela, you're going to move this for the party, right?
It's not on theme.
It's the nativity scene.
All right.
You can keep your camel, sheep, elephant, and the North African king.
Can you stay?
Everything else goes in the drawer.
I am not going to judge Phyllis for desecrating Christmas.
There is one person who will though, and Phyllis just stuffed him into a drawer.
I need you to get rid of the tree.
What?
Thank you.
I do not mind doing hard labor.
Ronald Reagan got his start as a stock boy lugging heavy boxes ten hours a day.
Don't mess with Phyllis.
And he went on to become the president of a party planning committee I like to call
the United States of America.
Most people call it that.
Did you know that an ant can carry five times its own weight?
All it needs is a strong queen to tell it what to do.
And there's nothing that little creature can't accomplish.
I don't think it's blackmail.
Angela just does what I ask her to do so I won't tell everyone that she's cheating on
Andy with Dwight.
I think for it to be blackmail, it would have to be a formal letter.
You brought in your doll collection.
These are not dolls, Jim.
These are commodities, the same as gold or oil.
Every year I do research to determine which toy will be the most popular of the Christmas
season.
This year it's a doll, half girl, half unicorn.
Match phrase, my horn can pierce the sky.
Pathetic.
I bought out every store in the area over the last couple of weeks.
And as lazy parents become more desperate, I will sell them at an enormous profit.
Isn't that right, Princess?
That's the Christmas spirit.
I am simply punishing those parents that would wait till the last minute to give their child
a gift.
And such a genetically improbable one.
Look at that.
How does that happen?
The king has sex with a unicorn.
A man with a horn has sex with a royal horse.
Oh hey, is that Princess Unicorn?
I thought they were all sold out.
They are now.
Cool.
My horn can pierce the sky.
The Christmas party doesn't start for another hour.
So I think we should just work until then.
I'm just kidding.
That was my nerd character.
What we are going to do is have a little pre-party before the party, which is what I think we
should do.
Have pre-party, dude.
That's my surfer, dude.
I love the stage.
French guy.
How long is this going to take?
Hey, don't pressure the bartender.
S the H. Might mess up the drink.
Hey.
I would love to open my own bar.
I have a pool table, a couple of dart boards, I have an open mic night, but a real one.
You know, one that anybody could use.
Where they would actually let you finish your god damn routine.
All right.
Do we have to take off our shoes?
Sorry, Toby, but if you really want to experience Morocco, that's what would happen.
This is equal parts.
Scotch, absinthe, rum, gin, vermouth, triple sec, and two packs of Splenda.
Call it a one of everything.
Oh my god.
Hit me again.
All right.
One more time around the block.
I will grant you one wish.
I wish you would stop running that lamp in that creepy way.
Stupid.
Everybody knows to ask for a hundred more wishes.
Dumb.
Musical instruments are very complicated.
When you first pick one up, she's a mystery.
But once you get to know her, you learn how to play her, the two of you can make beautiful
music together.
I wish women were the same way.
Hey, hey.
Ants, check it out.
There's a place in France where the naked ladies dance.
Really, Andy?
It's Christmas and you're singing about nudity in France.
Jim, check that out.
What is it?
That is vodka and I mixed it with orange juice.
I call it an orange vod juice cup.
Wow, that is delicious.
Yeah.
I can't believe no one's thought of that.
I know.
This man is a genius.
Thank you.
Another one.
Well, I have one all hooked up for you there from your genius friend.
Another red wine, please.
Another red wine.
Actually, can I interest you in some sangria?
Now, this is red wine with fruit mixed in it, Stanley.
And stew is red wine with me, Dan and Michael.
I'd like a red wine, please.
Okay.
Red wine.
There you go.
Thank you.
I can't get a simple red wine.
How about some sangria with some peppermint schnapps?
The doctor is Amy.
You call that sex on the couch?
Ugh.
Okay.
No.
Double chair is the worst one in the mess you're in.
Oh, yeah.
Belly dancing.
120, 180, 200.
All right.
Thank you so much.
My daughter is gonna love this.
Oh, so glad I could help.
Merry Christmas.
You too.
Fa la la la la la la la la la la la la.
Oh, so this is what every day would be like if you hadn't left India.
Oh!
Oh, my God!
We got a live one!
Oh!
All right.
She went up quick, so she's definitely a witch.
Or she's definitely not a witch.
I used to know this stuff.
Honestly, Meredith, it's not so bad.
Yeah, and you kinda needed a haircut anyway.
It's completely uneven.
No, it's cute and spiky and fun.
Oh, you know who you look like?
Rihanna.
Or you could just shave it all off and then you'd look like Pink or Natalie Portman.
You really think I look okay?
Yeah.
Mm-hmm.
You know, when Ryan broke up with me and I was miserable, nobody cared.