Yeah, that's no problem.
Pam. Sure.
Uh-huh.
Pam, knock, knock.
I'm on the phone.
I know you are. Knock, knock.
You can fax it over.
Yeah, 570-555-
491-74-7-
5-0175.
Thank you. Bye-bye.
That really makes us look unprofessional.
They would never know it was me doing it.
Here we go. Knock, knock.
Who's there?
Buddha.
Buddha who?
Buddha that spread for me.
Great.
I need something to wipe my head.
There's butter on my nuts.
That was melting.
That was a classic.
I got a knock-knock joke.
No.
Michael, please. Please, please.
Please let me.
All right.
Knock, knock.
Who's there?
KGB.
KGB?
Viva Ask the Questions!
What the hell was that?
What are you doing?
Hey, hey! Stop it! Stop it!
You like that?
Hey, come on!
What are you doing?
Mine is part of a hilarious joke!
Mine was retribution.
What are you doing?
No more knock-knock jokes.
That's it.
Ding-dong.
Who's there?
KGB.
Try and get the door.
I'm not answering the door.
Answer the door.
Ding-dong.
No way.
It's the KGB.
Ding-dong.
I'm not answering that.
Yes, you're going to.
You answer it.
I'm not going to answer it.
It's the KGB.
The KGB will fit for no one!
It's true.
Hey, Ken.
How was your weekend?
Good.
Hey, Kim. How was your weekend?
Good. I watched TV for fourteen hours.
Hold the door, please.
Hi, Kevin.
Hey, Lynn.
Did you get my message?
Um, yeah. I've been really busy.
Oh. It's okay.
Yeah, I'm probably gonna be busy for the next twenty days or so.
So, yeah.
Bye.
You're going to be busy for the next twenty days or so.
I thought you liked Lynn.
I do like Lynn. That's what Andy told me to say.
Andy offered to help me, and I said yes, absolutely.
Because other than getting laid, I don't know that much about women.
I was raised to be a gentleman around women.
But when your fiancé is Satan, that doesn't work.
So I have some new ideas and new techniques, and I'm trying them out.
Kevin Malone is my guinea pig.
Good morning, Michael.
Oh, no, no, no, no. I am not Michael. I am Willy Wonka.
Good morning, Mr. Wonka. Here are your messages.
Why, thank you very much. What are those? What are those? Tell me, please.
Jelly beans.
No, no, no. They are not just ordinary jelly beans, little girl.
These are extraordinary jelly beans.
The Willy Wonka golden ticket promotional idea is probably the best idea I have ever had.
It's probably the best idea anybody has ever had.
Three days ago, I slipped five pieces of gold paper into random paper shipments.
This entitles the customer to ten percent off of their total order.
It will be a day for them that is full of whimsy and full of excitement and full of fantasy.
I've written these things because it is my responsibility as manager of this branch to profiligate great ideas.
And I think I have done my part with the golden ticket promotion.
Now it is your turn. I want to hear some great ideas from you that are just as good as mine.
We own our own delivery trucks. We could lease them out on the weekends.
Too many words. Good ideas are simple. Golden ticket.
Free paper.
No, Jim, we're a business. Post-its. That is a golden ticket idea.
NASA took five or six golden ticket ideas to get men on the moon.
Golden girls? That's a golden ticket idea, right? How great was that, Joe?
That's a golden grams. Another. Is it? I don't get this.
No, you don't. No.
What will be the state of this company if I am the only one coming up with the great ideas? Right?
I think I should call her.
No. No. No.
Why is it so bad for me to call and ask her to lunch today?
You're making it too easy for her. You're just conveying, oh, I like you just the way you are.
But I do like her just the way she is. Well, that's not what we agreed on.
What are you doing? Huh?
Why don't you just go on a date with her? Try to spark up an ongoing joke and then in a month or two, if it feels right, you'll know.
No. You don't have to wait that long. I mean, you don't have to wait a month to ask her out. Just ask her out.
You're asking him to give up all of his power. What power?
Andy, Pam, and Jim are all telling me how to deal with this girl that I like.
Lynn, I don't like getting advice from more than one person at a time. I'm a textbook over thinker.
You can't let a girl feel good about herself. It will backfire on you.
Every compliment has to be backhanded. Oh, I like your dress, but I'd like it more if you had prettier hair.
That's psychotic. Do you guys actually do that?
Oh, guys with girlfriends don't. That's low, Tuna.