Wow, you guys look amazing.
Stanley, I thought you hated Halloween.
Shh. He wears it so he can sleep at his desk.
Who are you?
I'm Carrie Bradshaw from Sex and the City.
I like your shoes.
Thank you.
Will you help walk me to the fax machine?
Sure.
I got her. I got her.
I can help you.
You look amazing.
Inappropriate. Thank you.
Who are you? Larry King?
Gordon Gekko.
Oh, from the insurance commercials.
Yeah.
Whoa.
Awesome.
Let's put a smile on that face.
Damn it, Creed.
I've been up since four.
Well.
Sweet stume, dude.
Who are you supposed to be?
Dave.
I'm not sure.
Cool.
You are...
a cat.
We were looking for a kitten.
Oh. Give me one second.
Jim Halpert.
Hey.
Hey, New York. Happy Halloween.
Thanks. My costume's getting a lot of attention.
So apparently no one dresses up for Halloween here.
I wish I'd known that before I used grease paint for my mustache.
And I can't even take off my hat
because then I'm Hitler.
Wanna see a magic trick?
I'm gonna make a pencil dis...
Disappear.
MUSIC
Okay, I think we are set.
We have puzzles, string for cat's cradles.
Burn this last night.
Little road trip CD.
Puppets.
Look at all this stuff.
It's only seven hours.
When corporate found out that we were dating,
they decided they were going to transfer Holly
back to her old branch in Nashua, New Hampshire.
Michael's taking a personal day to move me out.
Roadtrip!
Right?
Breaker one night. Copy?
Copy that, Breaker.
Those Duke boys are at it again.
Hey! Do not touch my radio.
We're not...
Kidding.
We're not doing anything.
It's been a weird week since we found out I had a transfer.
Michael wanted me to quit and get some job here in Scranton.
And I said, well, why don't you quit and get some job in Nashua?
And he said, I asked you first.
And I said, first. At the same time he did.
And then I said, jinx.
And then we never talked about it again
and haven't been back to the conversation.
We'll miss you.
Well, I'll be around.
It's in a seven-hour drive.
Well, it's not that bad.
But if I'm really jonesing to see you guys, I can always fly.
I don't know if it'll be shorter to fly.
You have to drive to Boston, right?
That's an hour and a half.
Get there an hour before the flight.
Now you're up two and a half hours.
The flight to Philadelphia is an hour 15.
It's another two and a half hour drive to Scranton,
assuming there's no traffic.
Well, I just want to say goodbye.
Okay.
You know how?
This is it.
Um, yeah, that's not going to happen.
Yeah, but you have to admit, it would be wild.
So you're dumping Michael? Smart.
No, we're going to do the long-distance thing.
Oh, you guys are going to keep dating?
That's so romantic.
I almost quit my job so I could be closer to Bob.
And we're in the same building.
Oh, well, look, we can always call or email, right?
I should get all your email addresses.
Yes, we'll email you and then you'll have our addresses.
It's a little sad.
Michael and I just started dating.
He wants me to stay and get a job around here as a baker
or baker's helper.
This is going to be awesome.
I decided that on my drives to Nashua,
I am going to learn French, the language of love.
And on my drives back, I am going to learn Spanish,
what the cleaning crew speaks.
I'm driving him up for five times
when I would have made it work.
I thought I made a good deal.
Then I realized I'm going to be trapped in a truck
with Mike all day.
All right, everybody, I am out of here.
Jim, you are in charge.
Oh, I'll walk you out.
Ah, you are quite the gentleman.
You can let people go a couple minutes early if you want.
All right, we'll see.
I am off to New York.
My brother Pete from Boston and my brother Tom from New Jersey
are taking Pam and I out.