What's this?
Looks like a red wire.
Well, I wasn't here before.
Well, it's a computer, do I?
I mean, computers have wires.
Yours doesn't.
Doesn't it?
No.
It's going in a different direction than the other wires.
Dwight, I'm really busy.
I can't talk about this anymore.
Dwight!
Just shut up.
How did you?
I got 500 feet of red wire at a flea market up by Dunmore High School.
20 bucks for the whole spool.
Crazy.
What a deal.
Oh, he'll be fine.
I made it up there.
What you talking about, Wallace?
Hi, Michael.
How are you?
I'm well.
Very good.
So, listen.
As you know, we haven't yet filled the regional supervisor job.
Oh, have you not?
Correct.
And I was wondering if I could get you to do some of the field work that would normally
go to the supervisor.
Okay?
There's an area from Carbondale to Marshbrook where you've never done any business.
There's a small company there, Prince Paper.
I can't get a report on it because it's not a public company.
But we've been talking about going after their market, so I was hoping you could do some
fact finding for me.
Okay.
I'll fax over some of the things we're looking for, okay?
Fax?
Why don't you just send it over on a dinosaur?
This is important, Michael.
Oh, well then email it, David.
This is a doggy dog world, and I am a shark who eats doggy dogs.
I am going to pull it down underwater and drown it.
I am going to be one of those insane sharks who jumps up on the pier and grabs the doggy
dog and pulls it back on the way down.
You've got no taste, Stanley Hudson.
Oh, I do.
What are you guys talking about?
Some actress, whether she's hot.
Who's the gallon question?
Hilary Swank.
Ah, Hilary Swank.
Not at all, man.
She's gonna be nice.
Have you seen her with her bangs?
She looks like a monster.
Guys, she is a beautiful movie star, so maybe we should just go to work.
She is an amazing actress.
That's not the question.
She's not hot.
Yeah, thank you, fellas.
Okay, okay, okay.
Why don't we just put this to a vote, and then we'll be done with it.
I'm not voting.
No one cares.
Who thinks that Hilary Swank is hot?
Raise your hand.
Okay, and who thinks that Hilary Swank is not hot?
Five.
Five to five.
Thank you, accounting department.
So what do we do now?
What if the owner of Prince Family Paper has a beautiful daughter and we have to seduce
her in order to get their secrets?
I will seduce her.
No, I want to seduce her.
I'll seduce her.
Let me seduce her.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Michael, please.
Can I seduce her?
I got it.
So what if I did?
That would take precedence and I would expect your support.
Okay, so let's go over the plan again.
Alright, I am a local business owner.
I need to buy paper.
I find out everything about their prices and policies.
Your fictitious name?
Michael Skarn.
Good.
I am a paper salesman looking for a new job.
I find out everything about their expenses and salaries.
Then we meet at the Denny's and we compare notes.
No, I never said Denny's.
IHOP.
No, I said Denny.
You know how I feel about IHOP.
Socialist.
I don't want to get into this debate again.
Okay.
I enjoy IHOP.
I'll have a cup of coffee.
You will have pancakes and you'll like it.
The store next to them has released.
So what?
Means they're not expanding.
Maybe they're shrinking.
No.
It could be shrinking.
No, because the sign is centered perfectly above their store.
No sign of the sign being moved.
Uh-huh.
No.
It's lunchtime, but no sign of anyone coming in or out, which means they're not taking
new customers out to lunch.
Uh-huh.
Which means they're not acquiring new business.
So once again, no growth.
No.
And there are clouds.
Clouds in the sky.
It's going to rain.
Bad for business.
Well, it would if they were also cumulus and not serostratus.
Why are you all...
Okay.
Michael.
Whatever.
You're clouds, right?
Shut up.
Okay.
So you go in now.
I'm going to go in in exactly ten minutes.
We have never met each other.
We are complete strangers.
Right.
Also, we're going to need a signal to bolt out of there in case there is danger.
Fine.
And that signal is lick your lips.
Try it.
No, no, no.
Like this.
Good.
Ready to do this?
Yeah.
All right.
Here come the sharks.