This morning, the phone guy comes in and he shows Michael that our phones have a PA function.
And then he just... left.
This is your captain speaking.
The office will be flying at an altitude of two stories.
Look out your left hand window and you will see Vance Refrigeration.
I am the ghost of salesmen past. Do not come near me.
Yes, Michael Scott for Dr. Johnson, please.
Hello, doctor. I was just following up about my mole again.
Now, I was looking online about sebaceous snits that I had not been squeezing.
Could I stick it with a pin?
Uh...
Toby Flunderson to the principal's office. Your mother called.
And it appears that you wet the med again.
So you have to get home and wash your sheets because they're yellow and they're wet with your urine.
And at six foot six on the University of North Carolina, Jim Hedberg!
That's pretty funny.
Hey, you know what? Did I drop my... what the heck?
Did you find it?
I didn't. I'll look somewhere else.
Alright.
Would you like fries with that? Please drive around.
Hello?
Good morning.
You ready?
And we're off. Like a herd of turtles.
Well, Pam and I have eloped. Actually, we just robbed a bank. And we are on the lam.
Seriously, I am on a lecture circuit.
Apparently, Scranton has the best sales of any regional branch.
So David Wallace has asked me to go to all the branches.
Except Nashua, still a little bit raw there.
But I'm going to these branches and I'm telling them my secret recipe for success.
My eleven business herbs and spices in a sales batter.
Oh, that.
Well, that is Pam. Pam is coming along as my assistant and my driver so I can focus.
And I like to pack heavy.
He brought a sled.
No, that is a toboggan. You never know when you're going to find a snowy hill.
So every magician has a hot assistant and every rock star has a roadie and Pam is my hot roadie.
Yeah. I love being on the road.
But I especially love the time and a half pay, 24 hours a day for three days.
Because I have a mortgage now. Got to bring home the bucks.
No, don't say bucks. It's not ladylike.
Here we go. Okay.
So what we do is we drive all day and we stay in hotels together.
Separate rooms.
Well, that goes without saying.
I'm going to say it anyway.
Hey, look at what you're wearing again.
Pam, have you ever seen a magician's assistant?
This is a new cardigan.
Kind of blech.
Maybe you could tie it around your waist.
Or lose the shirt underneath or something.
No.
Oh. All right.
Pam is off with Michael earning money for our nest egg.
Man, I love that girl.
You know what's funny?
Sometimes I'll just wake up in the morning and I'll be looking at her in the early light while she's still asleep.
And I'll drag this shoelace across her face and I'll yell, Pam, wake up.
There's a bug on your face.
She wakes up screaming.
I really miss that.
Hey, Kelly.
Screw you.
Excuse me. That is no way to address a superior.
Oh, yeah?
Screw you, too.
Whoa. What was that all about?
You forgot her birthday.
It was yesterday.
Go ahead. You do it.
Okay.
I insist.
Basically, after Phyllis blackmailed Angela, Michael asked them both to step down from the party planning committee because there was too much drama.
What he said was...
Just easy.
There was a problem with having one head of the party planning committee.
She becomes too powerful, so he appointed two heads.
Party planning?
This is literally the stupidest thing we've ever done.
This is humiliating.
That's on my side.
So this is fun.
My birthday was yesterday and everybody forgot.
I got really dressed up and excited and no one said a word.
There wasn't even a party.
I think sometimes people are really mean to the hot, popular girl.
I reprinted my vendor's list for parties.
It's a list of birthdays, half birthdays, minutes from past parties, and an enemies list.
You're gonna need it.
If there's some cat stuff mixed in here, I'd appreciate you returning it to me.
Of course.
I wish you two the best of luck.
Thank you.
Angela.
Dwight and I would like to say that we'd be honored if you would stay on as a member of the committee.
And we think you could even run it and take care of everything and we would not get in your way.
Well, that is a great idea.
Nice try. It's your problem now.
Run it? Coming in a little hot, are we?
She responds to power.
You know what? Why don't you start going through this?
Can I turn on the radio?
No. I need silence or Sam Kenison to prepare.
But then you fall asleep and there's nothing for me to do.
Then listen to your iPod, Pam.
That's dangerous.
Well, then hey. You know what? Let's just talk.
That's okay. I can... I'm fine. I'll just...