Hey everybody, I have some wonderful news.
As leader of this office, I would like to personally congratulate Daryl, Stanley, and
maybe Kelly on the inauguration of our next president, Mr. Barack Obama.
And for everything that that means, that racism is officially dead.
Stand up you three.
I'm not black.
Really?
Okay, whatever.
Stand up you two.
Come on.
Don't be shy.
See now, now that an African American is in office, you guys are the man.
You guys are whitey.
And suddenly, you're the ones who can't jump or dance or do math.
Do you understand the responsibility that that has put upon your shoulders?
Do you have any idea how often you are going to have to bite your tongue now?
And I'm not talking just about race.
I am talking about the obesity epidemic that's going on over here.
Or the fact that somebody is gay and acts like it and looks like it.
No, no, see, here's the thing.
I can say these things.
You guys can't anymore.
You can't do it.
You can't say that.
Are you up to the task?
Oh, no, no, no.
You know what?
Nothing about white people either.
You can't.
And I expect that you treat me with the same amount of respect that I have treated you
all these years.
And you can't call us honky because that is something we only say to each other as a term
of affection.
And from you, it's just a little too charged.
Wow, I don't think honky has been used for 35 years or so.
Not to your face, am I right?
No doubt.
I'm a honky.
Okay.
So, you guys ready?
You guys up to the task?
Yes.
Can I say a few words?
Oh, yeah.
Oh my God.
This is your time.
You have two minutes.
As the social leaders, there will be some new rules.
Our food will be slightly spicier.
Public radio is now private.
Cut it out with the Jonas Brothers.
NASCAR is over.
No more Morgan Freeman movies.
Really?
Yeah.
These are more for you guys.
And no more Winter Olympics.
What?
Those are the best Olympics?
Stanley?
No.
But there's good news.
You can stop pretending like you like jazz music.
I like jazz.
Okay.
Okay, good.
Last week, I gave a fire safety talk and nobody paid any attention.
It's my own fault for using PowerPoint.
PowerPoint is boring.
Does anyone smell anything smoky?
Did you bring your jerky in again?
Oh my God.
Fire.
Oh my goodness.
What's the procedure?
What do we do, people?
The bones are dead.
Oh, how did that happen?
It's out in the hall.
No, we don't know that.
The smoke could be coming through an air duct.
Oh my God.
Okay, it's happening.
Everybody stay calm.
What's the procedure?
Stay f**king calm.
Everybody stay f**king calm down.
No, no, Michael, no.
Touch the handle.
If it's hot, there could be a fire in the hallway.
What does warm mean?
Oh my gosh.
Not a viable option.
What next?
Come to the other door.
Oh, here's a door.
Check that one out.
How's the handle?
It's warm.
Okay, go to the back door.
Well, another option.
Another option.
Geez.
Come on, everyone.
I forgot my purse.
Leave it, woman.
Get out of the way.
Go, go, go.
Things can be replaced.
Things can be replaced, Phyllis.
People, human lives, however, can...
My hand.
That's hot.
This one's hot, too.
Okay, we're trapped.
Everyone for himself.
Okay.
Let's go.
Get out of my way.
Okay, okay.
Have you ever seen a burn victim?
Move it.
Okay.
Procedure, procedure.
Excellent option.
Where do we go, folks?
Use a what to cover the mouth?
A what?
A rag.
A damp rag, perhaps.
Let's remember those procedures.
What are the options?
Okay.
That's the wrong way.
We've already tried that.
Remember your exit points.
Exit points, people.
What's next?
Oscar!
Stay alive.
I'm getting help.
Pull me up.
You're too heavy.
I only weigh 82 pounds.
Save Bandit!
How about 9-1-1?
Anyone?
9-1-1.
I'm going to die.
What do we do?
Use the surge of fear and adrenaline to sharpen your decision making.
Okay, I am not dying here.
Come on.
What is that?
The fire's shooting at us!
Look at the neighborhood fire!
It's going off!
You're trying to get us through here.
We're in.
We're inauthorized.
Help!
Oh my God!
No!
Attention!
Employees of Dunder Mifflin!
This has been a test of our emergency preparedness.
There is no fire.
It was only a simulation.
What?
Not real, this was merely a training exercise.
So, what have we learned?
Oh, come on, it's not real, Stanley.
Don't have a heart attack.
No, no, no, no, no, you will not die.
Stanley, Stanley, you will not die.
Stanley, Stanley, Iraqi's president.
You are black, Stanley.
I'm gonna give him mouth to mouth.
No, no, no, don't give him mouth to mouth for this.
You're gonna swallow this up.
Open your mouth.
Michael.
Don't swallow it.
I'm fine, leave me alone.
Save him.
How could you possibly think this is a good idea?
A lot of ideas were not appreciated in their time.
Electricity, shampoo.
You could have burned down the whole building.
I just want to say for the record,
I did not kill anyone.
Stanley was attacked by his own heart
and he should be released from the hospital
and back in the office in a couple days.
Did you shout fire, causing a panic?
Yes, I shouted fire, I shouted many things.
I also shouted instructions.
I was a little bit scared.