You gonna answer that, Kev?
Alright, thanks.
Dunder Mifflin, this is Kevin.
Please hold while I transfer you.
Oscar! Your mom!
Charles is having Kevin cover the phones for a while.
How do I say this diplomatically?
I think Kevin is doing exactly as well as anyone might have expected someone like him to perform in a position like that.
Please hold. Andy! Phone call!
Nope, stay there.
Kev, I thought we nailed the whole transfer thing earlier.
Yeah, I wrote it on my hand, but then I washed it.
It is transfer, extension, and then transfer again.
Okay. Andy, get ready. Transfer, extension, transfer.
Oh man.
It is one, three, four, Kev.
Kev, come on. Hustle.
You are murdering the Nardoc!
This is Kevin. Please hold and I will transfer you.
You're bad at this too.
Don't answer that call.
Just transfer the damn call.
Your call is very important to us. Please.
Hey!