Michael, since it is your 15th anniversary at the company,
I thought it might be appropriate to begin the festivities
with a 15-minute round of applause.
I like it.
Followed by a 15-minute moment of silence.
I don't know.
Is it classy enough?
Jim, enough with the classy, okay?
I just feel like after 15 years at this company,
bravo, by the way, that we should celebrate
with a very classy event, a night to remember.
I think you're right.
This party has to have all the excitement, drama,
and intrigue of my time here.
And, of course, classy.
And classy, yeah. Michael.
You're just agreeing with him because he's wearing a tux.
Don't you see what he's doing here?
Last week, Dwight sent out a memo about the dress code.
So this is me showing him that I'm taking it very seriously.
Oh, here's one.
A string quartet playing classy cowl music.
Mm.
You know, that's good, but it's not classy.
I need something classy,
like the opening of a car dealership.
That's it. Or Mr. Peanut.
Yes. Mr. Peanut is not classy.
Yes. He is a regular peanut.
He just happens to have a cane, a monocle, and a top hat.
That's what makes him classy.
Okay, how about this?
An ice sculpture shaped like you,
covered in chocolate, covered strawberries.
Oh, Dwight. You're trying too hard,
and that's just not classy.
See, the thing about classy is it's a state of mind.
Well, I'm sorry. I just don't know what classy is then.
Okay, let's just try this one on for size,
and I apologize,
because it's right off the top of my head.
An ice sculpture of you,
completely surrounded by a variety of chocolate-covered fruits.
Strawberries?
That's inspired. I said that!
Not classy.
Not classy at all.
De classe A. French?
Classy?
Ah.
Hi. Can I help you?
Yeah, I'm Charles Minor here to see Michael Scott.
Sure. Just one second, please have a seat.
Phone ringing
Yes?
Michael, there's a Charles Minor here to see you.
Minor? I hardly know her.
Hello?
Yeah, are you coming out now?
Uh-huh.
Well, well, well. Who have we here?
Ah, it is Prince Charles Minor.
At your service.
Everybody, this is Sir Charles Minor.
And he is the new VP for the Northeast Region.
So just give it up for this big guy, right?
Give it up!
Here he is. Hey.
There he is. Hi. Hi, William.
Wow! Hold that thought.
You know what? I want everybody to go into the break room.
I have a little surprise for you.
Go ahead. You too.
Dwight, would you escort our guests in there?
Come on. Here we go. Don't be shy.
Don't be shy. You're one of us.
Dwight, stall them a little bit to get the fish.
Hey, yes.
Really wish you had told me the new boss was coming today.
What? No. I don't want to make everybody nervous.
Nope. I mean, I could have brought a change of clothes.
You look dynamite.
What are you talking about? Very slick.
Okay. We got the fish.
Originally founded in 1866,
Scranton quickly became one of Pennsylvania's
largest anthracite coal mining communities.
Surprise!
There is nothing in here.
The real surprise is in the conference room.
Let's go! Ow!
God!
Okay. Come on. Come on.
I'll finish it up later, but
essentially what we're talking about is...
Surprise!
As you can see,
I turned the bagels from O's
into C's for Charles.
Thank you.
Took me all night.
This is what you did last night?
I met this guy at corporate last week,
and we were just
digging each other's vibe.
I was totally grooving on him, and vice versa.
Besides, the last two people to have his job
were Jan and Ryan.
The former was my lover,
and the latter my best friend.
So who knows?
I do.
It's gonna be mental!
It's going to be mental.
Oh, my God.
He's like a black George Clooney.
Really? I don't see it.
I mean, he's okay.
He's not unattractive.
Hey, how you doing?
I'm Jim Halpert from Sales.
Just wanted to say, if you need anything, let me know.
Why are you wearing a tuxedo?
I didn't think you'd notice.
It's funny, actually,
there's another salesman out here,
Dwight Trute. He sent out this memo,
as he always does, and it was about
professionalism in the workplace, and of course
he singled me out, so I just had to
mess with him.
Oh, you'd understand it
if you read the memo, which I should probably get you.
I'm gonna put it in the drawer.
It was pretty crazy.
But, uh,
not more crazy than wearing a tux
at work, I grant you that.
So I'm gonna, uh... Your name's Jim?
Jim Halpert, yep, so just gonna let you
get back to it, so...
He just had to wear his tux
today. I thought that'd be funny.
Took him 40 minutes to get ready.
I'm telling you and corporate
since somebody, it is big
trouble, or
really good news.
And then again, sometimes it just means
business as usual. Okay.
What do you think? Well, it's...
Why are you asking him? I just told you.
The real question here is who's
this guy work for?
Dr. Meflin.
Oh,
well it's all starting to make sense now.
I am nothing if not professional,
and if
Charles is going to be my
boss,
then it is my job,
no, it is my profession,
to get to know
him and to show him
exactly what I bring to
this branch, which is
competence and success.
And above all,
laughter and professionalism.
And above all, a sense of
whimsy.
All right, let me introduce you to some of the troops.
Accounting, front and center.
Coming up here, I'd like you to meet
somebody. This is the accounting
department. Hey, I come from
accounting too. Oh, nerd alert.
This is Oscar Martinez.
He is
Latino, and he
just got out of a long term relationship with
a man, Gil, who broke his
heart, but he didn't bring any of that into
work. It did not affect his job performance
whatsoever, and I'm very proud of him
for that. Hey, Oscar. It's good to meet
you. Good. This little
hell raiser is
Angela. She has slept with a bunch
of different guys in the office.
Right over there, the orange.
Hey, yo. Hey, yo. Where's
the other? You know, Michael,
I don't need to know everyone's sexual history.
Well, perfect, because we have
now arrived at Kevin, and he has no
sexual history. Hey,
how about I just say hi to everyone at one
time? Good, good, good, good. Everyone,
please give it up for Charles
Miner. Thank you, Michael. Thank you
for the C-shaped bagels.
Oh, well. Great. That's great.
Above and beyond. Hey, you know, we're in
tough times, and we're not immune to this
economy. That's true. But the goal is
to, you know, fight our way through this.
Stanley Hudson,
are there going to be layoffs? No,
absolutely not. Hold on, Michael. Thank you.
Stanley, you know, we
can't make any promises, but we'll try. Everything
in our power to avoid that. Do you
have specifics? Well,
Michael should have filled you in last week.
Well,
due to the economy, there's a lot of worry
going around. I didn't want to worry.
You didn't tell them. Well, why don't...
Yeah, what I told Michael is...
Charles is going to tell you. ...is that
we are cutting 3% across the board,
which means we will no longer be matching
401k contributions.
And all overtime requests
will need to come through the corporate office.
Fantastic. Well, it's not official.
It is official. Well... It is official.
And actually, guys, I'm encouraging branches
to consider a freeze on discretionary
spending. Such as
salary, benefits, etc., etc.,
insurance... Not salaries.
Petty cash supplies
and, you know, parties.
Things like that. Well... What about your party?
No. Okay, okay. You know what?
I think this has been great. I think
this gives us a lot to think about, doesn't it?
Charles Minor, ladies and gentlemen, is a long
trip home. Thank you for coming in.
We have to get back to work. Michael, I'm going to stay
for the day. Oh, no, no, no. You don't have to do that.
I've got this covered. This was just a meet and greet.
No, it's a little more involved than that. I'm going to set up in here, okay?
I am thrilled
that the new boss has taken such
an active interest in all of
the responsibilities that I'm supposed to have.
Thrilled.
David, it was my
understanding that I was not going
to be managed. What gave you that idea?
It was my understanding.
I see. Listen, why don't we just
leave that position vacant?
Truth be told, I think I thrive under
a lack of accountability. Look,
Michael, Charles is very qualified.
Get to know him. I really think
the two of you are going to make a great team.
But the branch is still mine? You're still
the branch manager, yes. And if you
need anything else at all, just let Charles know.
Ask him about the party.
Oh, right. David, are you coming to my 15th
anniversary party? I'll give it
my best shot, Michael. No, no, no, the other thing.
Okay. If we hire Cirque du Soleil as
salaried employees, will that help us with the year-end tax
stuff?
I think you hung up.
No.
I just got off the horn of David Walls,
and he said that you and I should try
to get to know each other better, and I agree.
So, what I
would like you to do is
tell me something
that you've never told anybody before.
No. Come on.
What's your wife's name?
Where did you work
before you came here? Saticoy Steel.
Beautiful.
See, African
Americans have such a rich
history of unusual
names. No, I worked at a company
called Saticoy Steel.
You're not from paper? No.
Does...