Are you swallowing them whole? You're eating them so fast, are they even touching your tongue?
Yeah.
Brownies, is that? Pastry cubes made of sugar and fat? No thank you, I'll stick with my jerky.
So why'd you come in here?
To socialize and inform.
Ooh, brownies! I'm taking two so I can parcel them up and eat them at my leisure later on. Much healthier.
You're taking two?
Yeah, but one of them is for Toby.
Yeah! Why don't you send that to him in Costa Rica?
I'm just gonna hand it to him right now.
Okay, weirdo.
Why's that? Why's that weird?
She said she was gonna give it to him right now.
She's probably going to because they sit next to each other.
Yeah, they used to.
Toby works here again.
Oh, can you imagine?