I had no idea when I got into that car to go to New York that I was going to be quitting.
I got on the ramp and I was like, two hours, two hours to go, feeling good, cranks and
tunes.
Should have peed before I left.
Michael, get to the good part.
Okay, so, get up the building.
Revolving door, broken.
So I have to take the normal door.
Oh my God.
At least he's in the building.
No, no.
I was so nervous it was the wrong building.
I had walked into the wrong building.
He finally has a story we really want to hear.
And he knows it.
Okay, focus, focus.
You're in the right building, you're with the right people.
What happened?
I looked at Wallace and I said, I quit.
And as I turned to leave, I looked back and I said, you have no idea how high I can fly.
You didn't tell him how sick of him you were?
Why would I do that?
Well, wouldn't it feel good to tell him that he's incompetent?
That he's wasted 15 years of your life?
Maybe spit in his face.
You guys have thought about this a lot more than I have.
I just winged it.
I love a good quitting story.
It makes me feel like I have control over my own life.
It gives me hope.
Maybe I'll have one of my own someday.
But I dream.
I'm sorry.
About a week ago, Michael gave us two weeks notice.
And surprisingly, there is a very big difference between Michael trying and Michael not trying.
Michael, is that scotch?
Scotch and Splenda.
Tastes like Splenda, gets drunk like scotch.
Clinky, clinky, clink.
Come on.
What am I going to do?
I'll tell you what I'm going to do.
I'm going to do a little bit of this, a little bit of that.
I'm going to stay up all day.
I'm going to sleep up all night.
I'm going to give it a ho, hey, ho.
And I'm going to stop worrying about calories.
Maybe you should go into your office, close the door, and make some calls about jobs.
I have a job.
For four more days.
Do you have any leads on a job?
Pamela, you don't understand.
At my level, you don't just look in the wanads for a job.
You're headhunted.
Have you called any headhunters?
Any good headhunter knows that I am available.
Any really good headhunter will storm your village at sunset with overwhelming force
and cut off your head with a ceremonial knife.
Right, because that's what we're talking about.
I need you to go over this clandestine.
Indicate any wrong or false data.
Your I need you to is my command.
Okay.
Hey, Michael.
Hey.
Can I talk to you for a minute?
You can talk to me for as long as you want, because I have all the time in the world.
Oh, God.
Oh, Phyllis.
I just wanted to tell you that...
Oh, what's that?
Oh, hey.
What is this about?
You know, because you're leaving and everything.
It's farewell.
Right.
So I hope I get to work with you someday again.
Me too.
Is this wine?
Ah, busted, yes.
I already have wine.
Oh.
Hello.
Hi.
Isaac Sylvie here for the interview.
Yes, please have a seat. It'll be a few minutes.
Thank you.
You interviewing too?
Hmm.
Hmm?
Interviewed?
For...
Regional manager?
Yes, I am.
For regional manager, I've decided to go with an outside hire.
For obvious reasons.
Where are you from?
Philly.
That's a drive.
Yeah, well, this is one of the few places that's hiring.
It's, uh...
It's brutal out there.
Pam?
Mm-hmm?
When will the new copier be ready?
I'm working on it, Kev.
You said it would be ready by today.
And it is today.
It'll be ready soon.
Soon couldn't mean anything.
Soon could be three weeks.
Is that what soon means to you?
Sometimes.
Then come back soon.
During the course of business,
a copier goes through something called normal wear and tear.
I think it's 75 cents.
That's a lot.
Bandit, no!
No, no, no!
I'm not going to do that.
Bandit, no!
No, no, no!
Yesterday, they delivered the new one.
But they didn't set it up.
So my day just got a little more interesting.
It's monster.com.
Singular.
Thank you.
You work in paper long enough, you get to know the players.
Hi.
You've reached Prince Paper.
We are sad to inform you that after 40 years of serving the community,
we are no longer in business.
Thank you for your support and may God bless you.
Bye.
What am I going to do?
Uh...
Oh, Michael, where are you going to go?
What are you going to do?
Well, this is going to give me a chance to spend some more time with my condo.
Yeah.
You know what I want to do?
I want to go to Mexico.
Just make jewelry, and be naked,
drink margaritas all day, have amazing sex.
Maybe I'll come.
No, you can't come.
It's just me and Charles.
Right.
Maybe you'd want a dog, though.
I don't want some weird Mexican dog.
Hey, Toby, I have a real quick question for you.
It's about a resume.
Sure.
So we might start with, say, your most recent thing, you know,
a summary of achievements.
What have you done here at Dunder Mifflin?
Regional Manager, Dickwad.
Okay, that's your title.
You know, how would you actually describe what you did?
Changed things.
Ushered in a new era of love and comedy and comedy and comedy and comedy.
A new era of love and comedy in the workplace.
Hired many, fired none, made money, lost money,
learned to stop counting.
This is our moment.
This is our time.
This next part should be sung, if possible.
Sst.
Yep.
You want me to come into your office?
No.
Okay.
All right.
Close your eyes.
I'd prefer not to.
Just close your eyes.
I'm going to start my own paper company.
You're starting your own paper company?
Yeah.
Why?
Can you believe it?
Because I know paper.
I know everything there is to know about paper.
Do you know that the industry is in decline?
Yeah.
Oh, God, I practically invented decline, right?
I know paper.
I know how to manage.
I have a name.
Close your eyes.
No, I did that before.
That is nothing.
Close them.
Okay.
All right.
I'm going to start my own paper company.
Close them.
Okay.
All right.
Michael Scott Paper Company.
You want in?
You want to be a part of this?
I am not going to do this.
Oh.
And you are not going to either.
Oh, agreed.
Except...
Here's the thing.
What I wish for you is that you land a job at a company that, A, exists and, B, has a salary,
because they're set up to do that kind of thing.
A-K.
What's up, Chuck?
Jim.
Hey.
What have you done?
Nothing.
Just talking.
Okay.
Michael handed in his two-week notice.
Did you also hand in your two-week...
I didn't.
No, okay.
After you.
No, I'm staying.
Good.
You want me to translate the German instructions for you?
No, I'm sure they're pretty much the same as the English instructions.
Typical American arrogance that got us involved in a war we never should have been in.
World War II.
Well, fine.
Did the German instructions say what this is supposed to do?
Deutsch.
Let me see here.
That is either an incense dispenser or a ceremonial sarcophagus.
Hm.
My German is pre-industrial and mostly religious.
Damn.
Listen, this order for him, instead of saying Dunder Mifflin at the top, is there any way
I could get it to say something else?
Like Michael Scott Paper Company?
Oh, somebody's been talking in bed.
Pillow talk.
Yeah.
Listen, Michael, have you really thought this through?
Because it's a pretty big risk.
This is a dream that I have had since lunch and I am not giving up on it now.
Yeah.
You could give it up though, right?
And almost no one would know.
Before you got here, I'm the one who landed all of these clients.
Half of them, at least.
I can do it again.
I know the market.
I know the price points.
I'm on it.
Don't worry.
So how do I do that?
Well, you can scan it and then you can upload the image and then you can copy a new image.
Could I take a piece of paper and just tape it with transparent tape?
Yeah.
Good.
Oh.
Thank you very much.
So that is why I have to leave at five on Tuesdays.
It's to pick up my little sisters from school.
We're really tight.
We're like the Kardashians.
You know, you can run this stuff by Toby.
Yeah, I don't like talking.
Come in.
I'm sorry.
I didn't realize you were with anyone.
But I just wanted to bring you the brochure on that accounting seminar that I was telling
you about earlier.
Okay, we're in the middle of something.
Actually, you know, it was so much fun last year.
There was a Sunday bar.
I mean, I didn't have any, you know, to stay trim.
Did Michael just let anybody in his office?
Yes.
He loved it.
He loved the Sultanate.
He loved facilitating all the time.
Yeah.
As I come in.
I am aware of the effect I have on women.
See, you should be heading back to your desk.