Well, I should go.
All right. I'll tell everybody here that you say hi.
No, don't. I'm mad at them.
Why? What happened?
Not one of them called to congratulate me on our engagement.
Ah. That?
They might be off the hook for it because I didn't tell them.
What? Why not?
I just didn't, you know, want a deal.
Come on. It won't be that bad.
Okay. You know what? Here we go.
Here we go.
Everybody, I just wanted to make an announcement.
Pam and I are engaged.
Hi, everyone.
I thought you were already engaged.
No. That was Roy. She was engaged to Roy.
Thank you, Angela.
I got a gift for Pam and Roy. Do I have to get another one?
Yes. A little close to my engagement there, Tuna.
What's your game here? To get married.
She's not a virgin, you know.
Wow. What's going on?
No, nothing. Nothing, Michael. Just saying hi.
The tall guy got engaged.
To be married? Yep.
Sorry.
Pencils down.
Just kidding. Take your time.
Today's ethics day.
After they finish the quiz, I'm going to run my first meeting here.
It's going to be insane.
No, it's not. I have to read from the binder.
You should probably be finishing up those questionnaires.
I'm going to read them.
Stop it.
What'd you get my number seven?
It's an ethics questionnaire.
Holly, Jim is...
Dwight's cheating.
Okay.
I got it. I got it.
Let's get ethical, ethical.
I want to get ethical.
Let's get into ethics, yeah.
Let me hear your dun-da-mif-la talk.
Your body talk.
Let me hear your body talk.
Woo! All right.
Why are you helping her? You're not even dating.
She's my friend.
And ultimately my strategy is to sort of merge the two.
I'm not going to be dating her.
I'm going to be dating her.
My strategy is to sort of merge this into a relationship
without her even knowing.
Oh.
Okay. Let's give it up for Miss Holly Franks.
Thanks, Michael.
Today we're going to have a business ethics seminar
because recently, without mentioning any names,
there's been some misconduct at corporate,
and we have a very strict ethics policy,
and that employee has been fired.
Come on. He's right there.
He was hired.
Ooh, check it out. Hired guy.
Okay. Elephant in the room.
Let's talk about it.
Do I regret what I did?
Of course I do.
Even though it was an amazing ride,
and I'll give you an example.
Anyone see Survivor, season six?
Anyone know Joanna on that show?
In New York City, I hooked up with a girl
who looked exactly like that.
Indistinguishable.
Okay. Well done.
Good speech, Ryan. You're a good guy.
Let's start discussing those questionnaires
that you filled in this morning.
It is wrong to make personal calls during work hours.
Now, some of you mark that you very strongly agree,
but ideally you would have selected totally agree.
I thought very strongly agree
sounded stronger than totally agree.
Corporate would like to emphasize that,
ideally, you would all totally agree with that statement.
Well, I think we can all totally agree
that Holly is totally fantastic.
Thank you.
Okay.
In fact, spending a half hour at the water cooler
during work hours is a form of stealing.
What?
Yes, it's called time theft,
and it's the same as taking money from the company.
Can anyone think of examples of things
that are over-the-line time wasters?
This meeting.
Can't set them up like that.
Why is it okay for smokers to take breaks all the time?
If I want to go outside and hang out once an hour,
then I'll just take up smoking. I'll do it. Okay.
I'll smoke with you. I got a bag of cigars in my purse.
Stealing office supplies is another big ethical area
that there seems to be some confusion about.
That's a big ethical area?
Listen, I would love to have an honest conversation
with management about ethics.
Why isn't the company doing better?
Hmm.
It could be the pad of posts
it took home last week.
Or it could be the $12 million in deferred compensation
and stock options they paid the CEO for a year
of substandard performance.
I'm sure we'll cover both in the seminar.
I've done some things I'm not proud of.
Committed some atrocities in Vietnam
two years ago.
Princess Cruise Lines.
During our honeymoon safari in Africa,
Bob and I were driving late at night
and he'd been drinking
and suddenly, thump.
We hit something with our jeep.
It was probably a man.
We didn't know what to do.
We heard the sound of a car
and we were like,
we didn't know what to do.
We heard the police were corrupt and they might beat us
so we just kept driving as fast as we could.
We bribed the airline,
got on a plane that night and fled home.
Maybe it was just an ostrich
and a soccer uniform.
Okay, can we have a moment?
Can I talk to you for a second?
A lot of good stuff.
And you look, you look
a little bit fantastic.
What should we be working on while you guys are talking?
Do some work.
People expect a lot
from these meetings. Laughter.
Sudden twists.
Surprise endings.
You need to be Robin Williams
and M. Night Shyamalan.
You need to be Robin Shyamalan.
I just have to get through the binder.
You're kind of losing them.
Don't think about the stakes.
I'll take you out.
Well, Michael makes a really good point.
So let's just open this up a little bit.
Say my name is Lauren
and here I am
shopping in a supermarket
and I steal a pencil.
That's not right.
Lauren, enough with the pencils.
No, I have to go over pencils and office supplies.
It's part of the ethics thing.
That isn't ethics.
Ethics is a real discussion of competing
conceptions of the good.
I use the corporate anti-shoplifting rules.
I'll drop an ethics bomb on you.
Would you steal bread
to feed your family?
Boom! Exactly, Andy.
Yeah, I took in short a philosophy
twice, no big deal.
It's a trick question. The bread is poisoned.
Also, it's not your real family.
You've been cuckolded by a stronger, smarter male.
No, that's
not how it works.
I would not
steal the bread.
And I would not let my family
go hungry.
What if you didn't have any money?
Well, I
would
get a job or I would own a farm.
Okay, you're fired.
There's a drought, locusts,
the whole thing. The farm is a money loser.
Then I would
steal a little bread, but just
the ends.
But what if that meant the baker's family would go hungry?
Doesn't the baker
have backup bread?
That was his backup bread you stole.
I didn't know I was stealing his backup bread.
Okay, okay.
Alright, you got me.
That was fun.
That was fun to think about. Wow, do you have any other
brain ticklers for us?
No, that was fun. But we should get back
to business. Wait, hey, Michael, you see that wall?
Yes. Okay, now look away from it.
You don't know if the wall is
still there. What do you mean? Of course it's still there.
Well, you don't know that because you're not looking
at it. What if it disappeared? Where would it go?
That's not, I don't know.
I know where the wall goes.
Okay, so you're saying
that if I'm not looking at the wall,
how do I know it's there? Yes. Easy.
Oh, alright.
How does the wall know
when I am looking at it?
Okay, I think we've gone too far off topic.
How do we know that
we are not on topic for a
different conversation?
Because it is not in the
binder. Binder?
I don't see a binder. I'm not looking
at the binder. How do I know the binder exists?
Binder?
I hardly knew it.
So, wow! Still there.
Unfortunately,
my binder does still
exist, so why don't a couple
of you keep an eye on the walls and the rest of us
will continue the discussion.
Very good. Stanley, you take the west wall, create
the east, I'll take the ceiling. Okay.
Thanks, Dwight. Alright.
Have any of you ever faced
any ethical dilemmas in the workplace?
Anybody?
This is a chance for you
to say something without any repercussions.
Stanley, Oscar,
come on. Pass.
I will go first.
When I discovered YouTube, I didn't work
for five days. I did
nothing. I viewed
Cookie Monster sings Chocolate Rain
about a thousand times.
What was the dilemma?
To tell you or not, and I'm
glad I did. I feel very, very good.
I'm cathartic.
I promise you that you are not going to get into trouble.
You can say anything you want
with total and complete immunity.
Oh, no, no. Yeah.
Come on. Anybody. Let it fly.
Once in a while,
I'll take a long lunch. A siesta.
Time thief. Time thief. Fire him.
Dwight, you've
really never stolen any company time.
Never. You are
a thief of joy.
Anybody else? Yeah. Sometimes
I download pirated music onto my work
computer. Who hasn't? Good.
Good. What else? No, I'd like to hear
more about that. I once reported
Oscar to the INS.
Turns out he's clean, but I'm glad
I did it. Ryan.
Oh, but you mean other than embezzling?
Fraud, Jim.
Fraud. Sure. Last
year, you guys were writing me really hard for the website,
and I just peeled out my Z3, and I
knocked the mirror off somebody's car.
I never said a thing. Wait.
What?