All right, everybody, this is your last meal, so eat up.
From this point forward, you will not use the bathroom. We need to keep our starting weights high so we can lose more.
My perfect last meal? Easy. Souffle. Yummy. The guard brings it to me and I scarf it down.
Then I spit out a razor blade. Looks like my cousin on the outside came through.
I knock out the guard, pull his hair back, quickly slice his face off and pull it over my own.
I head out past the other guards. See you later, guys. I'm going out for a break.
And I waltz on out of death row, determined to find the man who framed me.
Major Plate. Oh, thank you, Dwight, my loyal sidekick.
Have you met my sidekick? Oh, I didn't...
Oh, very good, very good. I asked for that. Have you met Mr. Titty Twister?
There he is. Yo! God! What is wrong with you? I'm holding food. I'm sorry.
Kevin, you're putting your spaghetti noodles on your bread.
Yeah. Enough carbohydrates for you.
Wow, Kevin, carbohydrates. Very cool.
Jim.
Do you know what I would like to do right now? What's that?
I would like to take those grapes and I would like to go over there and feed them to Holly.
Just start popping them in her mouth. Surprise her.
Grapes are very sexy food. Or bananas.
Whoa. You know what? No sexy. Just friends. Remember what we were talking about? Just like me and Pam?
Friends first. Take it slow. Okay.
Because friends don't go running around popping grapes in each other's mouths. Thank you.
Ladies and gentlemen, Chili Dog!
Angela, could you go to the kitchen and get more mustard? Today?
This summer, corporate is sponsoring a little weight loss contest between the branches.
Whichever branch loses the most weight gets three extra vacation days.
What should we do with all these leftovers? I'm taking the dumplings for my wife.
No, no, no. This is your last meal. There will be no leftovers.
I can bring these to my shelter. I'm taking my dumplings.
There. Take those home to your wife.
Michael, it's time.
My dream vacation? I sleep in, putter around the farm, go fishing for a few hours, take a long run in the forest, check the traps.
Then the sun comes up and I head into work, which is empty because everyone else is out of town on vacation.
Hit the scales, everybody. Right on that black platform. This way. Step it up.
Don't go breaking my scale.
I'm excited to lose weight for the wedding because I really want to have washboard abs the first time Angela sees me naked.
Oof. Squeeze me.
No, I will ex-squeeze you.
Okay, everybody, get used to this because we are going to be standing here briefly every Monday for the next seven Mondays.
Wait a minute.