It's Brittany, bitch.
And I am back in the form of a new company, the Michael Scott Paper Company.
Okay.
Not gonna make this one.
Just admit, you're excited.
I am happy that I don't have to answer phones anymore, but it's not like I'm going into
space or something.
That's true.
I'm a saleswoman.
Woohoo!
I'm really excited.
I knew it.
Love the hair.
Morning, Michael.
Hello.
They took away my parking space, but they can't take away my pride.
I'm embarking on a new adventure.
There was a fork in the road and I took the road less traveled.
Never traveled.
Not even a road, really.
More of a path.
With a sign that says, those who pass shall die.
And a skull and crossbones.
The other road was kind of like Putnam Road.
That's a really boring road in Scranton.
Eighteen months ago, I was the youngest vice president in Dunder Mifflin history.
Last week, I was disinfecting shoes.
Today, I'm starting a new company that will either make me rich or leave me broke.
But no matter what happens, I'll always be the same guy inside.
The youngest vice president in Dunder Mifflin history.
The name says it all.
Michael?
Who?
Michael Scott.
Oh, yes.
I know him.
What does he sell?
Paper.
Does he sell it by himself?
No, he has company.
Is he incorporated?
I don't have a sweet number.
I would like to invite you all to come along with me on a journey.
Welcome to the Michael Scott Paper Company.
Once in a generation, something happens that changes everything.
Is that the old copier from Dunder Mifflin?
Yes.
That...
No, Ryan, you're sitting over here at the executive conference table, which is very sweet.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, that's way cooler than the desk.
I'm glad you think so.
Good attitude.
He's just trying to trick you.
So this is it?
Yes, this is it.
Once we get up and running, we have an IPO.
We will look to expand into a bigger space.
Once in a generation, something happens that defines that generation.
This is that defining moment.
I look around this room, and the faces that I see are faces of friends.
They are faces of coworkers.
They are faces of my brethren in arms.
Is there only one computer?
Yes, yes, yes.
Okay, let's just...
Watch it with us.
Okay, I know.
Sorry.
What these people don't understand is that it's not about the size of the office.
It is about the size of the brains of the people in that office.
Small can be awesome, like Apple.
Okay, Apple is a company with 35,000 employees spread across a six-building campus.
I believe that you are thinking about PC.
Apple is the Justin Long guy.
You are PC.
I am Apple.
I am a dude, and you are a dork.
So, I thought we could take the customers and...
And we could...
You realize you are not actually talking to me, right?
And...
Hey, Kelly.
Yes, Charles, you wanted me.
Oh, no, I meant that, Kelly.
The new receptionist is also named Kelly.
So, Kelly Kapoor has decided to hover around my desk so that she can run into Charles' office every time he calls for Kelly.
She thinks that if she says, you wanted me, enough, he will in fact want her.
It's not the worst plan she's ever had.
Oh, and Kelly?
Yes, Charles.
Yes, you wanted me.
Okay, I'm going to call you Kapoor, okay, and you, Hammond.
If we're changing names, can I be Erin?
That's my middle name.
Erin, okay, that's very pretty.
Well, you know what my middle name is?
Rajinigandha, and I hate it.
I hate it!
I thought Rajinigandha was a boy's name.
We are in the heart of it, and the surge of water carries our business out to the sea.
What should we do now?
We wait and hope that people show up to the pancake luncheon.
I don't know, I think I have done absolutely everything you can do to prepare for the day.
I've updated our contacts, I have gotten quotes from suppliers, I have sent out an e-vite for our big grand opening pancake luncheon.
Six yeses, one maybe, only 11 nos, and 788 not yet replied.
Of that group, 782 have viewed it.
Altoid, anybody?
I think I'll check the e-vite for the first annual Dunder Mifflin...
Oh, wow, Michael Scott Paper Company pancake luncheon, I am such a blonde.
Oh, sorry Ryan, no offense.
It is hurtful, actually.
Retracted, alright, thankfully I have enough batter for a thousand pancakes, or three thousand silver dollar pancakes.
Can I check my email?
Oh, you don't have any new ones, except one from Jim.
You read my email?
You forgot to log out, what do you want me to do?
I am going to need 800 of these on a nice bright paper.
It is a coupon for unparalleled customer service.
I make that one copy, and I become the girl who makes copies.
And by the end of the day I am receptionist again.
And the worst part is, I like making copies.
The paper comes out all warm and stuff, and it is cold in there, because it is technically a closet.
What do you think?
Let me check.
Oh, nope, clearly a hunter.
Who knows how to throw an outfit together.
Thank you.
Yes, I am taking Andy hunting after work.
Not long ago we were sexual competitors.
I used to hate him, hate him, hate him, hate him.
I studied him to figure out why I hated him so much.
But that blossomed into a very real friendship, as these things often do.
Dwight and Andy? Friends.
I mean, what do those two possibly have in common?
And you don't want to do any color or...
Right, of course not.
Yeah, exactly.
And you wanted three hole punch or no?
Can you... I am going to give you a call back.
Something just came up in the office.
Thanks so much.
Bye.
You guys having fun?
Yeah.
Anyway, you could do the play fight somewhere else maybe?
You would totally be dead by now.
Come on, you couldn't survive that.
That's not realistic.
All your organs were just vaporized.
You were dying.
I had to put a grenade in your mouth.
Thank you. Nice.
Well done, sir.
Hey, everybody, keep it down. Jim's taking a nap.
Keep it down.
Let me tell you something. When Angela and I split, ha ha ha, oh, I went through it. Big time.
Lost my hindrance.
I was just trying to get a little bit of a break.
I went through it. Big time.
Lost my high notes.
Top of my range was like...
Then it took some time.
I got my heel on.
I got some perspective on.
And I found a new friend in the most unlikely of places.
The enemy bin.
And now...
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah.