Did you know that in Morocco it is common to exchange a small gift when meeting somebody for the first time?
In Japan you must always commit suicide to avoid embarrassment.
In Italy you must always wash your hands after going to the bathroom.
This is considered to be polite.
Why are you telling us this?
I am jetting off on an international business trip.
Where are you going?
To Canada.
Where is it?
Canada.
Okay.
My boss is sending me abroad to do a presentation to an international client.
And I have always been intrigued by all things international.
The women, the pancakes, the man of mystery.
In England they say hi.
In China they say hi-ya.
In France the women are sexy.
In Latin America the women are spicy.
In Germany the women are robust and huge.
Where are you getting your information?
From the information superhighway and from movies.
Gung Ho, European Vacation, Notting Hill, Under the Tuscan Sky.
Michael, where in Canada do you need to know all this?
Good question.
I will be flying from the Scranton International Airport to the Winnipeg International Airport.
Where people from all over the world will see me not just as Michael Scott business man but as Michael Scott ambassador.
Then you should probably know that in Canada it is a sign of respect to offer a bottle of Vermont maple syrup.
Really?
Okay.
Wallace did a terrible thing to Michael.
He transferred Holly to another branch, destroyed their relationship, and then to make it all better he chooses Michael to go on a business trip.
Classic abusive parent.
Here Michael, take this drug to numb the pain that I inflicted on you when I was high.
And the drug in all this?
Status.
Meredith, I would like you to pretend that you are from Abu Dhabi.
Hello.
I am ashamed at your naked face.
I must cover it with my jacket.
You are now sexy in your culture.
T minus 6.5 days.
One more week.
Pam comes back from New York next week and everyone here has just been so excited for me and involved and intrusive and weird.
Do you have your passport?
I have my passport.
Got your per diem?
I have my per diem.
I already know what I am going to spend this on.
I am going to buy a sweater.
Michael, that is for your food.
Well, I will just use different money for that.
I was happy to send Michael on this trip.
He has been feeling pretty down since we had to transfer Holly up to New Hampshire.
But this little perk really seemed to turn him around.
And it is pretty tough to find somebody who wants to go up to Winnipeg mid-November.
And business class air, like a five-star hotel in the sky, nothing but the best, actually better than a five-star hotel.
You get a big cushy seat and you sit in a row of people and to eat whatever the mind can imagine.
I think I am going to have a filet with mushroom sauce.
Well, I am just glad you are happy because you know I felt bad.
Well, that is all in the past.
And in terms of nightlife, when you get there, just ask the concierge.
They have one of those?
Let's do this.
Wait, why do you need three suitcases?
Two are empty for souvenirs.
You have your money belt?
I do. It is right here.
Oh, no, no, no, no. You want to wear that puppy right up on the breastbone like a bra.
No, I do not want to wear a bra.