Hey, sport.
I heard someone got engaged, you dog.
Ow!
God!
Oh, nothing can hurt you now.
You're a man in love.
I was there, and that dude was not engaged.
I'm not a big believer in therapy, but I'll go into my own pocket to cover his copay.
Come on.
How did you propose?
Spill it.
Were you wasted?
How did I propose?
Well, I drove her up to Nashua, and I had the ring, big 10-carat diamond, beautiful,
and I got down on my hands and knees, and a shooting star crossed overhead, and it just
lit up the diamond like a shooting star, and we were in a restaurant.
And I put the diamond into a cheeseburger.
Oh.
And she took a bite, started to choke.
So what do I do?
I do CPR training, go around, start doing Heimlich.
Perfect.
The ring, 10-carat diamond, pops out of her mouth, hits her shrimp cocktail right onto
her finger.
Million to one shot.
All of the Greek people in the restaurant start screaming, whoop-ah!
Which means congratulations.
Oh, man.
Big idea.
Double wedding.
Me, Angela, you, Holly.
No, we would never do that.
And if we did, it would be with Jim and Pam.
Yeah, we'd never do that.
Yeah, so there you go.
Michael, I got my bridesmaids dress.
Oh, wow, so quickly.
Yeah, and you said I could get it in any color I wanted, so I picked white.
Oh, Michael, did you tell your mom yet?
Nope, nope, not yet.
You wouldn't tell your mom?
What?
You love your mom.
I do.
Call your mom, Michael.
I'll call her later.
I'll call her and tell her.
Call her.
All right, I will call her.
Rico.
Speaking of food.
Not spoon.
Thanks.
Hello?
Mom, I'm getting married.
No, you're not.
Why do you always do that?
Whenever I'm getting married, you don't believe me.
Are you getting married?
No.
Are you?
I'm not.
I'm not getting married.
No.
Psyche.
So I've returned from my wedding.
You're going to the wedding?
No, I'm not.
I'm going to the wedding.
I'm not going to the wedding.
So I returned my bridesmaid dress and it was on sale, so I'm out $100.
And I'm out of fiancee.
Are those the customer surveys?
Yeah.
This is all of them.
Jim, Dwight, Phyllis, Stanley, Andy.
Oh, it's the receipt to my bridesmaid dress.
What's that doing there?
I'll take care of that for you.
Thanks.
Kelly Kapoor.
Kelly Kapoor is our dusky, exotic customer service rep.
And once a year, she will contact our clients and find out how happy they are with our salespeople.
Sort of a Kapoor's List.
Schendler's List parody.
That's not appropriate.
Those reports affect our bonuses, which is kind of great for me because you wouldn't know from looking at her, but Pam's a gold digger.
Hey, New York ain't free.
Get back to work.
Oh.
It's the world's tiniest Bluetooth.
I found it in a Japanese gadget store in the village.
I got one for Jim, too.
Jim, say something.
Testing, testing.
Hello, everybody.
We wanted to stay on the phone all day, but the company has a policy against eight-hour personal calls, so we're not telling anyone.
Pam, what do you want on your coffee?
Sprinkle of cinnamon.
I should go.
Alrighty, Dwight E., let's see how you did.
Bring it on.
No.
Sorry.
Wow.
What does it say?
Dwight, your feedback is horrible.
That's impossible.
A number of your clients found your personal style abrasive and distasteful.
I somewhat agree.
No, no, no, no, no.
Wait, is this a joke?
I'm getting that queasy feeling that sometimes accompanies jokes.
Do I look like I am joking?
No, but that's sometimes part of it.
Why are you joking?
You'd be laughing.
Do you look like you are laughing?
Impossible to say.
I can't see myself.
You're not.
You, Tommy Tuna, did you get your scores yet?
Nope.
I got mine.
They were really good.
I miss them.
You must be really proud.
Yeah, pretty siked.
Whoa.
That's my mug.
Oh, sorry.
It was just, it was right here.
Right.
Well, it's mine, so if you could pour it out and get another one.
Okay.
Or maybe I could finish the copy that's in here and you could use, oh, Snoopy.
He's funny.
Don't give him Snoopy.
That's mine.
That is a great mug.
But it's not my mug.
That is my mug, so give it back.
How can you even be sure?
Why is my face on it?
Make the face?
No, that's it.
Dude, that is my face.
What was that?
Wow.
That was Dwight.
He seems upset about something.
Describe him exactly.
What color mustard is his shirt?
Yellow or Dijon?
It is a little spicy brown, actually.
What are you mumbling about?
How was your meeting with Michael?
None of your business.
Was it your scores?
These can't be my scores, Jim.
For your information, I'm being sabotaged.
Of course.
And I'm going to find that person and punish them.
Absolutely.
Or you could just be nice to your customers.
You're an idiot.
There's the charm.
Jimbo, let's do this thing.
That is me.
Wish me luck.
No way.
Good luck.
Thanks.
I didn't say anything.
I love you.
I love you, too.
What do you think I'm saying to you?
I'm not talking to you.
I've caught Jim talking to himself several times today.
What a loser.
Get a friend, loser.
Yeah, I'm looking at it right now.
It's really gorgeous.
You guys do great work.
I found the best tentist on the East Coast.
He personally tinted Giuliani's first and third weddings.
And I got him.
I got him.
Would you be able to do the same design but with walls of gray?
And a top that's gray, too?
Fabulous.
Ask how he's doing since the breakup.
So, how are you holding up?
I'm pretty much devastated.
Ask if there's anything you can do.
Yeah, whatever you should do.
Take a vacation.
Maybe go to Sandals Jamaica or the other Sandals Jamaica.
I just don't want to go by myself.
Tell him you'd like to go with him.
Ah, we should take a look at those surveys.
Why are surveys important?
Okay, hypothetical.
A man wants to buy 500 reams of carrots.
And so he's like, what do I do?
Where do I go?
Do I go to the insensitive carrot supplier, the insensitive carrot salesman,
or do I go to the nice carrot salesman
who will maybe charge a few cents more per ream of carrot
but guarantee next day delivery on your carrots?
Most companies need their carrots the next day.
Now, substitute paper for carrots.
And that is why surveys are important.
Oh, come on.
What?
You, too?
Did my scores drop a little?
Jim, they are our poopie.
Jim?
Are we even sure that's my file?
No.
Yes, I am sure.
Jim, it...
Well, there's got to be an explanation.
I agree.
Yeah.
So let's see if we can find out from reading.
Jim Halpert, is smudge and arrogant.
I think he means smug.
Arrogance.
Michael, I'm just trying to...
And there's our smudgeness.
I need a decent bonus because I'm actually in the process of buying my parents' house
so that they can retire.
And if history tells us anything, it's that you can't go wrong buying a house you can't afford.
Pam doesn't know about the house, so it's a fun surprise.
Pam, sorry about that.
Lost you for a second.
So, as it turns out, I may not have done so hot on my customer reviews this year.
Maybe it's because you spent the whole year flirting with the receptionist.
A little bit.
Worth it.
Great marks, fellas.
Hey, I did good too.
I knew it.
Stop!
Don't leave me hanging.
What do I do with my bonus check?
Simple.
Purchase paper from myself.
Boosts my sales, which boosts my bonus.
Last year, I bought even more paper to make this year's bonus even bigger.
Eventually, I'll get a bonus so big I can retire on it.
And I'll use the paper to write my memoirs.
I taught Jim and Dwight everything I know about sales.
But there are certain things that cannot be taught.
And it is these things that I now must teach them.
Attention, all problem salespersons.
Jim Halpert.
Dwight Schrute.
Intensive one-on-one retraining will begin after lunch.
That is all.
I am no longer the worst salesman in the office.
Yes!
Ow!
Damn it!
Dwight and I are both writing letters to our clients.
I'm just sending a quick note to say how much I appreciate their business.
And he is writing notarized letters to inform them that lying on customer reviews is a prosecutable form of fraud and defamation.
Just different styles.
My job is to manipulate the customer into buying paper.
In return, they give me money.
I am the predator and they are the prey.
Would a mouse give a positive review to a hawk?
Should the hawk even care?
Excuse me, I've got work to do.
Here's what's going to happen.
I am going to have to fix you.
Manage you to, on a more personal scale, a more micro form of management.
Jim, what is that called?
Micro-Gymn?
Boom! Yes!
Now Jim is going to be the client.
Dwight, you are going to have to sell to him without being aggressive, hostile or difficult.
Let's go.
All right, fine.
Hello?
Hello, this is Dwight Schrute from the Dunder Mifflin Paper Company.
Well, that's great because I need paper.
Excellent, then you are in luck because we are having a limited time offer only on everything.
Wow, this is my lucky day.
Ask him his name.
What is your name, sir?
I am Bill Butlerger.
Really, that's a good name.
Really, that's your real name?
How dare you?
My family built this country, by the way.
Be respectful, Dwight, please.
Yes, Michael.
Could you hold on one second? That's my other line.
What? No, but I...
Hello?
Yeah.
No, I'm just on the phone with this stupid salesman.
He's so dumb.
Probably just going to keep him on the line forever and not buy anything.
Okay.
It's up to you to change his mind.
Sorry, that was a family emergency.
Oh, no, what's wrong? You know what? That's private.
Boundaries, Dwight, come on.
I'm sorry, Mr. Butlerger. As I was saying, we are having a limited...
We're having a limited...
Speak up a little bit louder. I'm hard of hearing.
He's an old man.
Okay, as I was saying, right now we are having...
Yeah, you gotta talk louder.
Okay, our prices have never been lower.
Son, you have to talk louder.
Never been lower.
Louder, son!
Butlerger, our prices have never been lower!
Stop it, stop it.
Pete!
That is totally inappropriate.
You never yell at the client.
Now, you listen to me, sir.
Here we go.
The three words I would describe you as is aggressive, hostile, and definitely difficult.
Please, Mr. Butlerger.
I'm irate right now.
Give me the phone.
Please give me another chance.
Mr. Butlerger.
Give me the phone.
I have to put you on with my boss.
Well, I should hope so. Who is this?
Hello, this is Michael Scott, regional manager.
Well, this is William M. Butlerger.
Hello, Mr. Butlerger. How may we help you?
Michael, I like the sound of your voice.
You know what I'm going to do?
I'm going to buy one million dollars worth of paper products today.
See how it's done?
Thank you very much, sir. I don't think you'll regret it.
You know what I did?
You are the master.
There is one condition, Michael.
Yes?
You have to fire the salesman that treated me so terribly.
Don't do it, Michael.
It's a million dollar sale.
So, it's called the Shangri-La tent.
It's two stories, heated, and it has a bridal suite for my bridal suite.
Which is really simple, really tasteful.
I don't want to be married in a tent like a hobo.
Hobos live in trains.
Nana Mimi can't be in canvas that long.
Well, Nana Mimi...
Okay, look.
This tent is awesome.
And it's in high demand, so I really think we should put a deposit down now.
Okay, fine.
You can have your tent, but only if it's in a field.
A hand-plowed field.
Done. And done-er.
There has to be a barn.
That's old enough that you can see the stars through the roof slats when you lay on your back.
And antique tools to look at when you roll over.
Do you have a specific place in mind?
No. But any...