What is this thing you just sent me?
Oh, it's really cool. It's a picture of the most relaxing meadow you've ever seen.
Idiot. I know what this is. It's supposed to lull me into a sense of calm and then a ghoul pops up and scares me.
Why would I do that? Dwight, of all people I know, that you're unscarrable.
Damn right I am.
Oh, hello relaxing meadow. I'm so relaxed and calm looking at you right now.
Oh no, scary ghoul just popped up. I'm so scared, I'm so scared.
Really? Is this the best you could... Jim?
How are you?
Okay.
Mm-hmm. That is the best I can do.
Here are our final actual costs for this year. Okay. As you can see we did pretty well.
Yes, yes I can see that we did indeed. Why don't you explain this to me like I am an eight-year-old?
All right, well this is the overall budget for this fiscal year along the x-axis. Yes. There's the x-axis.
You can see clearly on this page that we have a surplus of $4,300. Okay.
We have to spend that by the end of the day or it will be deducted from next year's budget.
Why don't you explain this to me like I'm five?
Your mommy and daddy give you $10 to open up a lemonade stand. So you go out and you buy cups and you buy lemons and you buy sugar.
And now you find out that it only costs you $9. Oh. So you have an extra dollar. Yeah.
So you can give that dollar back to mommy and daddy. But guess what? Next summer. I'll be six.
And you ask them for money they're gonna give you $9. Because that's what they think it cost everyone to stand.
So what you want to do is spend that dollar on something now so that your parents think that it costs $10 to run the lemonade stand.
So the dollar is a surplus. This is a surplus. We have to spend that $4,300 by the end of the day or it'll be deducted from next year's budget.
We should spend this money on a new copier which we desperately need. Okay.
Break it down in terms of... Okay. I think I'm getting you.
Guess what everybody? Christmas has come early this year. Oscar, very smartly, has discovered an extra $4,300 in the budget. Thank you Oscar.
And I have decided with that money I am going to buy a new... Drum roll please. Can anybody guess? New chairs? No. A new copier.
All right. Unless everybody can agree on something better? No, no. Please, please do not do this. Yes. Michael, new chairs. These chairs are terrible. We were supposed to get new ones last year.
So we all agree to get new chairs then. Good? Good. Yeah. He said good. I'm good.
Listen, we are a paper company. How can we take pride in our jobs if we have to put our fine paper in this wretched machine? Oscar, no. This is not the time for one of your principled stamps. Pam, you make more copies than anyone.
Exactly. That should tell you how terrible the chairs are. Okay. Okay. Good suggestions. All good suggestions. Let's just decide and agree upon one. I'm with Pam. Cheers.
All right. So teams for me. We should really have the offices air quality tested. We have radon coming from below. We have asbestos in the ceilings. These are silent killers. You are the silent killer. Go back to the annex. You'll see.
Michael? Yes. I've talked to Meredith, Stanley and Jim about the chairs. I know they're with me on this. Actually, I'm going to go with a copier. What? Jim?
Ever since Pam and I started dating, I just feel weird asking her to make copies for me. So I make my own copies. And that copier sucks. Let me tell you. But you know what? Pam and I don't have to agree on everything.
Jim, good for you standing up to Pam like that. The ball's on you, man. So, Michael, what do you think? Why me? You have to make the decision.
Wow. Okay. Well, I swallowed all your ideas. I'm going to digest them and see what comes out the other end.
Dwight, I'm a little concerned about some of these directions to Shrew Farms. Yeah, do tell. I mean like 156 paces from the light red mailbox make a left. Walk until you hear the beehive.
How could it be more clear? I think Andy makes an excellent point. But my biggest concern is that there's only one bathroom. We'll dig a trench. As long as it's downhill from the well, we should be fine. Nana, Mimi cannot squat over some trench. We're going to put out stumps. Come on.
Let's three-way this little issue and come to a solution by the time we get to Shrew Farms. How's that for a plan? We're getting married at Shrew Farms no matter what. I have looked at 12 venues. I have lost eight deposits and I've seen Angela naked zero times. I am not losing another deposit.
I thought you were going to put a muzzle on that singing idiot. He's not a bad singer. He's pretty talented, I guess. Andy went to Cornell. Yeah, well, I provide America with two of its most beloved staples, beets and paper. His family is well connected in pockets of Connecticut. And his ancestors came over on the Mayflower. Oh, big whoop. Half my family came over on a U-boat. I would have destroyed the Mayflower.
Listen to you. Destroy the Mayflower? Sorry. I can't believe I said that. Angela. What I'm planning is like, imagine you're harvesting beets and all they do is complain. Oh, you're pulling us out of the ground too soon. I don't like the color hoe you're using. Just shut up and be delicious.
I don't think you read any of my requirements. Okay. As far as the centerpieces, I want there to be a fish bowl with a goldfish in it. Here's an idea. Why don't we put piranhas in the bowls with the goldfish? Massacre. No. The water turns red and plus the guests get to see a show. No, no. I don't want to see any blood at my wedding. I'm going to have to change the cake then. Oh, you guys. This is going to be so awesome.
Hey. Hey. So, I've been thinking about this whole chair copier thing. I really think you should reconsider. Oh, Pam. I really hate that copier. Yeah, I know. Yeah. But I really think you should reconsider. Beezley, are you threatening me? Jim. Jim, Jim, Jim. I'm not threatening you.
I love you. But you should know you're on very dangerous ground. All right. Okay. This is where you'll have your receiving line. Of course, we'll clear out all the livestock and hay and such. What's that smell? You're going to need to be more specific. Manure. Get rid of it.
Manure covers up the smell of the slaughterhouse. Do you have to slaughter on our wedding day? You want to eat, don't you? Honey, say something. Uh, Dwight, if we pay extra, can you slaughter the entrees the day before? I'll consider it. See? That's how you do it. Making progress here. Darn. There's a hose out back. Okay.
No, I know nothing about wedding planning. I tried to do some research once. Moe's and I rented a movie about a Latino wedding planner with an enormous can. The movie was not so good, but McConaughey was great. As usual. Hey.
There's no way that gay Mike and Broccoli Rob are having a better wedding than me. Moe's.
Did you see that?
This is the chair that was here when I was hired. It was crappy then, and it's even worse now. To give myself a break, sometimes I go outside and sit on the ground. Remember you were going to get a new chair and you were going to give your old chair to me. Remember that? Yes.
Well, that never happens. Michael? I don't know. I haven't decided yet. I'm just going to grab some lunch. Want to come with? Really? Absolutely. Yeah, that would be amazing. Whoa, you guys going to lunch? Yes. Mind if I join? Oh, God. All right. Yeah. Best lunch ever. Woo. Let's do it. All right. Cool. Where are we going? I have no idea. So I guess that's how they're going to play this. It is on.