Oh my god, I can't believe it. I just won an art contest
I still don't understand why you wanted me to say that shut up
I got her
Not cold white not cool
Ha ha ha
Oh
No, I still have the lease on the Michael Scott paper company
So occasionally I will sneak down here for a little coffee and dancing. I
Actually dance all the time
Tiptoeing around corporate. It is a ballet when I am breaking all the rules. I'm
breakdancing and
Expresso
Guys, I'm scared
I'm really scared. I think I'm growing into a giant because look at this normal-sized coffee cup
Looks so tiny in my giant hand now
Anybody want to go to lunch with me later on I do okay. How about a woman Pam? Oh, I can't do lunch
I was just sending you an email Jim and I need to leave early today to meet with our contractor. Oh, really?
Okay, just sent it. What about the rest of you?
Under Mifflin there is a very strict no lunch with the boss policy and I don't know who instituted it
I think it started right after my predecessor stepped down
But at the Michael Scott paper company, I really enjoyed having lunch with Pam and Ryan every day
So rules be damned. I want to have lunch with these people who else who else Ryan?
I don't do lunch
I'm doing five small meals a day now now that I'm back to doing the job of a temp again
I find that food is one thing I can control. Okay anyone anyone at all
Accounting I am accounting on you to go to lunch with me. No, I don't want to stay late to have a two-hour lunch
Michael we have a lot of work to do what?
Work. Oh
What happened you people we're just office drones we are office drones all we do is work
His work if you don't take out his battery he just keeps going all day. Oh, no your battery fell out. I
Was just learning to love
Hi guys, how you doing Aaron?
How many times do I have to tell you it is not necessary for you to ask us how we are doing every time you interact
With us, right? I'm sorry
Now
How can I help you did somebody here leave a map in the printer to Youngstown, Ohio
Attention office who here is planning a trip to Youngstown, Ohio
I will take your silence to mean that you're all hiding something. Oh, no, I love Ohio
Next time you're there say hi to my cousin Amel and then kick him in the groin area because he's a cheat and a bull hog
I
Be still married to Clarissa kick her in the groin area too because she's a heartbreaking tart and a ball hog
This location is the superior court. So someone's going to a court big deal
It is a big deal because there's only a handful of reasons why someone would ever go to a courthouse in Ohio and not be charged
With a crime claim an inheritance from a deceased relative to obtain a learner's permit at age 14 and a half instead of 15
Erin super certificate sure
There are other reasons to go to Ohio we're getting married today
So it turns out it's the closest place to get a marriage license without a three-day waiting period tell them how it happened
Okay, so we're going through all the wedding plans and boy it is complicated
Very expensive because you say you want a small wedding and that's great. But then you have to you can't leave anyone out
No one. Okay, just get to the good part, right?
So this morning we are having breakfast together and I just looked up for my cereal and I said
You know what I want to do today. I
Want to marry you I
Had just woken up. I didn't look cute. That's how I knew he meant it
I like to swim
Here
Watch broken
Guys I believe that I have figured out what is up your butts
There's no reason to be scared. The bad man is gone. Charles is gone
Charles really did a number on these guys. They are way too focused on work when I was in charge
this place
Was like Dave and Buster's people just hanging out having fun eating naps. I
Don't know. It's like
They've died or something
Daddy's here and daddy is gonna take care of you. Please don't refer to yourself as our daddy. I am your big daddy and
I am gonna kiss the boo-boo. We know Andy is afraid
Andy the frayed. Yeah, are you all afraid? No daddy's here for you my widow angels
Okay, I
Think that I have figured a way to get you guys out of your funk
What funk is the problem and the solution that makes sense?
I have taken my downstairs office and I have turned it into a place to hang out a place where
Unattractive and attractive people can get together to meet to greet to see the ones that you love
To love the ones that you see our punishment for not wanting to have lunch with you
Why don't you get over lunch Oscar? Everybody else is passing all work and no play makes Michael a dull boy
This is like a haunted coffee house. No Dwight is confusing you that it's it's more of a disco. It's like a haunted disco
With coffee but without the haunting it's a combo dance house coffee bar. It is a
Daytime disco on the ground floor of an industrial office building. It's a cafe disco. Exactly like a disco cafe
What no no not even close. I can't force you to go down, but I can entice you
I'm gonna be down there. Erin will be down there from time to time and all you can eat espresso
Oh, hi Kevin
Did you have bacon for breakfast no, oh
Cuz you smell like bacon I
Didn't think I did
How's everything going tight? I'm going down the hall to this office to see Michael. There's free espressos. I
I
Would invite you but I remember that you just want to be friends
We can still are you sure that you didn't eat bacon? Yes
Whatever it is I like it
Bye
Yes, I had some bacon this morning. I just didn't think it was anyone's business. I love the smell of bacon on a woman
Oh
Well Kevin I guess it is just me and you yeah holding down the fort yeah
This place is great. Thank you. Oh my god, Kevin. I am still on hold
You were supposed to get the answer from Michael and come back up. This is a no-work zone. Please respect the lay
Yeah, respect the lay
Come
Kevin stay Kevin come Kevin stay Kevin come stay stay
Come on right cookie Kevin cookie
There is no cookie Kevin
Is there a cookie? Mm-hmm