Hi.
Good morning.
Can I help you?
Yes.
I'm from Techstar.
I've got a new phone system for you.
I was wondering if I could talk to Michael Scott.
I'm sorry.
He's not in right now.
Really?
He's never around when I come by.
Shoot.
They have new phone systems now that can ring directly to a salesman or someone presses
star and they go to accounting.
Basically, 95% of my job.
But I'd like to see a machine that puts in a number of calls.
I'm not sure if I can get a call.
Michael Scott, manager.
Hi, how are you?
Oh, hi.
Nice to meet you.
Great.
Look at that.
I can assure you we don't need a new system, though.
Happy with ours.
Hello.
May I help you?
Jimbo.
Jim.
Hey.
Hey...
Okay.
I'm uh, let's be good.
Hey...
What was that?
That was funny.
Let's go do it to somebody else.
Hey...
Oh, look at that.
Cupid's and Hart's really shoving their faces in it this year.
You doing okay, bud?
I miss Stacey.
Yeah, I hear you.
It's been four months since I was with Holly, and she was way hotter than Stacey.
So if you think you're hurting...
I can't even imagine.
This is our first and only Valentine's Day as fiancés.
You're only engaged once.
Well, present company excluded.
Really, Jim?
On Cupid's birthday?
Yeah.
She's fine.
So I received my first Valentine from a secret admirer.
Roses are red.
Violets are blue.
It's time for your dental cleaning and maybe a checkup, too.
Oh, wow, look at those.
How nice for you.
Up there, front and center, beautiful.
I think they would look better right here.
They're very pretty, and I wouldn't want them to fall.