I'm sorry he's not in yet.
Would you like his voicemail?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, okay.
12 miles an hour.
Eat that call, Lewis.
Angela made several 911 calls about cars going too fast in front of the building, so the
police put up a radar gun.
It's actually a
bit of a traffic hazard.
No, no, no, there was wind.
I was just jogging.
Dwight, there was wind.
I want to do a-
No, no, no, it's not your turn.
All right, 13 is the new number.
Oscar, go ahead.
I want another try.
Here we go.
Angela, you're in trouble.
I'm going to get him.
Oh, wow. 13. No, no, no. There was wind. I was just jogging. Dwight, there was wind.
I want to do. No, no, no. It's not your turn. All right. 13 is the new number. Oscar, go
ahead. I want another try. Here we go. 31. 31. There was the car. I was ahead of the
car. 31 is my new number. 31 is humanly impossible. Go Oscar. 31 is my number. That's impossible.
Beat it!
Today's a big day. My presence has been requested by Chief Financial Officer David Wallace.
He says that he wants to talk about big picture stuff.
And I'll be honest, I have little or no idea what that means. So, probably bad.
Quick announcement. New year, new candy.
Woo hoo!
Okay, be careful, Kevin. They're kind of spicy.
Hot tamales.
Yeah.
Uh oh.
So maybe just try one at first, and then if it's okay, have a couple more.
Excuse me, everyone. Can I have the floor, please?
Um, this is insanely awkward. It's kind of the elephant in the room, so I'll just...
No one is RSVP'd to our wedding yet, and the deadline was yesterday.
Wait, you still don't know...
No, no.
No?
Hmm?
Nothing.
You still don't know?
What are you doing?
How about we just...
Just have to talk to you first.
Andy, has he?
No, no one has RSVP'd, and I don't understand it. And now you're shutting me out. You're not even listening. And that's really considerate. Thank you.
No, what I'm saying...
No, no.
No, they're not. I know it.
Andy still doesn't know that Angela's having an affair with Dwight. And it's been 17 days.
I mean, eventually he'll figure it out. When their kids have giant heads and beet-stained teeth. But right now it's just...awkward.
How about you, Phyllis? We can count on you at the wedding, right?
It's hard for me to say at this time.
Stanley, how does it look, buddy?
You asked me every day.
Well, I'll stop asking when you answer.
I answer every day.
Leave me alone is not an answer. It doesn't help me with my guest count.
Jim Helper?
Hello, Dwight Schrute. How may I help you?
Your phone didn't even ring.
It's going to take me a very long time to answer that question.
Let me try that. So, you're...
Yes.
I'm sure we have that.
Yeah, it's really hard to be around Andy. I can't look him in the eyes anymore. So today, I'm just going to focus on his nose.
Can we count on your gracious presence at our nuptials?
Um...
Why don't we say yes for now?
Oh! Yes for now. Thank you. Is that so hard, people?
Tuna, you still need to get your tuxedo. Not going to mind me again.
Yes, sir.
Yes, I will.
How can he still not know?
We can't figure that out.
I can't take it anymore.
Wait. What? You can't take what?
I am telling Andy.
No, you can't do that. It shouldn't come from you.
Who should it come from, then?
Angela. Angela. Angela.
Are you still having intercourse with her?
What is wrong with you? She is engaged.
Did you ever have intercourse in this office?
Are you serious?
Where?
Where, Dwight?
Seems like you already know where.
Kevin, you screwed this form up again. The amount owed goes at the top.
Oh, I'm sorry. I didn't realize I was doing something wrong.
If I had, I would have admitted it and stopped right away.
That's enough.
Because I wouldn't want an innocent person who doesn't know anything about the form.
What?
That was good.
It's just that at the end you weren't saying something that could also apply to the form.
How about, I'm sorry I did such a horrid job filling out this form.
There you go.
That cannot be true.
You're going to charge me a fee to cut my own cake?
No, no, no. What I'm saying is I want to cut it myself.
Trade seats with me. No.
I've got a better angle on Pam. I can see everything.
Please stop.
I need a soup spoon.
Rule 17.
Don't turn your back on Banner.
Don't turn your back on Bears, men you have wronged, or the dominant turkey during mating season.
There are 40 rules all Shroot Boys must learn before the age of five.
Learn your rules. You better learn your rules.
If you don't, you'll be eaten in your sleep.
It's just so important for you to get your big story, isn't it?
To edit everything together to make it look like there's a villain.
Well there's not always a villain.
Sometimes there's just a hardworking petite woman trying to make a conscientious decision about the rest of her life.
Too boring? Did I lose you?
Here, is this what you want?
What is it?
You've got to tell Andy about us.
That is a terrible idea. One of your worst.
Get it over with, then we don't have to hide anymore.
You're expanding on your worst idea.
Do you love me or not?
I've already admitted that I do. Why do you keep making me repeat it?
Because you're engaged to Andy.
Can't we just focus on what we have right now?
Aren't you looking forward to our weekend away together?
I guess.
Come on. Visiting the Quaker Meeting House?
Tell me again about its construction.
You know.
Tell me.
Come on.
It's rectangular in frame.
And each beam is made from a 40 foot timber.
And fashioned from a single oak over 300 years ago.
The cedar shingled roof is over two stories high.
The chimney.
You get Andy to watch the cats.
Yeah, this shouldn't be a problem.
Hey.
What's the haps?
What do you think the haps is?
It's freezing cold.
That's not it.
That's not the haps. You gotta feel the haps.
You have to open your eyes and...
What do you think the haps is, Andy?
I was just making conversation.
Haps can be terrible.
Haps can be so bad sometimes you just have to...