At least once a year, I like to bring in some of my Kevin's famous chili
The trick is to under cook the onions
Everybody is going to get to know each other in the pot
I'm serious about this stuff. I'm up the night before pressing garlic and dicing whole tomatoes
I toast my own anchovy chilies
It's a recipe passed down from Malone's for generations
It's probably the thing I do best
Oh
Someone is returning
He started his own company and now he's back. Who could it be?
I'll give you a hint. He is a man a man
You have missed with all your heart a man who has ruined all other men for you
Who is it?
It's Michael Scott
Conference room five minutes
Well, I guess the first order of business is to welcome back me and Pam and Ryan
And
How about casual Friday again, huh reinstituting casual Friday?
Well look great. What I want to do right now is try something a little different
I'm gonna throw it out there starting with this meeting. I want you guys to run it. I want you to say whatever you want
Take it away your meeting
What are you doing if
There is something that you would like to say as a group then by all means you may say it to me right now
Okay
Yeah, people are dressed inappropriately take it up with Toby what I want you to do
Is I want you to look inward and I want you to reflect and I want you to say something different. Can you give us a hint?
When I needed salespeople for my new paper company everyone here turned their back on me
Am I going to ask them to beg for forgiveness? No
Am I going to ask for a big
crying
Apology no am I going to ask them to slit their wrists for me? No, I just want a tiny
microscopic version of that
Oscar what were you gonna say nothing?
You didn't say anything
Good to have you back
Thank you. All right about a million different ways to apologize. I'm not sure that was one of them
Previously on 24
Michael Scott leaves his loyal friends of Dunder Mifflin to start his own paper company
However, his sales team doesn't believe in him and against all odds
He goes off is a success that is bought out by Dunder Mifflin to only be reteamed
With the people who didn't believe in him
Next week on 24, what will you stop it stop it?
Pam and Ryan and I have been through a lot in the last six weeks. We've bonded in some amazing ways and
I when people say love triangle, I don't know why they think of it as such a bad thing
Do I still have a job here? Not important
Okay. All right. Yes. Yes to know you have a job
Frankly, you have a job because Ryan and Pam are starting with us as salesmen
Wait, what? How is that going to work?
It's going to work very smoothly because Pam and Ryan are bringing over a ton of clients from Michael Scott paper company
I mean the clients you stole from us. Yeah, aren't we giving those clients back? No, you lost those clients
I call foul. So okay, you were bought out
So the company then bought out all the stolen clients. Okay, Dwight. Let me explain something to you
I set the rules and you follow them blindly
Okay, and if you have a problem with that then you can talk to our complaint department it's a trash can
Don't fall in love with me kid
All right, you're ready to wait ready for what?
What's this a little gift
On
behalf of desk area clump number one
We welcome you to our little island love Jim and Dwight. Okay. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa
I had nothing to do with that. Okay, I missed the storage containers that used to occupy that spot
Thank you Dwight and you obscure my view of the shredder
Little island
us and
Dwight that island is completely implausible
You're a train conductor that's my job on the island
It's a King Kong. You're like the attraction to raise money. Oh my god. Will you shut up? You're making me vomit
Boscov's at the steam town mall. It sure looked good on the mannequin. Well, you have good taste. Thanks
I sure wish I had more time to talk to my clients though
What isn't it what you said to a bunch of my clients when you were stealing them that I didn't have enough time for
Oh, I am close your mouth. Sweetie. You look like a trout
The man is wearing sandals I don't need to see Oscar's toes at work gross
I mean he looks like you just got off the boat. Okay, you just not look at his feet
Excuse me. Oh
You're so educated aren't you Toby so trained to deal with a hysterical woman, I don't want to look at his feet
Well, I was in the seminary for a year and
Dropped out cuz I want to have sex with this girl Kathy followed her back to Scranton took the first job I could find in HR
Later she divorced me
So no, I wouldn't say I have a passion for HR
Thanks
Thanks Michael
Fresh hot ink
New file system
Trust me Stanley. You are gonna want to read this memo very carefully
I am NOT changing the way I do my father. No, no this goes for all of you. Believe me
You are going to want to heat
You