Hey, Michael?
Yeah?
Contractions are coming every 10 minutes.
Okay, just remember to keep breathing.
My cervix is ripening.
Okay, good.
Jan is about to have a baby with a sperm donor, and Michael is preparing for the birth of
a watermelon with Dwight.
Now, this baby will be related to Michael through... delusion.
Michael?
Yeah?
My watermelon!
What?
Michael?
Yeah?
My water's breaking!
Oh, okay, okay.
What do you do?
I get a call from Jan and I meet her at the hospital.
Right.
Highways or surface roads?
I take Quincy Abt to Gibson?
No, Gibson is covered in potholes.
Your car breaks down.
Adapt.
I checked the route.
There are no potholes.
Come on.
Get in here and have a baby.
It's a bad adapting to the circumstances.
Andy, would you like to have my baby?
Yes!
No.
Okay, no.
I'm cramping!
Come on, I'm cramping!
Here we go!
Do it!
Babies are one of my many areas of expertise.
Growing up, I performed my own circumcision.
Just keep pushing.
Hold me!
I'm right here.
Cradle my head!
I'm screaming, I'm screaming, I'm screaming!
Quiet.
Just push and breathe.
Numb me up.
I want anesthesia.
No, you can't have it.
It's too late.
No, I don't want natural.
No, you have to just push it out.
Okay!
Keep simulating.
Okay.
Do you have the Sharpie?
Keep simulating.
Yes, I do.
Okay.
When the baby emerges, mark it secretly in a kind of a mark that only you can recognize
and no baby snatcher could ever copy.
Okay.
Ready?
Yes.
Hello!
Here we go!
Butter!
God!
Wow!
What was on that?
Butter.
Newborns are slippery.
Nice touch.
Good.
Let's try that again.
This is going to be the happiest day of my life.
Hello, ladies.
How was my shower going?
Phyllis, did you get the live storks?
No.
Dammit, Phyllis!
I'm sorry.
Dammit, Phyllis.
It was hard enough to convince Jan to come.
Jan knows the sex, but she's not telling me.
She did say that I could pick out a boy name.
Her exact words were, knock yourself out.
Jan's not thinking very well.
She's at that point of her pregnancy that the baby's just sucking all the blood right
out of her brain.
So are we set for refreshments?
Per your instructions, we have the personalized M&Ms with the baby names.
This is your boy bowl with the name Chevy.
That was me.
And this is the girl bowl with M&Ms with the name Ass Turd.
That can't be right.
Michael wrote down Ass Turd.
She said it is the name of a Viking princess.
Ass Turd.
I know.
It is beautiful.
No.
Thank you.
Is this it?
I mean, is this two bowls of M&Ms and some balloons?
Who?
Who's in charge?
She is.
Yeah?
Why?
That's how we worked it out.
Really?
Internally.
You need to step it up.
I think you need to get the lead out.
Because if I'm not mistaken, we gave you your wedding shower here.
We all came into this room and gave you a golden shower.
Well, you know what?
Where's my golden shower, Phyllis?
It does not matter to me at all whether this baby is biologically mine.
I'm going to love it.
It's like when the dog nurses the tiger cub.
Have you seen that video?
It is, it's so bizarre and unnatural.
But it happens.
Hey, I'm collecting for the baby shower.
But Phyllis, it's not his baby.
I know, Kevin.
Why do we have to pay money to get a gift for his ex-girlfriend's unborn sperm bank
baby?
Look at it as if you're paying for the cake, not the baby.
She cake.
I do enjoy being the head of the party planning committee.
I'm no longer under Angela's heel and her little grape head is under mine.
Hey, hey.
What are you doing?
Don't talk to them.
Sorry.
Make the party.
Don't, make the party, please, Phyllis.
Pump it!
So you know Stacey, right?
Right, the one from England.
There's no one from England, Jim.
Katie studied in Ireland.
This is Stacey, the one who does the Murakami style collages.
Right, that style.
So Stacey and Eric get to Phoners GTEC half an hour early so they don't have to sit on
the slab.
Okay.
Anyway, Phoners TA Sarah Kaya comes in.
Wait, who's Sarah Kaya comes in?
No, Sarah Kaya comes in.
Don't interrupt.
I have like 30 seconds to finish this and get to DigiCrate.
Okay, okay.
So Sarah Kaya says to Eric, no way, you can't reserve seats.
And then Stacey gets all up in her face and Sarah Kaya picks up Stacey's meet-amp pad
and throws it at the lightbox.
No way!
Yes!
That's hilarious.
No, it was horrible.
Jim, she might get arrested.
Who, Stacey?
No, Stacey is a boy.
Frustrating.
Why can't you just be in art class with me?
Oh wait, I gotta go, class is starting.
Okay, I'll talk to you later.
That was a good story.
Who's Sarah Kaya?
I don't know.
Who's Sarah Kaya comes in?
Hugh!
I got the Nard puppy for ya.
What's going on here?
It's a baby game where you guess whose picture is whose.
Aww.
Check it out.
Who would have thought that this little baby would be marrying that little baby?
That's Phyllis.
Well, it is.
So I hope you two are very happy together, pervert.
Why does that make me a pervert?
Well, it does.
That's me.
That's not you.
Yes, it is.
That's mean.
Come on.
Ahoy, matey.
Ahoy.
So, how you doing?
Good.
Listen, Jan Levinson is coming in today and she is in the terminal stages of her pregnancy,
a child of which I have a vested interest.
Sounds kind of weird.
Anyway, she is incredibly fat and enormous right now, extremely unattractive.
And you are, on the other hand, one of the more attractive people in the office.
So while she's here, I am going to be acting kind of cold to you.
And I am doing this to pay respect to her bloated feelings.
Of course.
Yeah.
The personal relationships in this office are a little complicated.
But I'm fine with that.
You don't go into human resources if you want to judge people.
Only if you want to hire and fire them.
I do not like pregnant women in my workspace.
They're always complaining.
I have varicose veins too.
I have swollen ankles.
I'm constantly hungry.
Do you think my nipples don't get sore too?
Do you think I don't need to know the fastest way to the hospital?
Sorry Phil, I didn't have time to boil the nipples.
I think it's okay if it's for adults.
Relax, it's for me.
When you go to the hospital, you need a go bag.
In here is everything they tell you to bring in What to Expect.
1986 edition.
Well, it's a classic.
Do we have a pager?
Check.
Dimes for payphones.
Film for camera.
Yeah.
Nightgown.
Don't know why I have that.
And Walkman.
Good.
And I have filled in some of the gaps on your list.
A concussion grenade for crowd control.
Cipro.
A butane torch for sterilization.
Knife for circumcision.
And crank flashlight.
Jan.
Hi Jim.
What do we have here?
This is my baby.
Really?
Oh no.
Jan had the baby and Michael wasn't there to market.
So the baby could be anybody's.
Except Michael's.
So this is Astrid.
Astrid.
Oh, okay.
Why didn't you call me?
Well, you know, labor just kind of started very suddenly and the birth instructor thought
it wasn't a good idea for him either.
So I just.
He had no sense of humor and I proved him wrong in so many ways.
You don't have any idea what I've been through.
No, I don't.
I'm sorry.
I thought today at the baby shower would be a good time for the two of you to meet.
Can I hold her?
Yes.
Yes, you can.
You know, I think just leave her in the car seat.
Just.
Yeah.
Okay.
I love babies.
I think they are beautiful in all sorts of different ways.
I try to pick up and hold a baby every day if possible because it nourishes me.
It feeds my soul.
Babies are drawn to me and I think it's because they're so beautiful.
I think they're beautiful.
It feeds my soul.
Babies are drawn to me and I think it's because they see me as one of them.
But cooler and with my life put together a little bit.
If a baby were president, there would be no taxes.
There would be no war.
There would be no government and things could get terrible.
And actually probably it would be a better screenplay idea than a serious suggestion.
Ladies and gentlemen, it is my privilege and honor to present for the first time in her life and in the office Astrid Levinson.
Hi Astrid.
This is everybody.
Look, this is your family.
You're going to know them for the rest of your life.
Well, well, he may not be here.
Say hello.
Okay, here we go.
Lion King.
Michael, Michael, Michael, that's too high.
I'll take that.
Okay.
Come on.
Let's get our shower on.
Conference room.
Choppity chip chop.
Are you okay?
You seem kind of.
I'm fine, weirdo.
Such an HR weirdo.
Try not to suck all the air out of there when you walk in.
Oh, hey.
Wait for me.
It's going to be fun.
What's that smell?
Stanley?
No, baby powder.
Okay.
Do we have hats?
Phyllis?
No?
Okay.
Well, where am I going to sit?
Good.
If a baby's not crying and running my plane ride, then it's staring at me.
I don't know why babies need to stare at me.
Ready to play some games?
Let's do it.
Michael, the baby's already been born.
Yeah, it did.
So we had games planned, but the baby ruins all of them.
No, the baby doesn't ruin anything, Kevin, okay?
The baby multiplies the fun.
Let's just do what you were going to do.
Okay.
Who wants to guess when the baby will be born?
All right, how about we play the game where we guess how big the mother's belly is?
Oh.
Okay.
So how many squares of toilet paper go around the waist?
Does that mean there's no toilet paper in the bathroom?
Kevin, relax.
Okay, you know what?
I don't think we're going to get it.