Things are a little slow here, and there's only so much cold calling you can do in a
day. Turns out there's no limit to the number of cheese puffs you can throw at someone's
face. We're getting pretty good at it.
Who is that knocking on my taste buds? Why, it's Mr. Lemon. Nice to meet you. It's
good. But won't it feel weird cutting into a cross? Don't think of it as a cross in
the Judeo-Christian sense. Think of it more as a symbol of your lives crossing in marriage.
When I think of it like that, I do not think of the other connotations. Yes. I don't think
so, Andy. Sorry, man. Hard day. What's wrong with you? These sleeves are cutting off my
circulation. There's not a blood getting to my hands. I think you look nice. Doesn't Charles
know he's compromising my attack readiness? It's not a dress code. It's a death sentence.
Looking good. Okay, thank you. Straight jacket. Okay. When Michael was in charge, this place
was like the Roman Empire, in the Wild West, in war-torn Poland, and Poland. There was
just a lot going on. So what you were to work was the least of anybody's worries. And that
chaos, I soared. Andy put down a bunch of deposits on stuff for his wedding with Angela,
but then she was sleeping with Dwight for several years. Wait, no, that can't be right.
That timeline's messy. Anyway, now we are going bargain hunting in the haunted graveyard
of their love. This is my solo. I'm confused. Am I walking down the aisle to you can call
me Al? Trust me, you will not be walking. You will be boogieing. I am extremely interested.
So how much will all of this cost? Well, 12 guys, airfare, three nights in hotel, food
per diem, table up front for merch, $9,000. I don't know, it seems like a lot for an acapella
group from a college we never went to. Did you even hear the music I just played for
you? Mm-hmm. Hey. Ed's Tires is thinking of making a change. Is this good? They have
some great kitchen ideas. Oh, okay. Ed's Tires, huh? It's small, I know. I really appreciate
it. Thanks, Michael. Wait, what is this? It's for your trouble. I don't need $6 to help
a friend. No, no, listen, as a friend. I hope you know I can't take this. Yes, I do. But
don't forget, you owe me $10. It was four years ago. I should have let it go. Michael.
He gives me leads and I take the leads from him and in exchange it makes him feel good.
And if a friend can't make you feel good, then I don't want any friends. Except Dwight,
because he is our only source of fertile leads. What was up with Pam being all pushy and negative
in there? I think she just didn't want a crucifix cake. It scares me to see you going down a
road that I went down. Am I going down a road? When I see her bossing you around like that,
it just makes me wonder if this thing really has the legs to go the distance. It's so scary
how right the things you're saying are. And you're coming at it with almost no knowledge,
so of course I trust your opinion on this. I know a few things about love. Horrible,
terrible, awful. Awful things. I was going to use today to purge my inbox, but now something
much more pressing has come up. Ed Stiers, why don't you tell them that we have fewer
clients so that we can spend more time with each of them. Also, try to discuss it over
Indian food and try to mention how you distrust women. I'm not going to do that. That is smart.
That would not seem genuine. Ryan? I can get there. Good. You take the lead on this one.
Also, do not forget that he has just gone through a messy divorce. Oh, awesome. Bring
it in. Morning, cheer. U-G-L-Y. You ain't got no alibi, you ugly. You ugly. You mama
say you ugly. Hey, go Michael Scott Fabricante. I'm here. I'm part of this now. You needed
to speak to me? Dwight, take a seat. I prefer to stand. Less blood clots. No, that's weird.
You're going to sit? Great. You know, Dwight, it has been quite a transition for all of
us. Are you happy with the way things have been running lately? Why do you ask? Do you
mean compared to the way things ran with other bosses, comparisons are hard? I've just been
impressed with your performance and I wanted to make sure good work doesn't go unnoticed.
Your concern is noted. Yeah, I like your work ethic. You're so focused. Like a wolf, thank
you. I want to start giving you more responsibility. What do you say you and I go out for a drink
this week? Really? Definitely. It's firm. I need you to get me the prices that you're
charging Ed's tires so I can undercut Dunder Mifflin. I don't know that I can do that now.
You know, something's come up. Oh, is it Moe's? Did you put the cover on that well? No, Moe's
is fine. I roped it off. It's not about Moe's. Listen, things are changing here, Michael.
They're changing fast. I'm not following you. Imagine someone has a personal hero in the
house. They really want to help. Then there's this new guy. Very cool. Very Will Smith-esque.
Would not like it if he helped his hero. Personal hero, cool new guy. Okay, I think I'm getting
you trapped. Good. So you see what I'm saying? Chris O'Clair. So is this for a movie that
you're writing? No. Can I use it? No.
Dwight, are you talking about us? It is possible that I could be talking about us. So one could
say it is like the situation that we are in now. It is the situation we're in now. So
I would say that the old boss has always been good to Dwight and he was there first, so
he has dibs. You respect dibs, don't you? I'm not a barbarian. Good. Will you meet me in
the spot? I will. Dwight? Yes. Is the cool new guy Charles? That's not too much. Is
it Stanley? Hey Andy, you know I've been thinking about what you said. Noish. I just don't know
if I can do it. That's interesting because what I hear you saying is that you do want
to do it, which means you can do it. Believe me, I broke up with Angela and I'm like the
happiest guy ever. I mean I'm so happy. I'm so happy. Like total freedom, you know? It's
just that Pam gets me through the day, you know? I really rely on her. I'm pretty emotionally
needy. And you know what? I am here for you. Let me be your traveling pants. Oh, who did
you do that for? You know what I was doing there. Totally. Alright everyone, welcome
to your one stop shop for all discount party supplies, any occasion, any occasion at all.
Erin, Kelly, Meredith, how would you girls like a saucy night on the town in matching
gray dresses? Jazz it up with a little horse drawn carriage action. Oh, that sounds fun.
How much? 1600. Oh, what do you guys think? I'll go in on it with you and we can be best
friends. Great. Would you like to make it official with a church ceremony? Girl on girl. Any
red tablecloths? It's a wedding. We have white tablecloths. Crap, I want to make some pants.
Oscar, rice, 100 little baggies, perfect for a lovely dish of arroz con arroz. And these
are the ones that I like. You told me this was going to be a business related meeting.
Then I like it when you deceive me like this. Stanley, you like flowers? How would you like
60 centerpieces? I wouldn't be interested if they were free. Why are you here Stanley?
Me for the rice. Boom, sold. 100 bags of rice, Stanley Hudson. Creed, how would you like
a crispy new tuxedo for your funeral? I'll take the bottom half. I want to go out the
same way I came in, shirtless. Dwight, what's with the shirt? Are you all right? I'm sorry
Michael. Oh my God, run, run, set up, set up. No, Michael. Dwight, run. No, let's be cool.
You be cool. Yes. Just what's going on? We need to talk about our two companies and how
we should behave. Dwight tells me you've been pestering him for company info. Dwight would
not. He did. I did, Michael. I was upset about the shirt sleeves at first, but now I'm okay
with it. Michael, I want you to stop pestering my salesman. I want you to leave Dundamifl
alone. Do you understand? I understand nothing. Michael, are you all right? What's going on
here? It was a set up. Dwight told Charles. He told him. Tell us what you're talking
about. It's like a girl says she'll make out with you, but then her boyfriend is waiting
around the corner with a pee-filled balloon. We can't help you if you don't just tell us
what happened. I got hit in the face with a pee-filled water balloon. Bam. Okay, I don't
know how they did it. They filled the balloon with pee, a funnel. I don't know. Is that
clear enough for you?