Pam, line three.
Okay, thanks.
New York, as it turns out, is very expensive, and I ran out of money.
I thought about selling a kidney, but Michael offered to get me a part-time job at corporate.
Hey.
Vemola.
Of course. Now Michael knows where to reach me 16 to 18 hours a week.
Hey, Michael.
Vemola.
Mr. Kiddo.
I'm guessing that job that I got you is working out pretty well, then.
It is. Thanks again.
If there's anything else I can do, just let me know.
And of course, if there's ever anything I can ever do for you.
You know what? I would love a slice of real New York style pizza.
If I get you a slice of pizza, are we even?
Even as pie.
Okay. Don't ask me how I got it. Let's just say that I have connections.
Mmm.
I'm the Godfather.
I'm gonna eat this whole pizza.
And then I'm gonna kill you.
Girl, some cheese.
You gotta fold it up. That's the way to eat pizza.
Hey.
Hello.
That was really fun last night.
Yeah, it was nice.
I'm actually thinking about getting my own set of pot pot cough clubs.
Oh, that would be great. You need that.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Oh, really?
It would help.
I let her win.
So when can I see you again?
Tonight. I'm free tonight.
Is that too eager?
I don't care. I'm free tonight.
Okay. Oh, wait. Oh, tonight's no good.
Because I am busy taking you out.
Oh, I just remembered. I can't tonight.
Why?
I'm going out with you.
Wow. Oh, wait a second. Oh, I can't tonight.
No.
Tonight's so...
All right. Too many times.
It's all good. All right. So good.
So have a nice day.
Thank you.
You too.
You're welcome.
In my opinion, the third date is traditionally the one where you have sex.
Does Holly feel that way? I don't know.
I will probably find out tonight.
If she starts having sex with me, I'll know for sure.
I am going to run three possible date ideas by you,
and I want you to tell me which one gets your blood percolating.
I'm sure they're all great.
I have two sure things, one wild card.
Let's start with the wild card.
Okay.
The wild card is dinner at an ice restaurant.
Uh-oh.
Exactly. Here are my sure things.
I blindfold her.
Here are my sure things.
I take her to the Houdini Museum.
She chains me up.
I think I got a pretty good sense of that one.
Okay. All right.
Let's move on to the next.
Number two, we go to the mall, go to the bed store.
I let her choose whatever bed she wants.
Oh, that's sweet.
That way it was excellent.
I like the wild card.
I don't know. It's a big third date, Jim.
What do I do?
Have you asked her what she wants to do?
I thought as the man that I should make the decision.
You got that backwards.
Times have changed, Jim.
That's for you.
And, uh, oh.
I am right in assuming that Dwight is short for D-Money.
That's what I wrote on your save the date.
You set a date.
J-Money?
Or should it be T-Money for tuna?
Exceptions, Money.
K-Money.
What are you making?
A knife.
You're making a knife with a knife?
You got a better way?
You want to talk about it?
About what?
You know I know.
You know they know.
I know none of that.
And if I did, you'd be the last to know.
Oh, the mall could be fun.
Yeah.
We could go to the food court, get different foods.
You could get chicken teriyaki.
I could get a hot dog.
Some of what we order depends on if we're having sex after.
Oh, my.
Wow.
Elephant in the room.
Are we, do you think?
Do you think we're gonna have sex tonight?
Hell yeah.
Okay, so we do the restaurant thing and then we can do,
we'll just do the restaurant thing first.
Yeah, that's good.
Probably get soup or something light.
The pallet truck's got a busted caster.
We're still waiting on those safety goggles.
And we need a new fork lift.
Well, I can take maintenance cash and put it in the supply budget
if Michael's okay with it.
Michael, do you approve that?
Hell yeah.
Fine.
Also, we have gnomes living in the wall.
You mean rats?
No.
I mean little scary men with red hats.
I think they're drinking all our soda pop.
You okay with that, Mike?
Soda pop.
I don't get it.
I just don't know if he's presidential enough.
I know.
And how long is CJ gonna spend this whole MS thing?
How can Josh and Sam keep quiet?
Every night, Jim and I watch an episode of The West Wing together on DVD.
He wanted to watch Battlestar Galactica and I wanted to watch Cranford,
so we compromised.
Next, we're gonna watch Cranford.
Cranford? No.
We will never watch that.
Hi.
She introduced me to so many things.
Pasteurized milk, sheets, monotheism.
Presents on your birthday, preventative medicine.
It's nice to learn new things.
I was talking to myself.
Okay.
I just don't get it.
What don't you get?
Why is she marrying Andy?
Angela's not really a risk taker.
And Andy's not really a risk.
That's really fattening.
No, it's lettuce.
Our first date was at the Anthracite Coal Museum.
We had both been before, but we pretended like it was our first time
so we could get all the extra information.
They knew we were faking, because they recognized us,
but we made them tell us all the stories,
all the safety information,
and we corrected them whenever they got it wrong.
You want half a sandwich?
Okay.
I'll bring you one tomorrow. You've earned it.
Mmm.
I hope you like fox meat.
It's time to go?
No. No.
Reservations are a date, so we've got like an hour and 45 minutes.
Okay.
I'm a crazy eight. I'm crazy.
You're crazy. Go crazy.
Oh, I forgot my keys.
Do you need them?
Yeah, let's go grab them.
All right.
Oh, after food.
Thanks, food.
What?
Whoa.
I didn't forget my keys.
I just didn't want to make out with you in front of the cameras.
Do you think they can hear us?
Not if we turn these tiles all the way down.
Now they can't hear us at all.
Oh, good.
We're totally alone.
Yes, that's correct.
I need to cancel checks from 10,001 to 90,000.
Great. They stole my laptop.
Yeah, well, they stole my surge protector.
How does that even compare?
Oscar, I'm now going to be prone to surges.
Do you need any police tape?
You have police tape?
Do you need police tape?
In my desk, I had a delicious bottle of cream sherry.
And on my last day at work,
I was going to drink the whole thing and take a cab home.
Now I have to buy more cream sherry.
I leave my laptop at work one day,
and nothing happens, so then I start to keep it there.
Oh, my God, what happened?
We were robbed last night.
Oh, Watson, looks like a classic seven-man job.
Security tapes were stolen, motives financial,
or possibly vintage HP computer collectors.
Hank done at security had clocked out,
and that is all we have.
Can I talk to you for a second?
Yeah.
Oh, oh.