Dundra Mifflin, this is Aaron.
He's not available right now.
Uh-huh.
Yes.
Sure, I'll give him the message when he gets up.
Gets back.
Michael had chicken pot pie for lunch.
Actually, let me rephrase that.
Michael had an entire chicken pot pie for lunch.
Let me be more specific.
Michael ate an entire family-sized chicken pot pie for lunch,
and then he promptly fell asleep.
So we're all trying to be very quiet
so as to not wake him up before 5 p.m.,
which actually should be in about...
10 minutes.
Okay, I'm gonna go in there and change the computer.
Are you sure you can change his watch?
I can do it.
What do you need from me?
Normally I don't condone leaving early,
but I have an appointment with the horse doctor.
How that horse became a doctor, I don't know.
Ha ha ha ha!
No, I'm kidding.
He's just a regular doctor who shoots your horse in the head
when its leg is broken.
Hmm.
Hmm. Hmm.
Hup, hup.
Like clockwork.
Oh!
Ha ha ha ha!
Oh, no.
Uh-oh.
Oh, it's so funny.
Glad to be there.
Oh, okay, geography joke.
Ha ha ha ha!
Oh, wow, okay.
All right, let's all go home.
Come on. See you all tomorrow.
See you later, Michael.
Michael!
Yeah!
Whoo!
Ah!
Yeah!
All right, you ready for this?
Yeah, we walk around, everyone sees our faces,
and we leave, right?
Yeah.
Okay.
Wait, should I have left the car running?
Oh.
Oh, don't get us wrong, we like picnics.
Come on, who doesn't like a picnic?
Tell them what happened last year.
I had this huge spider in my baseball mat.
No, no, the guy you hit on me.
Oh, right, some drunk guy hit on Pam last year.
Said he was grabbing her for balance.
Yeah, you don't grab these for balance.
No.
How you doing, Stanley?
Same as I was yesterday, just now I'm outside.
This party sucks, Meredith.
What do you mean, mom?
Look here, Meredith.
In the car, now!
All day!
Again?
Look, Jake, unbelievable.
You have to work hard to get to play hard.
And I think people work all year long
just so they can have that one beautiful day
outdoors, hanging out with their family.
I usually bring a guy from the condo complex.
But this year,
I would just rather catch up
with some of my old friends from the other branches.
Like Dan Gore.
And Holly will be here.
We exchanged emails.
And that guy from Akron?
I'm gonna say 30.
Ah, 40.
Insect repellent, which we clearly need,
reduces the effectiveness of SPF.
Good point, but I've thought of that already.
Combination SPF, repellent.
Whoa. How many?
Of course. You think the EPA would ever allow that much DEET?
Rolf is my best friend.
We met in a shoe store.
I heard him asking for a shoe that could increase his speed
and not leave any tracks.
Michael, isn't that Holly?
We're just friends.
Hey, hey, wait a second.
Who let you in here?
Is what I want to know.
Oh, no.
I see they're letting just anybody in here.
Yeah, that's right.
All right.
Mm-hmm.
Hey.
Hi.
You remember AJ, my boyfriend?
A little bit.
I meet a lot of people.
Hey, Michael.
So would you guys like some lemonade?
Or one of you?
Or both of you?
Either or.
Combinations are endless.
Lemonade sounds great.
I'd love an iced tea, actually.
You can go to hell.
I'm kidding.
Sure, I will get you the best iced tea in the world.
I lied to Kevin.
Holly and I can never be just friends.
I wrote down a list of bullet points
why Holly and I should be together,
and I'm going to find the perfect moment today
and I'm going to tell her.
Number one, Holly.
You and I are soup snakes.
And the reason is
because in terms of the soup,
we like tea.
That doesn't make any sense.
We're soulmates.
Holly and I are soulmates.
Jim.
Pam.
Hey, how are you? Hey, Charles.
Hey, nice day. Yeah.
Must be nice to get a rest from all your rest.
I don't get it.
He's not even my boss anymore.
I'm sorry to beat him up for you.
I shouldn't have to ask you to do stuff like that.
You should just do it.
Listen up, everyone. I've gone over this line up very carefully.
We cannot forget the humiliation
we suffered last year at the softball game
with Jim's whole spider in the mitt incident.
Right?
Well, I could have died, so...
I looked it up online afterwards.
Aaron, back row.
Ryan, you move up a row.
Broomigo.
You think you could put Aaron on my row?
I mean, if...
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. Wait a minute. I get it.
You want her to set you up
so you can spike it.
Uh...
I tell you what, I'm gonna do you one better.
I'm gonna put you next to Phyllis.
She's the best setter on the team.
That's... you sly dog.
Not what I meant. Come on, folks!
What is up with you two, Holly?
Uh, not much.
We're designing a house.
Cool. For who?
For us.
Wow!
I'm designing a chair.
It's part of your pants.
Sit down. You're supported.
I remember your chair pants idea.
Yeah.
I like that. Put me down for a pair.
I'm a size 34 waist.
All right, fatty. I will do it.
You know what? We should actually rehearse.
Okay.
You guys are really gonna do this?
You bet your fat ass we are.
Well, in his infinite wisdom,
David Wallace has authorized us
to put on a little presentation
about the history of Dunder Mifflin.
Yep. The whole comedy team
is back together again.
That's right.
Have you heard the news?
Extra, extra, read all about it.
Newspapers for sale!
Sit down.
Are you blind?
Sir,
with the glasses, are you literally blind?
I'm concerned you might be in danger.
These are expensive Ray-Bans, jackass.
Okay. I was just looking out for you.
You're doing great, by the way.
Thanks.
I got it.
Oh!
Oh, Kevin, come on!
Are you blind? I could have gotten that, idiot!
Can you see things with your eyeballs?
Come on, people! We need to get our heads
in the game with focus.
Come on, you're better than this!
I am better than this!
Phyllis, why are you sitting on the ground?
We've been out here for a while.
I don't need this.
God!
Applause