Sorry everybody, my apologies.
That is a surprise. Michael's almost never late. And he hasn't worked here in four weeks.
Hey, what are you doing?
Overslept. Do you think anybody noticed I was late?
I think they're just surprised you're here at all.
Huh, that's him.
Michael.
Gentlemen.
Was I supposed to stop him? He seemed so confident.
No, they're good.
Sorry. Sorry, sorry, sorry. Where's Ryan?
He's late.
It's 4.30 in the morning. Do you know where your kids are?
If you are Ryan's parents or Pam's parents or my parents, you do.
They're gonna be in this van with me. Who am I? Nothing to fear. I am just a 44-year-old guy with a paper route.
Time to make the donuts.
Come on.
Whoa!
No, I promise I won't do it again. Come on.
I lied!
We've been making 5M deliveries for a couple weeks now.
Ever since I've gotten clean, there's something about fresh morning air that just really makes me sick.
Hello? Time to make the donuts.
Oh, Halbert. Wow! Butter Patrol. Arrest that man. Your donuts make me go nuts.
Hey, Pam.
We got the van at a used car lot. We think it says, Hallelujah Church of Scranton in Korean.
It was either this or an old school bus with an owl living in it.
You didn't happen to bring any coffee, did you, Michael?
Milk and sugar.
Oh, awesome. You're a lifesaver.
Wait, is this just milk and sugar?
That's what I said.
Do you drink this every day?
Every morning.
We're doing okay. A couple weeks in, and we're having fun.
I consider myself someone who likes to work with his hands.
I type and I file and I will use a telephone.
But I have found that one of the things I really enjoy about making my own deliveries is the ability to work with my feet as well.
I get to use the accelerator and the brake of the van.
And I walk from the van.
And I walk back to the van.
So even though I consider myself a hands-on guy, I guess I'm also kind of a foots on guy.
20 of those.
Oh, excuse me. Sorry. Sorry. No, it's a paper company now.
It's not for the church.
Damn it! Where is my Amy room?
What's wrong?
Two things. Can't find my Andy mug and I lost another client to the Michael Scott paper company.
Tell me about it. I lost two this week.
I'm sorry. I thought it was a cute mug. You're making a funny expression.
Ah.
Then I decree that you, Lady Erin of Reception, enjoy the Andy mug.
I'm really just mad about losing a client.
I heard that Michael is hand delivering the paper himself. And Ryan's a blonde now.
I heard they get sausage.
Sorry. This is really bothering me.
Oh.
This is yours, isn't it?
Okay. Who covers Van's pet grooming?
Oh, they're my client.
No. They were your client. They just called and said they're switching over to Michael Scott paper company.
Ah. Shame, Jim. I expected more.
In the last month, we have lost ten major clients to Michael Scott.
What are we supposed to do? They keep undercutting us on price.
I don't want to hear excuses. I want to see improvements. This is unacceptable.
Hey, boss. I'd just like to point out that I have been here less time than these guys.
Why are you telling me this?
I just think the bar should be lower for a newbie.
Is this something you really want to have said?
I don't want to have said that.
But I think it's important that you know it.
I don't know what to do to inspire these people. Okay? Maybe it's my fault.
It's not your fault. Some people just don't want to be inspired.
I wrote a memo to all departments asking them to find ways to save money. But, uh...
Charles, I got your memo. Thank you.
I want you to know I'm putting my foot down when it comes to expense reports.
Waste not, want not.
Well said, Angela.
Been there, done that.
Stanley?
Andrew?
Rejected?
You never had a problem with me expensing cigars before.
Yes, I did. I just didn't have the power to enforce it.
Phyllis, this client you take out to offer it to us every Saturday night?
It wouldn't happen to be a refrigeration company, would it?
Michael never cared. He said it was a perk of the job.
Hmm. I'm sorry. I get no joy from this.
Hey.
Oh!
You know what we need? We need some couches in here.
Michael, we should really consider getting a delivery guy.
Oh. You know what you would love?
Is if we built a loft.
Why would I love that?
Can we afford a delivery guy?
You can't afford a loft in a dorm room.
You put your desk underneath, you have your loft up top, you can sleep up top.
Yeah, I know what a loft is.
Most dorm rooms don't even have that.
Most do in the magazines.
Let's see what a delivery guy costs.
We should look into that.
Or we just go for the loft.
Would you let Charles know that David is here?
Please.
David. David Wallace.
Hello, we've been expecting you, David Wallace.
Charles and I were waiting for you.
There he is. There he is. How was the trip up?
A lot better than a month at this Grand Radisson, I'm sure.
Oh, you know what? Hasn't been that bad.
Hasn't been that bad, these people who assaulted you up down here.
You couldn't ask for a better way to learn a company.
I feel like I should be thanking you.
Oh.
The conference room is ready if we want to get started.
You know, I just want to address everyone first.
Oh, yeah, take your time. Stanley, pay attention.
Hi, everyone.
Hi.
Uh, look, it's no secret...
Hello?
Uh, it is no secret that Michael Scott Paper
has siphoned off a large chunk of our core business, and I'm here.
I just want to reassure everyone that we think this is a good time to get started.
I'm not going to let you down.
I just want to reassure everyone that we think this is a temporary setback.
Right.
Okay?
Maybe, and I don't know, if you'd just returned Michael's call,
none of us would have lost clients.
I've been wondering that myself lately.
We're just going to get started, we're going to figure this out.
Rest assured, Jim, can you come in with us, please?
Oh, Jim, hold on.
You know, David, uh, Dwight's been my guy.
Yeah.
Jim...
Really? I find that extraordinarily surprising.
Oh, he shows promise.
And Jim, I don't know. I know he's been a disappointment.
We'll bring them both.
Okay, great.
Dwight, come on in.
Also, Jim.
Come along, afterthought.
Well, this is very exciting.