Dunder Mifflin is about to be sold, but first an investment banker has to drop by and sign
off on our branch.
And I'm pretty nervous about it, and I'm making some cosmetic tweaks to help create a more
appealing environment.
Is that dishonest?
Well, think of it this way.
When you look in the mirror and you see your push-up bra and your fake eyelashes and your
makeup and your press-on nails, the principles that I'm applying to the office are the same
ones that have made Lady Gaga a star or any number of drag queens.
Hello, Eric Ward.
Welcome to Dunder Mifflin.
I am Computron, your answer to everything.
Hello.
I see you've made Computron, our virtual helper.
I'm Michael Scott.
Welcome, welcome.
Computron is just one of the many modern devices that I have incorporated into the
office.
Watch this.
Computron.
Yes?
What is the world's largest ocean?
Calculating.
Pacific!
Pacific Ocean.
Pretty cool, huh?
Follow me.
Any messages?
Yes, the governor called.
He said thank you.
Well tell him I told you so.
What's the second message?
The treasury called.
Dunder Mifflin paper is being used for counterfeit currency.
That's how good it is.
That's the price you pay when you're the best.
Michael, we're now the official paper supplier of the NFL.
That is fantastic.
It's good but it's not good enough.
Keep working.
And here's Pam.
She's our international sales consultant.
Hello.
The NFL celebrated its 50th anniversary in 1972.
Hola.
Bonjour.
Ni hao.
It might seem crazy but since there's no one left in New York, Michael is Dunder Mifflin's
highest ranking employee.