Buenos dias, Aaron.
Buenos dias, Miguel.
Hello, Dunderiflam.
No, no, no, no.
Solamente en español, por favor.
I believe that every man, woman, and child in this country
should learn how to speak Spanish.
They are our neighbors to the south,
and this would be a healing thing for all of North America.
And,
I am going on vacation next week to Cape Coo.
Buenos dias, Jaime.
Buenos dias, Miguel.
¿Cómo está? Bien?
Claro que sí.
Yo soy fantástico.
¿Qué pasa?
Ha-ha!
Buenos dias, Dwight.
Guten Tag, Herr Michael.
I don't understand why Michael is wasting his time with Spanish.
I have it on very good authority that within 20 years,
everyone will be speaking German.
Or, I don't know.
Everyone will be speaking German.
Or a Chinese-German hybrid.
La telefona.
El teléfono.
Michael is having a hard time with the gender part of Spanish,
so I told him to mark everything with the international symbol for gender.
And, um, I should have been more specific.
Your office is full of genitalia.
Eso es lo que dice él.
That's what he says?
Damn it.
Ah, Angelo.
Angela.
Michael.
Yo soy Cancun.
All right, so I'll finish up on bulk pricing,
and then you go into delivery guarantee.
You know, maybe there's an opportunity for a joke there.
Like, um, like, I just delivered a baby.
They didn't offer me a guarantee.
Yeah, maybe we don't even need that.
Can you smell the power? Halperts.
Power couple.
You know what? I should be getting this client, Michael.
My numbers are better than either of you.
I'm not going to be able to get a client.
I'm not going to be able to get a client, Michael.
My numbers are better than either of theirs.
I went with the people I thought would put the best face on the company.
If you want people to put the best face on something,
why would you get two people who probably have never cut the face off
of anything in their lives?
That's a good point.
This is our first joint sales pitch,
and I think we're going to work really well together.
Yeah, I think we have complementary strengths.
We understand each other.
We have good give and take.
I give, he takes.
I don't even know who you are anymore.
Yay.