Stop it.
Stop what?
You're talking about me and Morse code.
But you know what?
Joke's on you because I know Morse code.
Ha!
Yeah, that's what we're doing.
In our very limited free time and with our very limited budget, we went and got a nanny,
and then we went out and took a class on a very outmoded and very unnecessary form of communication
just so we could talk about you in front of you.
Yep, that's exactly what we did.
It all started when Dwight was tapping his foot against the leg of his desk.
When I asked him to stop, he said, I will, when you lose the baby weight.
Very well. I must have imagined it. I apologize.
Detonator. Detonator, where? Michael!
Jim, are you clicking a detonator?
It's a pin. He said there's a detonator in here.
Okay.
Michael, that is totally not...
True.
Right?
Yep.
Wait, he just coughed not in Morse code, so he said that's not not true.
That's a double negative.
The only Morse code I know is J Morse code. ABF. Always be funny.
Michael, come on.
Get back to work, Dwight. Please.
Fine.
Hey, tap away.