Hey, Jim, Jim, come here.
Do you know who that is?
No.
Look at him. Look at him. T-shirt, jeans?
Is it you?
No. I am Flattered.
That's Johnny Depp.
Where'd you take that?
In my condo complex.
Oh my God, that's right.
I read in People magazine that he was looking for a two-bedroom condo on Scranton.
I'm flipping out, man.
Well, you remember my idea for the fourth Pirates movie.
Sure, I thought they should do one.
Hey, Jim, Jim, where do I find the Black Pearl?
Who's that?
Captain Jack Sparrow.
Captain Jack Sparrow, Jim.
John Dillinger.
No, I'm Captain Jack Sparrow.
Captain Crunch.
Okay, okay. Screw you, Halpert.
You know, it's not easy getting excited about stuff.
Remember how you felt when you thought you'd seen Roger Clemens?
At the Yankees game.
Yeah. Well, it wasn't him.
I had a little better reason to believe that...
You're right. You're right.
Well, you're not right, because Johnny Depp in your condo complex?
I know. I know.
It also explains why the name on his mailbox was M. Schulman.
M. Night Schulman?
First up, the lost and found has gone missing.
It itself is lost, so please try not to lose anything until we find it.
Okay, great. I'll write it up and shoot you an email.
Thanks, Bill.
Willis, please, no phone calls during my meetings.
Yeah!
Cha-cha!
I'm sorry, Bill.
I'm sorry.
Yeah!
Cha-ching!
Okay, item two. Congratulations, Willis. Way to go.
Item three.
The good ladies at bikiniweathergirls.com are predicting freezing rain next week,
so please tell your clients that deliveries may be delayed.
Mr. Darrell, all over that.
What you want me to do about it?
Call the clients and let them know that deliveries will be delayed.
Mike said let your clients know.
They're your clients. Let them know.
You're in charge of shipping, right?
They're your clients, right?
I don't think salesmen are supposed to be doing stuff like that anymore.
A saber wants us just to be selling all the time.
I've been here a long time.
31 years.
And for the first time, things are being done right.
In all that time.
I just think our new bosses realize what I've been thinking all along.
The sales business is the whole business.
It's the whole thing.
Ah, pet day. If you don't have a pet, please don't feel like it.
When are we getting to sales topics?
Yeah, what about those leads?
Did you hear anything from corporate?
Ah, yes, the leads.
The leads that Sabre has spent $50,000 to get from a market research company are not here yet.
Damn it.
No, no, no, no, no. The meeting's not over.
But is there anything relevant to the sales staff here?
No sales topic per se.
Well, then no Andy Bernard, per se.
I agree.
Dwight?
Sorry, Michael. I've got calls to make.
Okay, rules are rules.
I love these new rules.
I no longer have to deal with paperwork.
And because of this new pay structure, there is literally no limit to the amount of money I can make.
It is possible, stay with me here, it is possible I can make over $100,000 this year.
Finally be able to put in that pool Moe's and I have been dreaming of.
To drown pigs humanely.
And cross train.
I would like your undivided attention, please.
You couldn't handle my undivided attention.
Hey, good luck with the meeting.
I'll be finding the lost and found.
This is how it's going to be from now on.
Over the last few weeks things have been changing here.
Sabre says it is our duty to support the sales team.
And the salesmen are letting it go to their heads.
I think it's kind of screwed up.
Because the way this place used to work was make friends first, make sales second, make love third.
In no particular order.
Listen, Michael.
About what happened earlier.
Yeah?
When I was asking about the leads.
Is there any news on the leads?
Is that all you have to say to me?
Yeah.
You got any news on the leads?
Okay, I'll tell you what.
I'm going out on a very important sales call.
You get any news about the leads, you try me.