This here is a radon test kit.
Okay, I'll be putting them everywhere.
And please don't throw these out.
This is a radon test kit.
Please don't throw these out.
See them all over the office.
Toby has been leaving radon kits everywhere,
like he owns the place.
The first time I threw mine away,
I thought it was an ant trap.
But I figured I'd rather live with ants
than with this creepy little disk.
The second time, I thought it was one of those,
you know, the things you turn over and it moves,
like a cow thing.
But upon closer examination,
it was another ant trap, so I threw it away.
And the third time, I did it out of spite.
Come on, Michael, you're interrupting.
You're kidding me! God!
You say radon is silent but deadly,
and then you expect me not to make farting noises with my mouth?
What is this?
Sit down.
You know what? We're not going to die of radon.
We're going to die of boredom.
Right?
And if I had a gun with two bullets,
and I was in a room with Hitler, bin Laden, and Toby,
I would shoot Toby twice.
No.
Okay.
You were being really funny, and then you went too far.
I would kill bin Laden and then Toby.
No.
Okay, geniuses, how would you do it?
Curve the bullet like in my favorite James McAvoy film,
Wadid.
All that does is help you shoot around things.
Is there a curtain rod in the room?
I don't know.
How about make believe Lan-Ez anything you want?
Stanley, please, this is serious.
Is this the thing where they use an icicle so there's no evidence?
Yes.
Re-stab Toby through the heart with an icicle?
The bullet-two bullet thing is a red herring.
Here's how you do it.
You line them all up, you take one bullet,
shoot them all through the throat at the same time.
Watch this.
Phyllis, you're Hitler. Come up here.
Toby, you're Toby.
Andy, you're bin Laden.
Line up.
I don't want her to.
Throat's together.
Toby, just do it.
Toby, come on.
Oh, God.
Ready?
One bullet and boom.
Yeah, that works.
It worked.