MUSIC
Pam's doing great.
She's 10 inches dilated now.
Sorry, meters.
Centimeters.
And she's also fully effaced, which I don't know what that is.
But no baby yet.
It's only been six at 19 hours.
And I've sent out some ice chips because I might have passed out a little bit.
But these are very refreshing.
Very cute.
Daddy, he's ready to push.
Okay.
Where's my little niblets?
Halpert Room D1.
Alright.
Family only beyond this point.
Thank you.
Here we go.
Doing great.
Push again.
Not yet.
No, don't push.
Pull.
Why don't you get some more ice chips?
No, Jim, stay.
Okay, really push this time, Pam.
Okay.
Nope, not yet, not yet, not yet.
I'm gonna go wash my eyes.
That kid's gonna have a lot of hair.
Have you guys seen her?
She hasn't popped yet.
What?
Damn it.
She was supposed to come out yesterday.
I decided to give baby Halpert a newspaper from the day she was born.
This frame set me back 55 bones.
But she decided to take her sweet time, so now I have to switch it with today's paper.
This is ridiculous.
We just can't wait here.
I think it's gonna be any minute now.
But you don't know that.
I mean, we could be here another half an hour.
Phyllis, what could you possibly have to do?
I have an ice cream cake in the car.
Oh my God.
Oh, go, go.
Are you insane?
All right.
Guys?
Hello?
You're doing great.
Just relax.
Sorry to be a bother, but if we could have an ETA, when this is gonna...
You're kinda losing them.
Oh my God.
Look at her.
Babe, she's so beautiful.
Oh my God.
Yeah.
That's right.
That's your baby, see?
Sir?
Sir, you can't smoke that in here.
Okay.
Put it out.
All right.
I can't smoke anywhere these days.
Delivery wasn't so bad, right?
Ah, f*** you.
Wow.
Now I just made a wonderful ending.
Kinda rough getting here.
We did not handle that well.
I think you have to admit, you flipped out a little bit.
I think you should stop talking now.
Okay.
Uh oh.
Someone's still a little sore.
You sitting on your donut, hon?
She's incredible.
You want to count her fingers and toes again?
No, let's let her rest.
I'm sure there's still 12 of them each.
Okay.
Guys, guys!
Her name is Cecilia Marie Halpert.
Eleven pounds.
She's seven pounds.
Seven pounds.
Two ounces.
Eighteen inches.
Mother and daughter doing great.
Yeah!
Wow!
Yayow!
Congratulations.
That's great.
There.
Hey, Grandma's back.
Well, I was an adventure and a half trying to find the cafeteria, but I have returned
with the coffee.
Oh, great.
Oh, thank God.
I haven't had caffeine in nine months.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Oh, somebody has a full diaper.
Oh, let me get it.
I am a diapering master.
I have done little else in the past two months.
There is nothing I cannot diaper.
Go ahead and try to think of something.
I dare you.
What is the paper?
I want to see the paper.
Oh!
Oh.
Helene?
Hi.
Oh, my goodness.
What are the odds of this?
Congratulations on being a grandma.
Hello, Michael.
Hello.
Oh, how are you?
I'm worried about you.
You know, I think it's time for me to go.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
There you go.
Oh, okay.
Mwah.
Love you.
As a friend.
Love you, Mom.
I want to hold the baby.
Okay, you just have to use the hand sanitizer first.
Oh, right.
Again, no pants.
Ready?
Mm-hmm.
Oh.
Oh, okay.
Okay.
Oh, good.
Oh.
Mm-hmm.
Ooh, wow.
Michael. Michael.
That's so weird. She was saying it just before you got here.
Oh.
Oh. Oh.
Yesterday, I was dispatched to Jim and Pam's house
to find Pam's iPod.
I searched everywhere, but I didn't find it.
What I did find was mold and lots of it.
So I did what anyone would do.
I read a book, had a bath, I got a good night's sleep,
and I made plans to eradicate it.
I also made plans to ask Jim
where he bought his marvelous sheets.