Hello, hello.
Top of the morning to ya.
Woohoo!
Green M&Ms.
Natress Viagra.
Two of my favorite joke areas combined.
It's gonna be a good day.
I don't want to be my friends.
Why can't it just be the two of us?
Because it's St. Patrick's Day.
People go out in groups.
Well, why don't you invite your friends?
Why are you being so weird about this?
Stop fighting.
Just on St. Patrick's Day, okay?
Just one perfect day a year.
No hassles.
No problems.
No kids.
Why no kids?
Yeah, we're your kids.
Nope.
Uh-uh.
Not today.
It is St. Patrick's Day.
And here in Scranton, that is a huge deal.
It is the closest that the Irish will ever get to Christmas.
Oscar.
You're not Irish.
It's St. Patrick's Day.
What if I wore a sombrero on Cinco de Mayo?
That would be wonderful, Kevin.
Gross.
I'd be offended.
I'm sorry.
Welcome back, Dad.
Oh, thank you.
Hey.
Very good.
Okay.
We'll get back to you in that right away.
Thanks.
What do we got here?
Mega desk.
Of course.
Command central.
Uh-huh.
Surveillance, gaming, and business.
Okay.
I got...
What?
Come on.
I'm sorry.
Jim.
Tweedle D and Tweedle Dumbass have been away on maternity leave.
But now Tweedle Dumbass is back and we have a problem.
Yes, getting hooked on Mega Desk was my own damn fault.
But I don't care about assigning blame.
All I care about is Mega Desk.
That is all I care about.
Getting more Mega Desk.
Oh, I love this so much fun.
There's such team spirit in this room.
Morning, darling.
Morning.
Well, this is my last day at this Granton branch for a while, but I'm leaving in the
very capable hands of some of the loveliest people I've ever had the pleasure of knowing.
You know, I'm gonna miss this place.
And the snow.
My dogs love being in that snow.
Makes me think they're on to something.
Oh, Angela, I love that sweater.
Phyllis, green is definitely your color.
Mr. Bratton, you look well rested.
Didn't sleep a wink?
Oh.
Excuse me, Joe.
This is that Japanese pistol I was telling you about.
Oh, you didn't do it justice, boy.
That is a fine piece of steel.
Oh, she is. Isn't she?
In hell, I'm gonna be dreaming about her tonight.
Oh, you and me both.
Oh.
Oh, good morning, sweetheart.
Good morning, honey pile.
I'm sorry, but is that a gift I see in your hands?
It is.
This is a little something for you to remember your time here in Scranton.
What?
Is that a lump of coal?
Yes, it is.
Have you been that naughty?
No, no, no.
That is a good gift, actually.
Buildings here in Scranton are literally powered by coal.
Thank you very much.
We don't get much coal down into Alahassee.
I mean, just alligators and some of the worst Chinese food you've ever tasted.
That sounds great, actually.
Well, if you ever get down in my neck of the woods, you got a place to stay.
When you work for Saber, only one thing matters,
and I don't care if you're a loser or you practice bestiality.
If Joe likes you, you are in, and I am in.
Erin, go brawl.
Andy, go brawl to you.
Nice.