Good morning, everybody.
Who would like an authentic New York bagel?
Hmm? Stanley?
Thank you.
Oh, no, no, no.
I got a pumpernickel just for you.
Wow. H&H.
You went all the way to New York City to get us bagels?
Oh, why? Is there a place closer that sells them?
This is really nice, Dwight. Thanks.
Thanks. Oh, don't mention it.
You owe me one. You all owe me one.
Good morning, Michael.
Good morning, Dwight.
Hungry?
No. I had a fish stick sandwich.
Actually, I had two fish stick sandwiches.
My girlfriend didn't want hers,
because I guess I'm the only aphrodisiac she needs.
Fish sticks are not an aphrodisiac.
Yeah.
You're thinking of deer penis.
It worked.
Regardless, that was over two hours ago,
and it is now a scientific fact that you are hungry.
Bagel?
I don't mind if I do.
Hey, I brought cheese, too.
I'm taking one for my lady friend.
Excellent.
Brain food.
Thank you very much.
Okay.
You owe me.
Can't a guy just buy some bagels for his friends
so they'll owe him a favor,
which he can use to get someone fired
who stole a co-manager position from him anymore?
Geez.
When did everyone get so cynical?
Pam, would you care for a bagel?
Oh, no, thank you.
Oh, that's right.
You're a woman,
and you need to refuse food the first time.
I'll try again.
Please, Pam, reconsider and have a bagel.
I have an early lunch.
Michael's been trying to get Jim and me to hang out
ever since he started dating my mom.
I don't know.
I really hoped this thing would just die out.
But today, he's planning a birthday lunch for my mom.
I'm sorry.
Today, he's planning a birthday lunch for my mom,
and we have to go.
No way out.
These are amazing.
You took all these?
I've always found beauty in uncommon places.
Homeless people.
Graffiti.
Photography lets me capture all that.
Have you ever been photographed before?
Oh, just by, like, friends.
Well, here's what I've been doing around here.
It's for a series on exposure in the workforce.
Woo-hoo!
Pammy?
Hey.
Hi.
Happy birthday.
Thank you.
Girls.
There they are.
Birthday lunch.
Birthday lunch, there's no better medicine than birthday lunch.
It'll cure all of your...
Gee, I don't know if Michael should be dating my mother
and fixes all occurrences of...
I don't really see them together.
So, open wide, Pam.
And take a big old spoonful of birthday lunch medicine.
Take with food.
Pam, aren't you gonna introduce us to Michael's girlfriend?
I think you guys all remember my mom from the wedding.
Yeah, I think everyone has met Helene, shall we?
Wait a minute, is that another birthday present for me?
Because you already gave me a necklace.
Oh, my God, I love it.
Tell her how you gave it to me.
No, that wouldn't be...
You put it around my neck while I was still asleep this morning.
A very nice way to wake up.
Yeah, the rest of the story has been censored due to inappropriate.
Because of sex?
Hey.
Kevin.
Please, Kevin, you're fired.
Sorry, sorry, work with a bunch of idiots, shall we go?
Yes, let's go.
Oh, wait.
Um, Swords Lumber's on the phone for you, Pam, and they say it's urgent.
Oh, you guys, just one second.
Oh, my gosh.
Are you serious?
Shipping emergency.
I don't think I can go to lunch.
Oh, man, that's crazy.
Right as we were on our way out, too.
I know. Isn't that always how it goes?
Rarely. If ever.
Let me give it a whirl. I'll talk to them.
I want to handle it.
That's okay.
I feel like it's...