You want to see me?
Yeah, have a seat.
Is it serious?
Wow.
Any little scale.
Okay, right there.
Right there is the problem.
There have been reports around the office
that you have been talking baby talk.
Why would people say that?
Well, I have not good authority
that you said the following.
Can you read that back to me?
Andy have a boo-boo tummy.
Would you rather me say,
hey guys, my irritable bowel syndrome is flaring up.
Crazy diarrhea happening right now.
Because things can get real adult real fast.
You are also on record as saying,
whittle-iddle, footy-woody's, num-nums, jammies,
make boom-boom, widdicawess, and woad-eye-wind.
Do I sometimes replace r's with w's?
Do I sometimes repeat a word to get my point across?
Well, if I do, Andy, sorry.
You can't be a baby in the office.
It makes me look like I hire babies.
Well, if we are complaining,
a lot of people think your Elvis voice is annoying.
Okay, who said that?
Just people.
For the record, I think it is pretty fantastic.
Well, thank you.
Thank you a lot.
And for what it is worth, I think your baby voice is top.
Thank you, Mr. Elvis.
You are welcome, by the way.
MUSIC
Dr. Tude, I have some terrible news.
Wait, are you the patient or the doctor?
The entire office is come down
pernicious case of the Mondays.
Wow, what do you put our chances at?
Zero percent.
Unless we perform an immediate
emergency morale transplant stat.
Oh, sounds risky.
Don't worry, there is a surefire cure.
Employee of the month.
Every awesome place I've worked had one.
Bear Stearns, Lehman Brothers, AIG,
my summer den run.
Wow, that's not such a bad idea.
Great!
Anything else?
Nope.
Frankie's dirty joke with the day.
There's a bunch of those.
Keep.
There's a bunch of sent emails that just say delivered.
Should I delete those?
I wanna keep those so I can see what I sent.
That's why you have a sent mail folder.
Keep.
There's about three news alerts for nip slip.
For what?
Nip slip.
Oh, okay.
I don't know how those get on there.
Well.
Must be hackers.
Ooh.
Hey.
What's up?
What if I told you I had done the worst thing
ever, would you still wanna be my friend?
Did you murder someone?
Worst murder.
Oh my God.
Lurk much?
I miss Pam.
I think she's okay.
Is that what we're going for now?
Okay.
We used to go for pretty good.
Great.
Hey, how do you feel about starting
an employee of the month program?
Yeah.
You know what, that actually might make me feel better.
I'm not in this for the trophies, but.
You're not in it at all
because you can't be employee of the month,
you're a manager.
Well, technically I am a co-manager
and I barely have any responsibilities.
All right.
But I work hard.
I love this company and for those reasons
I think I would make a good employee of the month.
It would look bad.
Sorry.
It would look good on my mantle.
Dude's talking to Michael right now.
They totally went for our idea.
Yeah.
Your idea.
My idea.
I just need Andy to think it's his idea
so it won't get traced back to me.
In approximately six hours,
Jim will get a phone call from David Wallace.
He will be fired.
You were like, we should do an employee of the month
and I was like, genius.
You said that.
And then you were like, go talk to Jim about it
and I was like, I'm on it.
No, I think you pretty much came up
with the whole idea yourself from top to bottom.
And you know what else?
I think you're a shoe in to win it.
And I think that Ms. Erin will be mightily impressed
when you are crowned employee of the month.
Was Jessica Simpson impressed with Dane Cook
in the motion picture employee of the month?
I don't know.
I didn't see it.
Was she?
I didn't see it either, but one has to assume.
Huh?
Oh yeah, I guess so.
Okay.
Whoa!
I love having Pam around.
I don't know what I'd do without her.
Whenever Erin shows me her work, I just say, looks great.
Looks great.
That usually does the trick.
Hey Pam, do you have a sec to check over the Saturn Rary?
Looks great.
Oh, did you really look it over?
Felt like maybe you didn't.
Okay.
The Michael Scott Foundation is still in existence.
There you are.
I don't think we have finished with my inbox.
What's Scott's tot?
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha.
Has it really been 10 years?
Local businessman pledges college tuition to third graders.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha.
Michael, why did you promise that?
To change lives?
No, Michael, why would you promise that?
You know, okay, I can't.
College school, cancel.
I can't go through with this.
We've already rescheduled seven times.
Michael, this is a terrible, terrible thing you've done.
Well.
It's terrible.
Just terrible.
And the longer you put it off, the worse it's gonna get.
I just, I fell in love with these kids
and I didn't wanna see them fall victim to the system.
So I made them a promise.
I told them that if they graduated from high school,
I would pay for their college education.
I've made some empty promises in my life,
but hands down, that was the most generous.
Just tell me it is going to be okay, all right?
No.
I'm not a bad news person.
I bring good news.
Like when I promised those kids I'd pay for college.
Ha ha ha ha ha.
Okay, all right.
You have to tell them.
Would you come with me, you know,
like old times instead of.
I can print out a new itinerary with Pam's name on it.
It's fine.
Aaron, you're gonna go
and you're gonna make sure Michael tells the truth.
Oh God, you know what?
Could this day get any worse?
Hello everyone.
Could I have your attention please?
I know things have been a little rough lately
and I thought it might be a nice boost of morale
to start an employee of the month program.
The winner would get a plaque, my parking space
and one paid vacation day.
Mr. Scott.
Hey, Michaela Lasker.
How are you?
I'm good.
Good to see you.
Where's your saxophone?
It's in the music room, Mr. Scott.
Eighth grade graduation.
She gave a rendition of when the Saints go marching in
that would blow your freaking mind.
Wow.
Well, you didn't even hear it.
Everyone's so excited that you're here today.
Oh, good.
Now I know you probably wanna see everyone
but I was wondering if I could ask you some questions first.
You're famous.
I'm sure you remember this place.
Oh, yep.
Do you wanna go in?
No, not at all.
No, come on.
Hey, Jimmy, what's up?
Not much.
Cool, very cool.
I bet if you tried,
you could grow the best beard of anyone in the world.