Could you please sign my expense report?
No way, no how.
Expense reports are a day-to-day item.
That is Jim's now.
I am exclusively big picture.
Epic.
Sign this.
Where's the please?
We're not animals.
Sign it.
No, not without a please.
Idiot.
I have a complaint about Jim.
That is not big picture.
I would like to file a huge, enormous, massive complaint about the tallest guy in our office.
I'm sorry, Jim.
I'm sorry, Jim 125.
The tallest guy in our office.
Jim won't sign my expense report.
That is not okay.
That is a big...
That is a day-to-day...
No, that is huge.
You're trying to trick me.
This has to do with...
Get out, get out, get out, get out.
I'd like to lodge a complaint.
I'm sorry to hear about that.
Who is this about?
You.
Okay.
I know I take complaints very seriously, so...
When did this happen?
One minute ago.
Okay.
And how do you feel?
Angry.
All right. Did he hit you?
No.
Did you cry?
Did you feel like crying?
No.
I'm just gonna write, held back tears.
Wait, stop writing that.
That is not true.
If you stop crying, I'll stop writing it.
I'm not...
I deserve that promotion, not Jim.
Oh, man.
Makes me want to put him in a triangle chokehold
and force him down to the ground
and just keep pressing and pressing
and then flip him over
and then put him in a hammer lock.
And he's gasping, he's panning for every last breath.
And the crowd is going crazy.
And boom, I emerge victorious.
Aha!
$18,000 and a chance at the title.
Ooh-hah!
I have to... Jim wants you to keep it down.
Oh, sure.
Things are great for Michael.
And why wouldn't they be?
Absolutely nothing's changed for him.
He still acts like he's the only one in charge.
But today, Jim Halpert puts his foot down.
So that was three days ago, and it didn't take.
But today, mark my words,
Jim Halpert really, really puts his foot down.
Everyone, now would be a good time to freshen up
because I'd like everyone to meet in the conference room
in five minutes, and I suggest that you bring a snack
because we may be in there for a while.
Michael. Yes.
Can I talk to you in my office for a second?
Sure, but could I first talk to you in my office?
Can I also be a boss?
Look, it doesn't take a genius to know that any organization
thrives when it has two leaders.
Go ahead, name a country that doesn't have two presidents,
a boat that sets sail without two captains.
Where would Catholicism be without the popes?
I have noticed that we... Welcome.
Thank you.
I've noticed we've been having a lot of conference room meetings,
and I'm wondering if perhaps those are a bit...
Disruptive. Yes.
No, I don't think they are.
I think the meetings are very important.
Okay, maybe we should talk specifics.
Let's do.
Okay.
Yesterday, we had a meeting about planets.
Well, to be fair, Jim, James,
and Jimothy.
To be fair, Jimothy, the...
That sounds weird.
Are you okay with being called Jim?
I am.
Jim, to be fair, the conversation wasn't about planets.
At first, we were talking about introducing a line of toilet paper,
and what part of the human body does one use toilet paper upon?
So you draw a line from there to the other planets,
and I think by the end, we all learned a little bit about how small we are.
Yes, I agree.
We're a big universe, and we're all just little tiny specks of dust.
I just think that maybe they're eating large amounts of the day.
You know what eats a large amount of the day?
Naps.
You go to sleep, it's light out, you wake up, it's dark.
That's the whole day.
Where did that day go?
I have no idea.
You mean on a weekend?
Yes.
How about this?
I think our goal should be we don't have meetings
unless they're absolutely essential.
No more meetings this week.
Really? You just agree to that?
I can be very surprising.
Do you mind?
I'll tell you what.
You show me one of those crossword puzzles that you've finished,
and I'll be quiet in there.
You guys see this new memo from Jim?
No.
He wants us to make 20 cold calls a day.
You sure?
In addition to all the calls we make to our clients.
I hate making cold calls.
It's like trying to sleep with someone you've only known for a month.
It's impossible.
Jim needs to remember what it's like to be a salesman.
And get a new haircut.
Thank you. I've been saying that for years.
You know what?
Big Tuna is starting to stink a little.
And nobody wants to be around somebody that's stinking.
Oh, no.
What's going on?
I need to fit into my wedding dress.
However, I'm also pregnant.
You know, it's a myth that women have to gain more than nine pounds
in a pregnancy.
Look at these actresses. Some of them lose weight.
Hey, did you guys register for wedding gifts?
We did, but mostly because people expect us to.
We're also accepting other gifts.
Not on the registry.
However much.
It's awkward asking people for money, but we could really use it.
Why doesn't Creighton Barrow let you register for a toaster full of cash?
Perfect. I hate registries.
Oh, good.
My cousin makes the most amazing romantic birdhouse mailboxes.
I know I shouldn't tell you, but you'll still be surprised when you see it.
You're not registered for a birdhouse, are you?
No, we're not registered for a birdhouse.
No, we're not.
Good. Good.
Hey, Jim.
Hey.
I just wanted to congratulate you on your promotion.
Oh, thanks.
Yeah.
And also, I was wondering if you could forget what I said last week
about the fact that I don't really do my job.
Oh, sure. Is that why you've been avoiding me?
Oh, no. I wouldn't do that.
Oh, it was just that I was late today and I took a nap in the bathroom for a while.
All right. I think you're going to want to stop telling me those things.
Gotcha. I will stop telling you things.
Delicious.
All right.
Thanks, Jim.
No problem.
Comparing Jim and Michael is like comparing apples and oranges.
I like apples, but I really, really don't like oranges.
Oranges are annoying and hate me.
When you ask Jim a question, he'll tell you an answer.
When you ask Michael a question, he'll do an imitation of you for five minutes.
Then he'll show you three YouTube videos.
Then he'll try to tickle you.
And if that's not enough, he'll ask you to repeat the question.
Meanwhile, he's wandered off somewhere.
He comes back, looks at the clock, and leaves for the rest of the day.
But he also doesn't care if you come in late.
So I prefer Michael.
Michael is like the fun dad.
And Jim is like the serious mom.
And little Andy is stuck in the middle.
But he loves them both very much.
But if he had to pick one, he would probably pick Jim.
Because Jim gives him his num nums all the time.
Num nums are, of course, my commission checks.
Mm-hmm.
Okay. I thought I saw people missing.
Yeah. Just focus grouping a product expansion idea to these folks.
Got one of each.
Really? Hey, Stanley, what was the last thing Michael said before I came through the door?
Stanley, you don't need to answer that.
Stanley.
If you don't smell this, you're fired.
Okay. Michael, I thought we agreed to not take up people's time with meetings like these.
What do you mean by these people?
Michael, this is a conference room meeting.
Oh, hey, everybody. I think that Jim has gone insane because he thinks that my office is a conference room.
That's not what I meant.
Listen, Jim, no offense, but when push comes to shove, what I want is more important than what you want.
I disagree.
What do you guys think?
Can I go back to my desk now?
Great. Guys, can I just have a moment alone with Michael?
No, no, no, no. You don't need to go anywhere.
Anything that Jim has to say to me, he can say in front of these types of people.
That is not what I said. And also, I am co-manager, meaning you are not the only manager anymore. I am also a co-manager.
That is not what Wallace told us.
That's exactly what Wallace told us.
That is not the way I heard it.
I love rivalries. Michael or Jim. Paris or Nicole. Heidi or Elsie. It's so much fun.
But I guess if I'm really thinking about it and answering your question honestly, I'd have to go with Elsie.
Heidi is a bad friend and her skin is terrible.
It is one thing me giving you the co-manager title. It is another thing you bossing me around.
I'm not bossing you around. I'm trying to do my job, which is sharing your job. So maybe we should just call David Wallace.
No, no, no. No, we will not call David Wallace. I will call David Wallace.
David Wallace is on line two for you guys.
Or David Wallace will call us on line two. Why don't we just...
Hey, David.
You got Jim here.
This is Michael, senior co-manager.
Hey, guys. I'm calling because unfortunately we will not be able to give out cost of living raises this year.
And I know people expect it. However, there just is only a small amount of money for each branch.
So we're leaving it up to the managers to decide how to distribute it.
Got it, Dave. Sounds like your classic big picture decision.
Which will clearly affect the day-to-day well-being of our employees.
It's probably a little of both.
Which is it more of?
Excuse me?
Hey, David. I know that I'm very new at this, but I have a very good perspective on how things work.
Wait, I'm sorry. Michael, are you texting me?
I thought maybe we could talk after this is over.
Look, I need you both to take care of this. This is not going to be a problem, is it?
Nope. Not at all.
No, it will not be.
Nope.
I am on top of it.
Alright. Thanks a lot, David.
Talk to you later. Okay, you didn't let me...
Say goodbye.
Alright. I am looking forward to this.
You don't have to lie.
I hate the fact that we have to do this together.
I think we work much better separately.
When I am irritated and I look at you, I don't see you anymore.
All I can see is how big and gross the pores on your nose are.
Alright. Let's get started.
Hey, why haven't we ever...
We have.
Okay, we can give everyone a tiny raise if we keep it to the 1.5%.
Then everyone is just a little bit mad.
Okay. Let's do it. Let's do it.
Thank you, Sean.
Wait. On the other hand, if any of the sales staff feel underappreciated,
one of them can leave and actually take clients with them, which would hurt everyone.
So maybe we should give it to the sales staff.
Want to go for a walk?
Let's see what that looks like.
I'll get something to eat.
No.
Let's get some pie. You want some pie?
Pie was helping me think.
Where could we go to get something to eat where we have to travel?
It would help us think.
Maybe you could help come up with a solution.
Why don't we just give it to Stanley?
Why is that?
Because he was just looking at me and his eyes said,
Give me the money.
So we just do whatever comes out the top of your head?
There are worse ways of making decisions, Jim.
Here, Stanley, have an 80% increase for absolutely no reason.
No reason? Wow. Racist.
Put it this way.
Would you walk into Cooper's and order the first thing off the menu?
I do. Coconut shrimp.
What?
No, just for such a big catfish fan, I thought.
Well, Cooper's has the best New Orleans-style catfish I've ever had.
Sides?
You can pick two.
Damn it to hell.
You know, there's no easy way to do this.
I say we add 1.5% of the total.
I say we add 1.5% to their paychecks and don't say anything about it.
Do you mean like break in in the middle of the night and change the numbers on payroll?
No, we can do it during the day. It doesn't have to be that dramatic, Jim.
Okay. You know, what would help is a pros and cons list for our options.
Jim, don't take this the wrong way. Are you going to take this the wrong way?
It's hard to tell so far.
You use your brain too much.
I'm sorry, are you advocating that I use it less?
Sometimes the smartest people don't think at all.
You just came up with that.
As I was saying it.
Yeah.
Okay, so for the 1.5% increase, pro, everyone gets a little bit.
Con, you look like a nerd.
Con, no one gets as much as they did last year.
Pro, you get to share your pros and cons list with the other nerds.
Pro, no favoritism.
Con, you unzip your pants and you find that there's a calculator out there.
I've been studying Michael for years and I've condensed what I've learned into this chart.
How Michael spends his time.
As you can see, we have procrastinating and distracting others.
And this tiny sliver here is critical thinking.
I made it bigger so that you could see it.