I'm sorry, you guys have probably noticed my stomach's a little more sensitive lately.
So if you wouldn't mind wearing a little less perfume, and if your lunch is especially pungent,
maybe have it in the break room.
We would really appreciate it.
Pam is constantly throwing up because of the pregnancy.
If she eats something the fetus doesn't like, she is screwed.
It's amazing, a three ounce fetus is calling the shots.
It's so badass.
Phyllis, if you could switch to a different soap just for a month or two, yours is kind of perfumey.
Now this is getting ridiculous.
Oh gee, I'm sorry, I guess I missed the meeting where we all voted for you to get pregnant.
No, I reserve the right to peel my hard boiled eggs at my desk.
All morning I look forward to my afternoon cigars, and I am not stopping for anybody.
I don't think I'm asking for too much.
I guess it's just the end of courtesy in the workplace.
Watching people get sick always makes me sick.
And frankly, so does talking about it, so wow.
Hello world.
This is Pam Beasley, and this is the latest installment of my wedding video diary.
This afternoon my fiance Jim and I are going to Niagara Falls to get married after a half day of work.
Woohoo, I'm getting my marriage on!
Sorry, I'm just really excited.
Okay, so let's see.
Last time I talked about the difficulties of throwing a wedding on a budget, specifically flower arrangements.
My solution? Paper flowers.
I made these using a regular card stock that I found in the warehouse.
Can you believe they were going to just throw that away?
Hey babe.
You gotta let me know when you're doing that.
Well, what do you think? Spent all morning doing it.
It is really special.
Yeah, but aren't you supposed to do that to Arc? No, it's great.
It's just a really important day for me.
Well congrats.
Thanks.
Dunder Mifflin Scranton will be closed today and Friday for a company wedding in Niagara Falls.
So please leave a message and we'll get back to you as soon as possible.
Have a great day.
Believe it or not, Kevin, firecrackers are in the don't column.
So you're going to provide them then?
No, this is a firecracker free wedding.
What the hell?
Come on, you've got to be kidding me.
Okay, all of these things are important to remember,
but the most important thing is that no one say anything about my pregnancy at the wedding.
Absolutely, because not everyone knows and some people might be offended.
Decent people everywhere will get offended.
Well, we're thinking of my grandmother, who we haven't told and who is very old fashioned.
Well, you're lucky to have a grandmother. Some of us have to be our own grandmother.
You know, Angela, you don't have to come to the wedding.
Yes she does, yes she does. We're all going to go and we're going to have a good time.
Ow! He pitched me!
Next time we're all in this room, Jim and I will be married.
We'll see.
Thank you, Dwight.
Goodbye.
See you later.
Bye.
Oh hey, and don't embarrass me when we go to Niagara.
What happens in Niagara stays in Niagara.
Don't, don't, don't. You stole my joke, don't steal my joke.
No, I didn't steal your joke.
Yes, I said that yesterday.
I bet you could say that about anything.
What happens in accounting stays in accounting.
No, no, no, no, please, please. Dwight, that's my joke.
No, but it's so easy. That's what I'm saying. You can say it.
This is what I am talking about. When we leave here and go up to Niagara Falls,
we are representing Dunder Mifflin, everyone.
This is a very important wedding for this branch.
The most important wedding until I get married.
So I want you all on your best behavior. Or so help me God.
So I will see you up there in Niagara Falls.
I stole the guest list from Jim's desk and I search-engineed every female
on both sides of the family.
Get out of here.
Yes.
Oh my God.
For instance, Pam's cousin, Jocelyn Webster.
There's a name.
Two years ago, she was selling a mountain bike.
Oh, well, tell me about Jocelyn. What's she like?
She's really into mountain biking, but not so much lately.
Okay.
She had a couple hundred dollars to spend.
I mean, if she was able to sell her bike, then...
Is that all you have on her?
Well, this is in fact her because it's a very common name.
Okay, you're an idiot.
Pam and Jim's wedding will be the single best pickup destination
in the history of the universe.
Deodorant, toothpaste, check.
Did you bring condoms?
Yes, extra large.
I brought 78 condoms.
Oh, man.
For three days, you can have sex 78 times in three days.
26 times.
How many condoms do you use each time?
Three, right?
One...
One for each.
Okay.
People don't think of me as one of the sharper dressers in the office,
but I'm going to turn that around at this wedding.
I thought, how can I take it to the next level?
The hair.
It's the hair.
Hey, hey, I'm going.
God.
Hey, do one of you guys want to sit up front with me
so I have someone to talk to?
It's like a five-hour drive-ish, you know?
No, this is so much cooler.
We feel like we're in a limo and you're our driver.
Mmm.
Erin?
Oh, no, that wouldn't be fair to leave Kelly alone in back.
Not only is Erin really sweet and cute,
she smells like my mom.
Hey, my aunt told me something neat.
She said, everything with the wedding goes by so fast,
we should try to take mental pictures of the high points.
Oh, wow, that's cool.
Yeah.
Click.
Oh, you blinked.
Damn it, now that's in my brain forever.
Oh.
Lousy picture.
We should have hired a professional to take the mental pictures.
Oh, God, wow.
Oh, I was asleep.
What?
No way.
Those glasses are super dark.
Oh, wow.
Okay.
All right, we need some tunes, I think.
You know what?
I made you a CD.
You did?
Mm-hmm.
That was nice of you.
This is to play when you bring a woman back to your hotel room.
Oh, very thoughtful.
A little mix to set the mood.
Delightful.
Pop that in.
You're going to like this.
Hello.
My name is Dwight Schrute.
If you are listening to this, you are a lucky woman Michael has seduced.
Ah, to be in your shoes.
What's next, you're probably wondering.
Don't be scared of your night in heaven.
Are you serious?
You want me to play that for a woman coming to my room?
Yeah.
Oh, my God.
It's practical.
No, no.
That's not how it works.
Niagara Falls used to be like a spiritual experience to people.
They stayed in tents and it blew their minds.
But it's really kitschy now, which is a lot of fun.
Oh, hello.
We're standing in front of the majestic Statler Falls Hotel.
And I know what you're asking yourself.
How did they get into the number one hotel in the region?
In its price range on TripAdvisor.
Who do they know?
How do they swing that?
They are so fancy.
We hate them.
But secretly, we want to be them.
Stop it.
Stop narrating.
I actually think it's helpful.
I'm not kidding.
On the fourth of...
Come inside.
Helpert.
Ann Beasley.
Tonight we're in two separate rooms,
and then tomorrow night is the honeymoon suite.
Great.
I know, we're pretty excited too.
Can we take a look at the suite now?
Oh, I'm sorry.
Somebody just checked in.
Oh, is there another wedding at the hotel this weekend?
Oh, no.
Just an individual.
Got men there.
Hey, I got the room the night before you guys.
I'll break in the bed.
I don't like that.
I'm going to need the name and cell phone number
of the housekeeper responsible for changing the sheets, please.
Hello.
Reservation for Michael Scott.
One moment, will I check?
The proximity to the falls makes everything smell like a basement.
Mm-hmm.
I'm sorry, sir.
I'm not seeing you in here.
When did you make your reservation?
I don't have a reservation,
but I want a room in the Beasley-Helpert block of rooms.
Oh, okay.
Unfortunately, sir, the block only applies to the rate.
I'm afraid we're all sold out.
Dwight Schrute, I have a reservation.
Confirmation number, Romeo Tango G7745.
Yes, Schrute.
And I had spoken to Teresa about a room with two safes.
Sure, no problem.
Okay.
There's your key, Mr. Schrute.
Dwight, Dwight, Dwight, Dwight.
I need to stay in your room.
No way.
What if I meet someone?
I'm staying in your...
No, Dwight.
I would do the same for you.
You would?
Yes.
Really?
Yes, let's just go.
Wait a second.
No, no, no, no, no, this must be some kind of mistake.
This reservation is under an M. Scott.
Oh.
This must be yours.
Thank God.
Oh, no, now that I don't have a room, can I stay with you?
Um...
No.
You know what?
I would say yes, but you can't, and I'll tell you why.
If I...
If I have a woman up there and things are getting amorous,
she's gonna get turned off if she looks in the bathroom
and she sees you brushing your teeth with butter and clay, okay?
Okay, okay.
Ha-ha-ha!
That was a test, and you have failed,
for this is my room, okay?
You would not share with me.
I don't have a room.
No, you do not.
Okay.
Oh, you must pass the dungeon wisdom test.
It worked!
When Mary was denied a room at the inn, Jesus was born.
When Michael was denied a room at the inn,
we don't know what happens because that story hasn't been told yet.
Mr. and Mrs. Stanley Hudson.
Hey, Stanley, have a favor.
Could I stay in your room?