Vancouver Court Hotel. How may I help you?
Hello Vancouver. This is Michael Scott calling from the United States of America.
I have a reservation in your fair city from February 12th to the 19th, first week of the Olympics.
Well, we're looking forward to having you, so let me just pull up your information here.
Okeydoke.
Is there a unique spelling of your name?
Yes. It is M-I-C-H-A-E-L.
Right. I don't seem to have it, sir.
What?
I love the Winter Olympics. My favorite sport is one involving men with brooms.
And they broom the ice in front of these cylindrical discs that float gently across the ice.
And they smack into one another. And no one really explains the rules, but it's mesmerizing.
And there are no winners and no losers. Only poetry.
And it is called curdling.
I'm not seeing anything under confirmation. Could it be under affirmation? You have thousands of those.
No, we're just trying to look it up right now.
You did get the e-vite to my barbecue.
Michael?
Sir, a lot of people are trying to get last minute reservations at hotels here for the Olympics, but we've been fully booked for months.
Well, I have been booked for three years, so you should have that.
I have always heard that British Columbia is a very nice place, but I'm not getting that from this conversation.
Got it. Confirmation code. X-V-2-R-D-M.
Oh. Here it is.
Oh.
Yeah. Uh-huh.
Thank you.
Seven nights in our Street View economy single.
That's it?
Yeah. We changed systems a while back. I do apologize.
Uh-huh. Okay.
How may I help you, Mr. Scott?
All right. I would like to cancel my reservation, please.
There is a cancellation fee for this, sir.
Okay. Put it on my card.
Today, Joe Bennett, the CEO from Sabre, is coming to see us here for the first time.
She bought us sight unseen, like a mail-order bride, so she's going to be kind of nervous.
So she's got to be kind of nervous.
I mean, are we ugly?
Are we smart?
Are we cool?
Are we too cool?
Do we speak English?
Why, hello.
This is Michael Scott, co-regional manager
of this branch.
Pleasure to meet you, Miss Bennett.
That's Mrs. Bennett, sweetheart.
My husband and I are divorced, but I kept the Mrs.
Just to piss off the new wife.
Well, let's take a gander around this place.
These sure are pretty dogs.
They love a good garage.
Yeah, they sure do.
You should take that as a compliment.
Oh, I do.
Hello.
Do you always stay seated when a lady enters the room?
I am treating you the same as a man for whom I would also not
stand, unless it was the president or Judge Judy.
I like that.
This is accounting.
Uh-huh.
Hi.
Good looking group.
Over here is Meredith Palmer, Creed Bratton.
Another couple of heartbreakers.
Who's this tall rink of sun tea?
That is Jim Halpert.
He is the co-regional manager of this office.
I thought this guy was the manager.
Oh, he is.
He's the co-manager there.
That's the other co-manager.
Two guys doing one job?
We got to do something about that.
Got some Valentine's cards for my coworkers and my bro workers.
No.
What?
No candy?
Valentine's Day, right around the corner.
Erin and I have been on zero dates.
So I got her a Valentine's Day card.
But I didn't want to seem too eager,
so I got cards for everyone in the whole office
to kind of dilute it a little bit.
Look alive.
Ow!
She used to give me a paper cut on my throat.
Yeah, I have this thing about men cutting or threatening
to cut my throat.
Don't try to cut my throat.
You know, I get why you guys want to share a job.
You look real good standing there next to each other.
I mean it.
I mean, look, you're tall and thin,
and you're solid and dark.
Have a seat.
All right.
So it is OK to keep doing the co-manager thing then?
No, that's ridiculous.
OK.
I don't know how things work in Florida,
which from your description sounds
like a colorful lawless swamp.
But here, it takes two men to do one job,
where in Florida, it might take one very strong woman
to do such a job.
Whoa.
I'll take over.
What we're doing here, Michael handles more of the big picture
stuff.
And I handle more of the day-to-day stuff.
So together.
I think I understand.
Each of you is doing half a job.
Sometimes I can hardly handle that.
Now this is knucklehead talk.
I'm not going to bite it.
You know, you can't give me gravy
and tell me it's jelly because gravy ain't sweet, is it, Jim?
Oh, thanks.
Michael?
Forget the question.
I think one of you should return to sales,
and the other one will be manager.
I humbly accept the management position.
Why would you just automatically get it?
Because, well, Jim, where I'm from,
there are two types of folk, those who ain't,
and those who are knee-high on a grasshopper.
Which type ain't you ain't?
Y'all come back now.
Do you even know what that means?
Yes.
Well, I'm going to let this marinate so you can go.
You can go on.
Yep.
All right.
Shoot.
I'm Jolene Bennett, Joe for short.
I'm a breast cancer survivor, close personal friends
with Nancy Pelosi and Truman Capote,
and I slept with three of the same guys.
When I was a little girl, I was terrified to fly,
and now I have my own pilot's license.
I am CEO of Sabre International, and I sell the best damn
printers and all in one machine Korea can make.
Pleased to meet you.
Whoa, traffic jam.
Uh-oh, traffic jam on Route 3.
Beep, beep.
20 people dead in a pile up.
There's blood everywhere.
I got you a Valentine's card.
You did?
Yeah.
Oh, a bird and a dog.
Yeah, well, it's Snoopy and Woodstock.
You named them?
Charles Schultz did.
I thought it was relevant because I got you all those
birds for Christmas, remember?
Yeah, I do remember.
Oh, they love each other.
Oh, look at that.
They sure do.
I hadn't noticed.
Smells really good, too.
Yeah, it's Roger Petter for men.
I sprayed some in there.
Andy, whoa.
Thank you very much.
It's got fair bones in it.
Hey.
Hi.
Just choosing seats, not getting married.
Chop, chop, little onion.
Joe, there's books in my chair.
That's right, darling.
Now you're the proud new owner of a Sabre handbook
and my autobiography.
Why is it called Take a Good Look?
I was 26 years old, working at Kodak.
It was my first job after Vanderbilt.
It was very exciting.
I took it very seriously.
But I wasn't afforded the same amount of respect
that the rest of the board enjoyed.
One day, I'd headed up to here.
And I strode into the boardroom, wearing nothing
but a pair of spiked heels, a lace push-up bra,
and matching lace panties.
And I took my seat.
And I looked around at all of them.
And I said, gentlemen, if this is all you see,
then take a good look.
As a male manager, I would have never done that to you.
I am nothing if not not sexist.
That's setting the bar a little low, isn't it?
The only time I set the bar low is for limbo.
I can see it on your faces.
I mean, what's going on now?
I mean, who owns Dunder Mifflin, right?
I mean, Sabre?
What's that?
Some company we never heard of from down in Tallahassee?
Where is that?
Near Mars?
No, we know.
Texas?
Now, Dunder Mifflin has an arms reach
and all these small businesses all over the Northeast.
And now we're going to take that arm
and we're going to start selling printers.
I could manage my way around that.
They're the easiest to use printers in the market.
I will try to manage my excitement.
It seems like Joe feels that there might be one too
many managers around here.
And Michael's response seems to be to use the word
manage as often as possible.
I have been saying the word manager a lot.
So whenever Joe thinks manager, she thinks of me.
Camel cigarettes did the same thing with Joe Camel
by making him look like a penis.
I can't even go near a cigarette now
without thinking of a penis and vice versa.
I think that's it.
So we're all good.
Thanks, y'all.
When I was a kid, I used to try to work in ice cream
into every conversation I had with my mother
so she would get me ice cream.
And then one day she said, Michael,
if you don't stop saying ice cream, I am going to kill you.
And then she felt so bad that she went out
and got me ice cream.
So it's a pretty effective strategy.
Oh my God.
I guess Andy likes me.
I never thought of him in that way.
But I guess in most romantic comedies,
the guy you're supposed to be with
is the one that you never thought of in that way.
You might have even thought he was annoying
or possibly homosexual.
So check this out.
According to the handbook,
you could make more money as a salesman than as a manager.
They have all these incentive programs.
I ran your numbers from last year.
This is way more than I make now.
I don't think I'm gonna miss being manager.
You know, some people say they're not in it for the money.
Well, with all due respect to this job,
I think I'm definitely in it for the money.
And quite honestly, the women.
Hey, got a second?
Sure.
All right.
What are you here to tell me
that you think I would be a better manager
and that you are sorry for being such a jerk?