Attention, everyone! Jim and I, on behalf of the party planning committee, have it announced
— Too loud. Too loud. Too loud.
— but effective. Look. On behalf of Jim and I, Merry Christmas.
Merry Christmas, Jim.
Merry Christmas. Good. My diabolical plot is on hold for Christmas. My heart just melts
with the sound of children singing.
Not really. I'm just tired. The days are short. I don't know. Maybe I'm depressed.
It is time to unveil the tree.
Rockefeller Center.
Yeah.
I've actually been to Rock Center and this is nothing like that.
This is all we have.
Ugh.
No, it's not ugh. It is office camaraderie.
It is warm feelings.
Why don't we talk more about it instead of doing it?
Thirty. Twenty-nine. Twenty-eight.
Why would you start so high?
Twenty-seven.
Three. Twenty-six.
Twenty-six.
One.
Jim.
Oh. You didn't decorate it.
No.
Exactly.
We didn't because we think it would be better to do it together.
Everyone, why would you wrap it in a sheet if you're not covering anything up?
Is it fake?
Pam.
Yes. We are unveiling an artificial tree that will never die.
Yes.
Like the spirit of Christmas.
We're supposed to applaud you for taking a giant diabolical fake tree.
This was a successful unveiling. Go back to work.
Merry Christmas.
Hello. Sorry, guys. Sorry, guys.
I'm not sure I've earned the right to make announcements yet,
but whoever is giving me the 12 days of Christmas as my Secret Santa, please stop.
I can't take it anymore.
My cat killed a turtle dove.
The French hens have started pulling out my hair to make a nest.
Please stop.
What psycho would send that as a gift?
I begged Dwight and Jim to give me Erin for Secret Santa,
and I decided to give Erin the 12 days of Christmas.
Both die, guys.
Is it my fault that the first eight days is basically 30 birds?
Ho, ho, ho. Merry Christmas, boys and girls. It's me, Santa Claus.
Hey, Santa.
They finally let you do it.
Congrats, Phil.
It's so edgy.
I've been wanting to be Santa for years.
I believe I have the right temperament and the figure to do the job well.
I slipped a note to Jim 11 weeks ago, and he said I could do it.
It's been a long journey, but I'm Santa Claus.
So, Santa, what can we expect from this party?
It's going to be a very jolly time if you've been good.
What if you've been bad?
Oh, then nothing but a lump of coal for you.
What if you've been really, really bad, more evil and strictly wrong?
Hey, Creed, we covered it. Lump of coal.
Yeah.
For the past several weeks, my secret Santa has been giving me pieces of a machine that I've been attempting to assemble.
I'm suspicious of this because I had the exact same idea for catching Osama Bin Laden.
I would simply send him a different piece each day.
He would assemble it to find himself in jail.
You know, Oscar, every time I make this lasagna, people ask me if it's a family recipe.
But really, I just get the recipe from the box.
That's funny.
Is it funny? I thought it was more interesting than funny.
I think my water just broke.
That's too funny.
Oscar and the warehouse guy.
Go, Oscar!
Go, gay warehouse guy!
Here's Santa!
Hey, little girl, what would you like for Christmas?
Ooh, you have been a very naughty girl, I see.
Michael, we already have a Santa. Phyllis.
What the hell is going on?
Phyllis, Jim, Phyllis and Santa.
Yeah.
Phyllis.
Yeah, I told her a long time ago she could do it.
Take it back. That is absurd.
No, I can't do that.
No, Jim, come on!
I think she's doing a good job.
Lately there have been serious rumors that our company is going bankrupt.
So David Wallace asked me to keep morale high.
So I asked around about what people wanted with Christmas.
And I told them to get creative.
And they didn't really get creative exactly.
Secret Santa, karaoke, food.
Kind of the usual thing that we do here, which is great.
And people usually argue about food, so I told everybody to bring their favorites.
I made an organized sign-up sheet for karaoke so that there was no fighting.
And no crying.
I'm doing a good job, I think.
Because this year I care.
It's weird.
I know.
It's insane! A woman Santa? Where does it stop?
No! Jim, this may be the last Christmas that we have here.
Doesn't it make you a tiny bit anxious?
Me not playing Santa? Come on!
I'm not going to go tell Phyllis that she can't be Santa.
Fine. Then do it anonymously. Ransom note style.
You can... You know what?
I have a bunch of letters cut out of magazines in my desk. You can use those.
If this were Russia, yeah, sure.
Everybody would go to one Santa.
And there would be a line around the block.
And once you sat on her lap and she asked you what you wanted, you would say probably,
Freedom. At which point the KGB would arrest you and send you to Siberia.
It's a good thing Russia doesn't exist anymore.
Name?
Kelly.
And what would you like for Christmas?
I would like the photographer, please, Santa.
Good.
So far, people really seem to like the party this year.
We took some chances and it's working out.
Ho, ho, ho! Ho, ho, ho!
Why pay more to sit next to old tranny claws over there when you can sit on my lap?
Phyllis is only pretending to be a man.
I'm the real thing.
Sit down on my lap and there will be no doubt.
Okay.
No, it's not. It's not, like, penis-wise.
Hello, little boy. What's your name?
Michael, it's me, Kevin.
Phyllis says I'm too big for her lap.
Oh, I am so sorry that Phyllis hates you and hates your body.
But Santa remembers a reindeer that was just a tiny bit different as well.
When can I sit on your lap?
Right now! Come on over here, big boy!
There we go.
Oh, my God.
That's really comfortable.
Oh.
What was it like for Christmas, little boy?
I don't know. I didn't know you were going to ask me that.
Well, why did you think it was going to happen?
I didn't know.
Nobody's ever let me sit on their lap before.
All right, just say some toys, please.
Can you give me some choices?
Because I really don't want to mess up on this list.
Kevin, come on.
What about if I tell you the things I don't want?
Okay. Get off. Get off.
Oh, God.
I didn't even get to tell you what I wanted.
Okay, you know what you get?
You get 1,000 helium balloons attached to you,
so Santa doesn't have to go through this again.
Oh, awesome.
Put the sleeve.