Yeah, you wanted to see me?
Yes, Oscar, come on in.
Close the door, if you would.
Thank you. Thanks so much for talking to me.
Yeah, sure.
I'm going in for a procedure today.
Is everything okay?
Yeah, it's routine. I'm just a little bit scared.
I'm sure everything will be fine.
What's the procedure, if you don't mind me asking?
It is a colonoscopy.
Okay.
In your experience, what should I be expecting
in terms of sensation or emotions?
Is there anything I can do to make it more pleasurable
for me or for Dr. Chandri?
Oh, my God.
My main concern is should I have a safe word?
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
So, Michael...
Bill Simon from Buffalo.
Thank you.
Arrow Medical Supplies in West Seneca.
Thanks.
And Angela's still waiting for you to approve
You know what?
If you're going to keep coming in here with work
that I need to do, I'm going to need a new monitor.
It's not working.
Hey, Michael.
Yes?
I do want the Buffalo clients under new accounts
to be existing.
I've been doing some of both.
Everybody wants a piece of me.
So, Michael, how are you handling
the Buffalo transition on your end?
Great. On my end.
How about your end?
Well, I think we're on the same end, Michael.
Then why did you say your end?
Let me be more specific.
How are you personally handling
the increase in responsibility?
Well, I will tell you, David.
I'm either doing the work or I'm not.
So, are you doing the work?
Maria didn't weep.
Michael, if you need us to help you with anything...
You just let me know, okay?
I'm good.
I've got a lot of balls in the air.
If I wanted to be in the business of giving people bad news,
I would have become a coroner or an anchorman.
But I got into this industry
because I wanted to give people good news.
Like, your paper is on its way.
Yes, we have that in stock.
It's lunchtime.
So, Michael, you think you can get me a rundown
on the Buffalo clients by Monday?
You know what? I'll do you one better. Sunday. Sunday night.
Okay. I will get it Monday.
Hold on, big guy.
I'm gonna put it in the mail Sunday night. You'll get it Wednesday.
Okay. Jim, you want to hit the conference room?
Sure.
Okay. Good luck.
All right. This thing. I remember now.
What's this about?
Oh, this is just me and David, if that's okay.
It's okay. He's gonna want me in.
No. It's okay, Michael. We got it.
Really? Yeah.
All right. Do you mind if I sit this out?
I have so much work to do,
I feel like I'm gonna blow my brains out.
Okay. Go.
I'm gonna go.
Am I worried that Jim and David are having a meeting without me?
No. Because we are the three amigos.
And once in a while, one of the amigos will go off to the bathroom
while the other two have a secret meeting.
Hey, let me escort you to your desk.
It's just three or four steps, but thank you. Thank you.
You and Jim are close, huh?
Yeah, I think the pregnancy really brought us together.
Hey. What do you think he and David are talking about?
What are you...
Um, I don't know.
Well, you said good luck to Jim as you walked in.
Did I? Doesn't sound like me. Not very superstitious.
If you're lying to me right now, Pam,
your baby is gonna come out a liar.
That's how it works.
They inherit things through the breast milk.
Please don't talk about my breast milk.
I just don't want you to lie to me.