The fundamentals of business.
Mental is a part of the word.
I have underlined it.
Because you're mental, if you don't have a good time, you have to enjoy it.
Well, the fun is in it.
Fundamental.
Oh, right.
Get out.
I know, I know.
Yes, so it all starts with a handshake.
But you can't just go right to the selling.
You need small talk.
What topics can you use for small talk?
Golf, stock market, Dave Matthews.
Yes, what else?
Small things, peas, ball bearings, dimes.
No.
The weekend.
Yeah, that's good.
Come on out.
Meredith, come up here.
Let's do a little something.
So Meredith and I have just started conversing, and I will say, so Meredith, how was your
weekend?
What did you do?
Well, I caught my son taking a dump on the upper part of the toilet.
He calls it an upper decker.
Okay, okay.
God.
Well, you people don't know about business I could fill a book with.
Then do it.
What?
Write a book.
The Fundamentals of Business by Michael Scott.
Over one billion sold.
More than the Bible.
I'm not surprised.
Chapter one.
The Business Man.
Very good for breakfast.
It's really on the brink of going rotten.
Gotta wolf it down.
Man, doesn't it seem like Jim and Pam have been gone forever?
Who gives a crap?
I'm just saying, it's great that she has so much time off.
It's unusual.
Are you trying to get her in trouble?
Not at all.
She totally deserves time off for her honeymoon, and then I guess for her maternity leave after
that.
Teacher, teacher, Pam hasn't been in class this week.
Backstabbing a pregnant woman.
No, I'm just making conversation.
We can talk about anything.
Meredith, I saw your son's tag on the bridge.
Wow, he's so great with a spray can.
Look, you're never gonna be Pam.
We're always gonna like her more.
Deal with it.
Oh, Mr. Grotti, this is Michael Scott.
He's the person you should talk to.
Oh, hi.
I'm sorry.
Just a sec.
Karen, you're supposed to be the gatekeeper.
Do you have any idea how valuable my time is?
And your schedule just says nine till noon is creative space.
I thought this could be part of that.
Do you know how creative space works?
Okay, fine.
Just cancel my afternoon.
You don't have anything in the afternoon.
It just says free play.
Push free play till tomorrow morning.
Hi.
Sorry.
Crazy day.
You're seeing how the sausage gets made.
Come in the conference room and I will show you a finished sausage.
As a manager of business, you've got a lot of pride.
But you also got a lot of responsibility.
Yep.
You're one greater, perhaps, than the need to be sure
that your small or large business is secure
in the event of a covered loss.
Okay.
There is nothing more insulting to a great salesman
than having to listen to a bad salesman.
It's like a great basketball player
having to listen to a bad basketball player.
Phone ringing
Jim's gone on his honeymoon.
So I started borrowing his office to fart in.
Then one day I came in and I just stayed.
Because this place is awesome.
It feels like home now.
Even better than my home.
My home sucks.
What do you think?
I think you're right.
Definitely looks suspicious.
And his southern Italian heritage raises some flags.
God forbid you should have a fire in the warehouse.
Oh, yep. Yeah.