Oh, yeah, I got a big box. Yes, I do.
I got a big box. How about you?
I got a big box. Yes, I do.
I think you don't know what you're saying.
It is from Sabre, our new owner,
and it is to Sabre us.
I wonder what's inside.
Scissor me.
Dunder Mifflin was recently bought
by an electronics company named Sabre.
They stepped in at the 11th hour.
And they saved our asses.
Although David Wallace said
that we were the one branch
that was actually working right,
so we probably could have saved our own asses.
We didn't need them touching our asses.
Ow! Ow! Ow!
Wow! Awesome!
For accounting, a brand-new print-off.
And for the sales staff,
a new fax machine.
This cord has Creed written all over it.
And whoever would like a brand-new scanner
can come visit it in my office.
Thank you. Here we go.
Oh! Oh!
Wow! Cool. What next?
Uh, who's Gabe?
This note says to put the box aside
for a Gabe Lewis who's coming tomorrow.
Okay, everybody, listen up.
I have some bad news.
Due to circumstances beyond my control,
impulsivity and inattention to detail...
Hey, hey.
I have opened a box which should not have been opened...
Terrible mistake.
...and distributed things
which should not have been distributed.
Undistributable.
Well, maybe we can put the box back together.
Impossible. He opened it like an ape.
I think we can do it.
Yeah. Yeah.
Hmm.
Did we try printer first?
Shredder at an angle? Yeah.
Fax cable, then the scanner upside down?
Yes.