Not again.
Bow down before Recyclops!
Five years ago, corporate said we had to start a recycling program for Earth Day.
So Dwight took the lead on that and introduced us to a very close friend of his named Recyclops.
Happy Earth Day everyone. I'm Recyclops.
Did you know that an old milk carton can be sawed in half and used as a planter?
The next year, he really stepped things up.
Who has put a number seven plastic in a number four bin?
A year after that, Recyclops really began to take shape.
Recyclops will drown you in your overwatered lawns.
Then tragedy struck Recyclops when his fictional planet was attacked by some other fictitious thing.
I can't remember.
Recyclops will have his revenge!
I think this was also the year that he renounced Earth Day and vowed to destroy the planet he once loved.
Oh my god you guys! Look it's Recyclops!
Recyclops destroy!
Oh it's the day of Recyclops Day?
Yes.
I thought you were killed by polluticorn or something.
Polluticorn wishes!
That's aerosol spray! It's terrible for the environment!
Humans are terrible for the environment!
The thing I like most about Recyclops is that he's creating a different world for our child.
A world where you truly can be anything you want.
God bless you Recyclops and your cold robot heart.
Okay, okay, how about this?
That's great.
I want it to be better than great Pam.
How about I remain seated and I just do a little bit of a nod?
Sort of a humble thing?
Sure.
Nope, then my favorite part is the
I'm going to go to New York to the shareholders meeting and sit up on the stage with the board of directors.
Alan Brand is the CEO of the company, if title is important to you, has personally invited
me to go to New York to the shareholders meeting and sit up on the stage with the board of directors.
And at some point they are going to introduce me as the most successful branch manager that they have.
And then Michael Scott turns and waves the crowd and the crowd goes wild.
Ladies and gentlemen from Scranton, Pennsylvania, please welcome Michael the Machine Scott.
Don't do the twirl.
Lose the twirl.
Twirl sucks.
Michael, I hated the twirl.
Hate the twirl!
Okay, obviously I'm not going to do the twirl.
I'm going to do the twirl.
I only did it because I nailed the wave.
Yeah, good.
Don't do it.
I'm not going to do the twirl, alright?
It's not even a twirl.
It's a spin.
I might do the spin.
The long-term problem is bad investments that they need to dump.
The short-term problem is the company has no cash and there's nowhere to get it.
Okay, Oscar, I don't need the whole enchilada, just bullet points.
Those are the bullet points.
Well, could you condense it, please?
That's as simple as I can make it.
Michael, the limo's here for you.
It's not a limo, it's a town car.
Town cars are actually better, though.
Better torque, better handling.
He said limousine, so...
Check it out, guys.
There's a limo down here.
Michael, look.
Oh, man.
They said a limo.
Town cars suck.
Town car is something that a company sends when they're in trouble.
A limousine is something that a company sends when they have cause for celebration.
And in this case...