I'm getting married in eight hours.
Everyone else is too drunk.
Just don't let me die here.
Hey hey where are you?
Can you take Andy to the hospital?
What?
He tore his scrotum dancing.
He is in my room icing his balls.
What?
Please stop saying what.
Can you take him?
Look I would so take him in any other circumstance but I'm pretty certain I'm completely wasted.
Your brothers took you out drinking.
Uh.
Is that Pam?
Hey have her come out.
Have her come out.
It'll be like Coyote Ugly.
That's Michael.
You're out with Michael?
And Dwight.
Heyo.
Pam it just happened.
Okay fine.
I'll take him.
I love you.
Okay guys I gotta go.
Are you pushing me off the phone?
No.
Let's talk for a long time.
Goodbye.
Oh a bunch of us decided to go over the border to Canada for one quick drink.
So I'm in a car with Michael and Dwight.
When we get to the border Dwight refuses to relinquish his side arm so 40 minutes later
here we are.
It's after midnight.
You married?
He's married.
Oh that's not how that works.
Oh my god.
You're not going to be able to talk back?
I love Pam to answer that.
She'll be sitting at home saying Jim take the baby to the zoo because I want to sit
at home and eat bonbons and clip my toenails.
Jim hey why don't you braid my hair?
I want to watch TV.
You sound like Kermit.
Are you sure this is the right way?
Nope.
I like you have never been here before.
Well at least slow down a little bit because every little bump in the road is major pain
on my scrotum.
Look I'm not the one who asked you to do a split when you've never done one before.
No I was trying to liven things up a little bit okay.
I was kind of doing your job so.
My job?
My job is to get married in the morning.
That's my job.
Well it's also to make sure we have a great time at your stupid wedding so.
Ow.
I actually am really jealous of the fact that you are marrying anyone.
I would marry anyone.
Oh man you should have to have property at least as fertile as my farm.
I'd marry you.
You want to get married?
Let's go.
Let's go get married.
Alright.
I don't have to.
I spent the night with the bride the night before the wedding.
Oh yeah.
She stepped on my hand on her way to the bathroom.
Andy did I dream that you were crying through the night?
No.
No that was real.
Why don't you take a picture.
It will last longer.
God.
I got a little privacy.
Good morning.
How can I help you?
I left a pair of dress shoes in a bag outside my door last night to be cleaned and polished.
But they haven't been returned yet.
You must be Mr. Malone.
One moment please.
Thank you.
Sir.
Mr. Malone.
Your shoes are gone.
They were stolen?
No.
Destroyed.
What?
When the bag was opened by our shoeshine the smell overcame him.
I too smelled them and made the choice that they must be thrown away.
Incinerated actually.
But that was my only pair of shoes.
It became a safety issue sir.
Well, damn it.
I can offer you a complimentary breakfast.
Okay.
You have everything?
Cell phone?
Charger?
Yeah.
So you sure you don't want breakfast?
It's the most important meal of the day.
It really is.
I'm not hungry.
I ate a whole bunch of sunflower seeds after you went to sleep.
And besides, I wouldn't want to take you away from Pam on the morning of her wedding.
She needs you Isabel.
That's really sweet Dwight.
So I'll see you at the wedding.
You know it.
Okay.
Okay, get out of here.
Bye.
Okay.
Hey, good morning.
It's about damn time.
I haven't gone to the bathroom in a day and a half.
Oh my God Dwight.
This room was a pit.
Really?
Hadn't noticed.
Too busy knocking boots.
Who can you eat like that?
I'm ravenous after a night of lovemaking.
You?
Yeah, I'm hungry but I'm not going to make a pig out of myself.
Hey, what was she like?
She was cute.
You know, she was hot.
She was very hot.
She made love like a tiger.
Right side or groom side?
Or townie?
She was from Europe.
No kidding.
Uh huh.
I know.
I bet she had hairy armpits.
No.
Isabel was nice but I hope she doesn't think this is going anywhere.
Wait a second.
You're not into her?
Are you kidding me?
No.
She's Pam's best friend.
You guys could double date.
Swap maybe.
Oh please, put a gun in my mouth.
No, you're crazy.
Look, she's a dental hygienist from Carbondale and she makes love like one.
She's a bumpkin pass.
She's...
Okay.
Do you know how hard it is to be a hygienist?
You have to take x-rays.
You have to scrape the plaque off of people's teeth.
You have to tell kids when to spit and make sure that they're not scared when the dentist comes in.
It...
You should ask her out.
I already have my European girlfriend.
If your head hits me in the face one more time...
It's funny, your wife loved this hat the last time she saw it.
Oh my god.
Oh.
Oscar.
Angela.
Are you in a lot of pain?
Oh, because of last night?
No way.
Reports have been exaggerated.
Lettings make me very emotional.
I just have that side to me.
People say you cry all the time.
Well, that's...
That...
Crotch injuries are the worst.
You don't need to tell me.
I wasn't telling you.
There's still something there.
Excuse me?
They didn't get torn off?
No, they didn't.
Nothing got torn off.
Who told you that?
I may have told some people that.
I'm nervous.
I'm about to get married.
If you want to sit on this...
I was thinking the wood might be too hard on your damaged penis.
Make it softer.
That's my scrotum.
And it was.
Thank you.
Sure.
Oh, here we go.
They ask for cash, but you know, I give them cash every week.
So, how much cash does a person need?
I have taken it upon myself to do something a little more special.
I have painted a portrait of the two of them from memory.
And I have another one of them in the nude.
But that one is for me.
I got them a set of turtle boiling pots, shell hammer, and bibs.
Oh, thank you, guys.
Thank you, guys, so much.
I am hurting.
Oh, Dad, you wore the good kilt.
Yeah.
It's a bro one for you.
Uh-uh.
But it's okay.
You're so happy right now.
Oh, Dad.
Big day.
Big day. Big day.
Had a big night.
Is it still there?
Is it zipping over your belly?
Don't squish the baby.
Thank you, weirdo.
Everybody's seen Christie's stupid blonde extensions.
It's like they were made from a plastic broom.
Okay, here I come.
Oh, darn.
You look beautiful.
Thanks, Mom.
I hope he deserves you.
He does.
Are you sure?
Remember, you don't have to do this.
You don't.
Mom, you're totally projecting you being a drag.
Yes.
Thank you, Mom.
Hey, I'm gonna go outside and talk to Dwight.
Okay, great.
Yeah, I'll see you in a second.
Wait, what?
Oh!
Oh, no.
Hey.
Can you come here, please?
Is this allowed?
No, no, but I'm allowing it.
Just come here.
You are so lucky to have a cousin like Jim Halpert.
I wish I had a cousin as cool as Jim Halpert.
I have Mo's, who's way cooler than Jim.
You just tell girls what they want to hear.
That was an intelligent comment.
Hello, stranger.
How do I look?
Oh, fine.
Isabelle, nice to see you.
What do you want?
Uh, nothing.
Anymore.
So, uh, tell me again the difference between filings
and filings' basements.
Hey, hey, he's not sitting with me either.
What were you sitting?
You didn't need a seat, buddy?
I'm standing. I'm a bird to me.
Well, I wish I was a grasshopper.
Where am I gonna go?
Hey.
Wow.
You look...
Terrible.
So beautiful.
Hey.
My veil tour.
I knew when we were getting married
and I'm five months pregnant
that I'm not gonna be able to wear the dress that I always wanted
or high heels.
Hey, you look just as I imagine you.
Damn, you're so pretty.
Yeah.
Thank you.
And who cares?
It's a stupid veil, right?
No, this is the one thing I was supposed to be able to control
was this veil.
There. Now we're even.