They're back!
Oh yeah!
Jim and Pam!
How was Puerto Rico? Was it so romantic?
It was.
It really was.
I'm so happy for you.
Puerto Rico was awesome!
Oh my gosh, the honeymoon was great.
We met this other couple at the resort, Frank and Benny.
We hung out with them a lot.
Frank and Bane!
Always makes me laugh.
Is there someone there?
Who's there?
I hear voices. Is somebody there?
Yeah!
Is someone here?
I can't see you because I'm blind.
It's Jim and Pam, Michael.
It is?
They're back?
Oh! Oh!
Oh, Pam!
Nope.
Oh, Jim!
Hi, Michael.
Oh, I haven't seen you since my accident that I had when I fell...
I fell into the pool of acid, eyes first.
Blind guy.
Blind guy, McSqueezy.
How do I describe it?
It is a character I've been workshopping whose lack of vision gets him into all sorts of trouble.
The women in my improv class absolutely hate him.
So, what'd you bring us?
Some candy.
What else?
That's it.
Oh, because you spent so much on the wedding.
It's good to be home.
This conversation has two items on the agenda.
Did we have a conversation scheduled?
Number one, do not leave your things on my desk.
It's not some kind of personal pen receptacle for you.
I don't care how high they promote you.
Which brings me to item number two.
I never formally congratulated you on your promotion, so I'd just like to say...
Congratulations.
I'd just like to say...
Wow, that's really thoughtful of you, Dwight. Thank you.
You're welcome.
I inserted a listening device into the belly of the mallard.
Now I can observe Jim, trap Jim, and destroy Jim.
Just like in the Bavarian fairy tale.
Only this time, the mallard skins the toad alive.
And of course, in this version, you lose the whole veiled critique of the Kaiser thing.
I'm sorry to have been bugging you all these years.
It's a real handsome duck.
Mallard. Okay, I'll get out of your hair.
Hey.
We brought back some Puerto Rican candy.
Cocoleche. That's my favorite.
Awesome. I'll leave it up here so everyone can enjoy it.
Oh, let me just check with Michael first.
I think it'll be okay.
I think it will too, but I'll just check with him though.
Great.
Oops. Sorry. Oops.
I have recently taken a lover.
Well, that's great.
Congratulations. Who's the lucky lady?
Pam's mom.
What?
Pam's mom, Helene. Remember from your wedding?
You're messing with me.
About what?
You did not have sex with Pam's mom.
Oh, big time.
What kind of car does she drive?
She drives a green camera.
And the seats go all the way down. All the way down.
Oh my God. Oh my God.
What?
Okay, never tell Pam. And then secondly.
Good. A pact. A pact.
Although I may have to break it tonight when Helene and I tell Pam over dinner.
You all right?
Oh my God.
Hey, Jim.
Not now, Toby. My God.
Oh Jesus.
Get the hell out of here, idiot.
What can I do?
Okay, as far as dinner tonight, cancel that.
And please, for both of our sakes, never, ever, ever see her again.
I think you're underestimating Pam.
I think more than anything she wants me to be happy.
No. Not more than anything.
Okay. I have a good thing with the mom.
Don't call her the mom.
She's right on my way home from work.
Then take a different way home, man.
All right. I'll take surface streets.
The last thing in the world I would want to do is upset Pam.
Okay. So we're good.
Yeah.
Can you change my dinner reservations from four people to two?
Sure.
Oh, is it okay if I put out some candy that Pam brought back from Puerto Rico?
Sure. Thanks for asking.
Pam, we're all set.
Yum.
Fried cut beans.
So, what did we decide for Michael?
The bottle of rum or the seashell alarm clock?
You know what? Can I have the weekend to decide?
Bottle of rum it is.
All right. Shall we?
You know what? I am really slammed trying to catch up on everything here.
And I know that Michael's slammed too.
So maybe we should do this when things are a little less crazy.
Come on. It'll take two seconds.
Now, it...
Oh, wow.
That is amazing. I feel like a real Puerto Rican.
Michael, you're all set at Botticelli's. I changed the reservation to two people.
Erin, look.
Fun.
Yeah.
Wow. Botticelli's, that sounds like a special occasion.
Yeah. No, it's nobody.
I don't know. I think Michael has a date.
No.
I think you have a date.
I don't. I don't.
Come on.
I think we should just drop it because obviously he doesn't want to talk about it.
I don't deserve this, guys.
Yes, you do.
No, I don't.
Just take the parrot.
Okay. Back to the old grind.
I was probably going to break up with her anyway.
Oh.
Don't.
That's too bad.
Pam, it is very complicated. There are a lot of moving parts here.
Sounds complicated.
Yeah, but I mean, if you really like this person, then you should see where it goes.
You want me to be happy?
Of course.
Part of the problem is she is the mother of a close friend of mine.
Oh.
More than a friend. A co-worker.
Oh. Gossip. Who is it?
Who is it?
Who is it, Michael?
Who?
It's okay.
No, no, no, no.
No. Oh my God! Oh my God!
No!
That could have gone one of two ways, but I never expected her to get upset.
I know exactly how Pam is feeling right now.
I've dated a lot of women whose children absolutely hated me, but I know that...
Rock!
She's throwing up.
You seem tense.
Hey, you want me to give you the chills?
Okay.
There's an egg on your head and the yolk is running down.
The yolk is running down.
There's a knife in your back and the blood is gushing down.
Sleeping with Pam's mom. Sometimes dinner.
The blood is gushing down. The blood is gushing down.
You know, I really would have appreciated a heads up that you were into dating mothers.
I would have introduced you to mine.
How could you do this to me? He's my boss!
How many times have I complained about him to you?
No, I am not being dramatic. You are being crazy!
Who wants a hot chocolate?
Thank you.
Oh, so Dwight gave me this wooden mallard as a gift.
I found a recording device in it.
Yes. So, I think if I play it just right, I can get Dwight to live out the plot of National Treasure.
You need to be more upset about this. She's your mother too now.
Your mother is sleeping with Michael Scott.
Of course I'm pissed. Michael stupid Scott is dating my mother.
But you know what? This is an office.
And because Michael isn't capable of it, it looks like I have to be the adult.
Annie, can I talk to you for a second?
Sure thing. Tune in to boss.
How may I be of service to you?
I am going to need your advice.
I was thinking of getting this opera for Dwight's birthday. What do you think?
This aria is a joke.
Really?
What are you thinking?
I was going to go with this one.
If you respect him at all, you will get him something better.
The bar door. Who was that?
I know, right? He's talking about it there.
Trust me, it would only make you mad.
I will die of grief.
Due to a certain recent incident, corporate has asked all the branches to come up with ideas as to how we can better communicate with our communities.
Is this because of the 60 minutes segment about working conditions in our Peruvian paper mills?
That was a hit job. If you read the Dunder Mifflin press release, it clearly states that they had absolutely nothing to do with that particular cancer cluster.
So if there is a lesson to be learned here, and I'm not sure that there is, it is that in order to help our communities, we need to put other people's needs ahead of our own.
And whoever comes up with the best idea gets a $50 gift certificate to the restaurant of his or her choice.
Who wants to help the world one step at a time?
Volunteerism is important. Every weekend I volunteer at the local animal shelter, and they need a lot of help down there.
Last Sunday I had to put down over 150 pets all by myself.
Paint a mural of Chicano leaders.
I have a way to make Scranton a better place. You could leave it.
Okay, I'm out of here. See you later guys. Bye.
Okay, oh no, here's an idea. Conservation.
I love it. Conservation. Let's start by conserving our time and stop having these stupid meetings.
No more meetings! No more meetings! No more meetings! No more meetings!
Anybody else? Who else has an idea?
I have some ideas about conservation.
Angela.
Thank you.
Please, could you hold down the port?
Sure. Well first of all, I think that we could totally...
Why are you crying?
Yes, I think we should look into that.
You could just speak up louder.
No, no, shh. No, I'll talk to her. I will, no, nobody talks to my baby that way. Uh-uh. Yeah, I'll let you know how it goes.
Alright, bye Pickle.
Who's Pickle?
Pamela Moore.