So what have we here?
I don't know what that is.
Oh.
Touche, Jim.
It's actually a lever connected to a ceiling tile.
When you pull it, something will fall on my...
falling asleep because of how lame this trap is.
What are you doing?
I thought, you know, he'd be looking up and I'd have time to...
Oh, I am rusty.
And a pie?
Come on, I'm better than that.
It's probably, you know, with all the kid stuff, getting ready for the...
No. There's no excuse.
Man, this used to come so easy.
I just wanted to check and see if there's anything you needed before I went on my maternity leave.
Yeah, I'm pregnant.
Great. Well, I'll write up the order.
Wait a minute.
Okay, thanks.
You can't do that. You cannot exploit your baby for sales.
Hey, did I tell you we're going to have a baby?
Oh, thank you very much.
I'm excited. Oh, definitely.
No, no. You need to come by your sales honorably.
There is nothing dishonorable about talking about your life. People like it.
Hey there. Dwight Schrute here.
Listen, would you be interested in restocking on paper?
Yeah, I could sure use the money.
My cousin came down with a case of that nasty new goat fungus.
Oh, it's just horrific.
The doctor says he's never seen it bearded so quickly.
Okay.
I need a baby.
I'll never outsell Jim and Pam without one.
Also, I've been noticing a gaping hole in my life.
Sometimes I wake up cradling a gourd.
Kevin, you're such a gourmand.
I cooked my way through Julia Child's cookbook,
and now I'm halfway through the Twilight cookbook.
Last night I had Edward's cornflake chicken.
Hmm.
Pregnant Pam and I, we get hungry at the same times,
so we've been eating together a lot.
Not all meals, but second breakfast, lunch, second lunch, and first dinner.
It's really fun.
I used to get her on the phone for bed meal,
but Jim put a stop to that.
I thought that maybe we should do something special for early dinner.
One last ultra feast.
Mmm. That sounds great. What are you thinking?
I think it should be a surprise.
Mmm.
Ooh, getting there, huh?
No, no, I still have time.
I don't remember. Is it a boy or a girl?
Um, I recall deciding not to find out.
Aren't you special?
Well, if it's a boy, I met this guy at Paintball who is a circumcision artist.
He does all of Joe Biden's grandkids.
If you say my name, I get 25 bucks. I'll give you five.
Hmm. Yeah, we already have a Paintball circumcision guy.
Is he going to give you five bucks?
What's a circumcision?
I'm having contractions, but they're irregular and far apart,
so I'm not really in labor. I'm near labor.
Yeah, we're slow playing it because of our stupid HMO.
If we check in after midnight, I get an extra day to recuperate surrounded by doctors.
Not to mention the extra night's sleep in the hospital will be very nice,
because once we bring the baby home, if it's crying all night,
one of us is going to have to take care of it.
And I do not plan on helping unless it's a boy.
I cannot wait for that joke to be over.
Walnuts or walnuts?
Walnuts. Puppies or kittens?
Puppies. Cashews or Brazil nuts?
Cashews. Europe or 10 minutes on the moon?
Europe. I don't like the moon. Pistachios or macadamias?
Macadamia.
Whoa! Contraption! She's contrapting!
All right, all right. It is baby time. Shall I scrub up?
No, no one's going to scrub up because it's not baby time.
It is, however, baby Ruth time. Pregnant coworkers.
That's all. Drop everything.
All I know is no one is commenting on my new high tops.
Pam, your due date's not until Friday, right?
Right.
How accurate are those due dates?
100%.
Wow.
Pam may be about to give birth.
And if I understand anything about the cycle of life, and I do,
that means somebody dies.
And I think we all know whose number is up.
Time to get my affairs in order.
So wish me luck, my friends, as I go gently into that good night.
Maybe it was conceived here, so might as well live here a little bit too.
That logic's airtight, but unfortunately it wasn't conceived here.
Burning Man, Porta Potty.
Oh! Yuck! TMI.
How was it? I don't want to know. Tell me later. Let's go! Let's go! Hospital!
Okay, okay, we're not going to the hospital. We are waiting until midnight.
Ooh, spooky. But why?
Because the insurance company only covers two nights.
Yeah, so if we wait until midnight, we get an extra day.
What's another day going to get you?
Knowledge, Oscar. Let's say they're sent home before they learn,
I don't know, proper spanking technique.
Speed, power, aim, noise, knuckles, spank.
Noise.
Let's go to the hospital, okay? Nobody wants to smell your stupid baby being born.
I don't want to smell it. I don't want to see it.
I don't want anything that reminds me of childbirth.
Look up the word episiotomy.
Okay, everything's fine. We have plenty of time.
Well, you don't want to wait too long, Pam.
Otherwise the baby's going to become a teenager in there, and you'll be up all night.
From the rock music.
Shut up, Nick. God.
Weird thing to say. Weird IT nerd. Don't get revenge on me, nerd.
What are you looking at?
Nerd.
My role in the birth of this child is that of the boss.
Within that, there is none of the pain associated with the mother's role.
There is none of the responsibility, which is associated with the father's role.
But in many cultures, the boss really plays no role at all in childbirth.
Did you know that labor can last weeks?
Then they take your insides out and they just plop them on a table,
and sometimes epidurals don't work, and you can poop yourself.
Bear my child.
Excuse me?
I want to have a child for business reasons, and I want you to be the mother.
If you agree, say nothing. If you disagree, say anything.
Very well. Let's meet at 4 p.m. in our old meeting spot and bang it out.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Whew.
That's seven minutes. Here we go.
Hold on, hold on. It isn't midnight yet.
Are you serious? Pam.
No, the doctor said every five to seven minutes.
I'm going to be okay. We should really try to make it to midnight.
Pam, please.
Yeah, no, you really should.
Because if your baby's born tomorrow, he's going to have the same birthday as Butt Mud Brooks, my old roommate.
Did you hear that? Butt Mud Brooks.
Okay, but we are leaving at five minutes apart.
Five minutes apart.
So the plan was seven minutes, but we're calling an audible because that's her call because she's the quarterback.
I'm just the left-ackel who happened to get her pregnant.
Okay, okay, okay.
Okay, stop watching me.
Okay, crazy.
I think I have some better things to do with my day than worry about you, like cell printers.
Mm-hmm.
Well, not until Friday, 20% off all toner cartridges.
That's a big deal.
While we're on the subject, why don't I just run you down to the hospital and just do a quick check?
Not until midnight.
Guys, full word of advice.
Speaking as a former baby, don't get too hung up on baby names.
I was named after a woman who was a little girl.
Don't get too hung up on baby names.
I was named Walter Jr. after my father until I was about six or so when my parents changed their minds.
I thought you said your younger brother was named Walter Jr.
My brother was born, and my parents felt he better exemplify the Walter Jr. name, so they gave it to him.
I was given Andrew, which they got out of a baby name book.
That's good.
You know what? It's getting really crowded in here.
Maybe you guys should all go back to work because the day's not out yet.
No, no, no.
You know what? You can't tell us what to do because you are not co-manager anymore.
Yes!
I feel like this noise is going to prevent Pam from being able to listen to her body's signals.
Actually, the distractions are good.
I mean, I don't think I'm going to make it until midnight if I'm just sitting here thinking about it.
Distractions are good.
That means conference room, five minutes. No, no, five seconds.
Right now, right now, conference room.
Topic, potpourri, let's go.
I'm sort of a master of distraction.
When I was a kid, my mom received compliments left and right from my teachers on how I was always able to distract others in class.
Try to think, what were the first 13 colonies?
Mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
Pfft.
The purpose for this meeting is to take Pam's mind off of what's going on inside of her body.
Can we do sleight of hand tricks?
I will allow that.
Yes!
Can anyone do those?
I'm going to go look at the internet.
Oh, God.
Oh, oh, all right. That's a good one.
Oh, okay. Sorry, guys. Just keep talking.
Okay.
Oh, my God, Pam. You are a woman warrior.
Oh, thanks, Kelly.
Does anybody have anything? Anything interesting? Any hobbies? Special skills?
Yes, this is the only time I'm ever going to make this request.
Yeah, Phil.
I can put on lipstick the way Molly Ringwald does in the breakfast club.
Nope, nope. I don't think anybody wants to see that.
I can do the evolution of dance dance.
That sounds good. Do you need some music?
No, actually, music would just throw me off. I need complete silence. Okay?
Okay?