Got you! Broken arm! Poof! Poof! Poof! Broken nose! Boom! Boom! Boom! Broken nose! Poof!
Ha! Gonna flip ya!
Once a year, Dwight holds a seminar updating us on the newest developments in the world
of karate. Because, as we all know, the one thing that thousand-year-old martial arts
do all the time is change.
How can I pose this to you in a relatable way? You are all members of the Yakuza, and you
happen to be visiting the Lackawanna Trolley Museum, and you're attacked by triads. How
can you hold them off until your clan arrives? You cannot go wrong with a throat punch.
Cut!
Okay, so there's no defense for that. Good to know.
No, there is a defense for that. Let me demonstrate. Someone attack me. Kevin, go!
No way. Last time you pulled my pants down, and then you tried to choke me with my shoelace.
That's false. I did choke you with your shoelace. Now come at me!
Okay, with all due respect to everyone here, I think the most worthy opponent of you is
you.
That is correct. Unless there happen to be measles present.
So let's just say that Dwight has come at you with the throat punch. Now how would you,
Dwight, defend against it?
Easy. Allow me to demonstrate. I am attacking myself with a throat punch. Here it comes.
Block. Grasp. Wrist. As such.
I don't know what if he comes at you with the other hand, because he does have two.
Good point. Second throat punch. Absorb the blow. Groin punch. Hip block. Elbows in the
gut. Uh oh. Up to the nose. No you're not. Ah! Oh!
Oh my god. He's making you look like such a fool.
He really is. But not for long. Ow! God! In step! Oh, not again! Ha! Ha! Ha! You let
go! You let go! Oh, you're right! I can't hold on!
You two are so evenly matched. I don't know how one of you is going to get the other hand.
The important thing to remember, Jim, we always have what is called the element of surprise.
But I would say my favorite art form is a tie between sculpting and stand-up comedy.
I did stand-up comedy once. You did?
Yeah. I killed. That sounds like it was hilarious.
It was hilarious. Hey, Michael?
Yes? What is the meaning of this email that everyone
got? You'll have to be more specific Dwight. I
got like eight emails a day. This one. From David Wallace to all Dunder
Mifflin. Woohoo! Shout out!
Hello everyone. I'm sure you've seen the item in the journal. Just want to stress it's all
conjecture. If there's any concrete news you will know ASAP.
Aaron, do we have the journal? Your feelings journal? You told me to put
it in the time capsule. Did you?
Michael, he means the Wall Street Journal online. Oh, the wall.
I found the article. On a day marked by panic corporate board
meetings, one that is relatively unsurprising is Dunder Mifflin's. It is rumored that they
will recommend and the article cuts off. It's a dollar 99 to finish the article.
I wonder what it was going to say. Are you serious?
I got it. I got it. Oh! Tuna beat me to it. It is rumored that they will recommend declaring
bankruptcy? What?
No. No. That doesn't make any sense. Oh lord, we're all going to lose our jobs.
Not necessarily bankruptcy could mean a lot of things. Maybe they're just restructuring
to get out of debt. Oh, that sounds awful.
Or it could mean the end of Dunder Mifflin. Oh god, well that's an interesting theory.
You know what? You can all have jobs at Shroot Farms as human scarecrows. It doesn't pay
much and you can't unionize. I'm sorry Michael, David's in a meeting.
Ah, well, maybe you should spy on him. Oh my god, wouldn't that be hilarious?
I'll just have him call you back. Okay. Okay. Good. I'll catch you on the flippity
flip. Bye. He's busy. Call me back when he's free.
If I lose my 401k, it's all over. Game over. I don't know why I thought this paper bubble
would last. It's like, I just didn't want to see the signs.
Game over. Game to F over for Stanley Hudson.
Michael, are you okay? Did you throw up in there?
I'm just pooping. You know how I be. But it smells like throw up in here.
Crazy world. Lot of smells. You guys, what if this is our last day at
work? What if we never see each other ever again?
I like Erin. There, I said it. I was kind of hoping she would ask me out, but things
had not panned out on that front. So, it's time for the Nard Dog to take matters into
his own paws. Yeah, I'm on lunch.
It's a busy, it's stressful today. Anything is at them?
It's my mom. Do you want? No, no, no.
I'll call you back. Okay, bye. Sorry, I just wanted to talk for a second.
Are you okay? Yeah, I'm good.
That no news is good news, right? Let me know if anybody calls.
Okay, should we? I'll transfer them or I can call you.
That's your job. Dunder Mifflin, this is Erin.
He is. Okay.
But he's at lunch right now. Sure.
Okay. Okay, thank you very much.
You too, bye. If it's not for me, don't make it look like
it's for me, okay? I'm sorry.
Because I'm going to **** my pants. Okay, I'm sorry. It's my fault.
Michael, I'm sorry before that I did not know what you were talking about.
Don't, okay. Do you want anything?
Don't even talk. Don't even talk to me. Okay?
All right? If they do call, don't.
Only if they call me, then talk to me, okay? If it's anything else or if you want to apologize
to me for calling me when they weren't calling, then don't do that, all right?
Do you understand? You're very, very nice, but you're really,
you're kind of pissing me off, okay? It's hard.
All right. Okay, don't cry.
Don't cry, please. Don't cry.
Everybody's sort of high strung, so chalk it up to that.
We're on it together. Well, don't laugh either.
Just don't cry and don't laugh. Good? All right.
Everything is gone.
We have to do something because people are losing it out there wondering what's going to happen.
Okay, we need some sort of distraction for everybody.
Anything new on YouTube? Michael.
Doesn't even need to be good. Oh, God, I can't think. I need more Mullins.
Listen, Wallace said these were just rumors, right?
So we have no reason to think that the company is anything but fine.
So if we just go on with our work, you and me, they'll follow along.
Monkey see, monkey do. That's it.
Monkey pee all over you. That rhymes.
So what have we on the docket today?
We have a monthly staff meeting.
All right. Let's conference room it up.
Okay. Where to sit? Which chair? Analysis paralysis. Bingo.
Okay, let's begin, right? Yes.
Is there any news about the company?
Nope. This is just a regular monthly meeting.
Can I take some time to work on a resume?
No. I only like games whose stakes are life and death.
That's why when I play Monopoly, I imagine that the reason I need to build a hotel on Boardwalk
is so that my snipers can target an assassin who's hiding on Park Place.
Here's the deal, guys. There is no new information as of yet, so I suggest we all just keep working.
Sure, I'm a little nervous, but doing our work will make us feel better.
I only slack off when things are good.
Customers have to use the coupon code from the website.
And as of now, there is no differentiation between the letter O and the zero, but we are working on that.
Stay tuned for that.
He needs me. Seed save infinity.
Okay. Great. Also...
What?
Oh my God.
What? What is it?
What happened?
Is there news?
There has been a murder.
What?
There's been a murder in Savannah.
Games have the power to distract people from stressful situations.
Battleship got me through my parents' divorce.
Operation got me through my vasectomy, i.e. my operation.
I don't think I would have been able to endure my breakup with Holly had it not been for Tossacross.
Bells, Bourbon and Bullets. A murder mystery dinner party game.
It is so much fun. Everybody plays a character. We go around the room. We try to figure out who did it.
Hey, I'm wondering if this is...