Parkour!
Michael!
Extreme!
Parkour!
This is Parkour.
Internet sensation of 2004.
And it was in one of the Bond films.
It's pretty impressive.
The goal is to get from point A to point B as creatively as possible.
So technically they are doing parkour as long as point A is dilution and point B is the
hospital.
Parkour!
Come over the camera.
Okay, we all go together or we go one at a time.
Here it is.
Truck to refrigerators to dumpster, 360 spin onto the pallets, backflip, gainer into the
trashcan.
Yes, gainer!
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
Parkour!
Good.
Excellent.
Thank you.
Here you go.
Is there anything else I can do?
Yes.
Um, see those files behind Kevin's desk?
Go put them all in random order.
Okay.
Then come back here for your next assignment concerning their order.
This is the last day of our summer interns.
It's been nice.
We haven't had interns in a while.
Ever since Michael's Monica Lewinsky incident.
He didn't do anything sexual.
He just made far, far too many Monica Lewinsky jokes.
It was just easier for corporate to shut down the program.
Hey, can you make 20 copies of these?
You know you're not supposed to talk to me.
It's not like I had them dig a ditch or anything.
I simply had them go to the bank, get out a couple hundred pennies, and search for old
rare coins.
They found one worth almost seven dollars.
So it was definitely no worse than Dwight's note passing service.
It was an interoffice messaging system.
It worked quite well for a while.
And ultimately it couldn't compete with computer IMing, which apparently has a stranglehold
on the whole instant messaging market.
Resume.
70 pound bond.
Excellent, Maury.
Interoffice memo.
Come on, come on, you can do this.
Megan, you've been awfully quiet.
Is something on your mind?
Why don't we just write this stuff down and then reference it when we need it?
Why indeed.
Cooper's Seafood, 2001.
A young man orders his first lobster.
Only he pronounces it lo-bster.
That's how little he knows.
The waiter corrects him and they get to talking.
The waiter is soon impressed with the young man's knowledge of paper.
The waiter is subsequently fired for talking to the young man too much.
The waiter then manages a small storage company and uses the young man as his paper pro.
Provider.
And to this very day, he is one of the young man's smallest clients.
That's why we do this stuff called for the small clients.
The big clients, they just care about price and you can use a list, whatever.
That young man?
That was you, wasn't it?
I can't believe I wasted so much time and energy on these interns.
Your generation could never fight in a war.
I have never fought in a war, but I could.
Specifically, the Boer War in South Africa.
That feels like a war that would suit me just fine.
Iraq and Afghanistan?
Too much hummus.
Think she did him?
I bet there's something there.
I was with them in the kitchen yesterday and they were all too happy to be cleaning the
freezer.
If they get married before I do, I'm going to kill myself.
Who's getting married?
Nobody.
If somebody doesn't tell me, I'm going to start screaming.
It's Eric and Megan.
Oh, hey, I hired them.
Patchmaker.
Places like Spaniard fly.
They're not getting married, it's just talk.
Did everybody know about this but me?
There's nothing to know, it's just gossip.
Okay.
We haven't told anyone that I'm pregnant.
What with her being unmarried, knocked up by some guy.
I mean, the yakety-yaks in this office would have a field day.
Yeah, and we don't want them at the wedding thinking Jim's being marched down the aisle
by my dad with a shotgun.
But there's not going to be a shotgun?
Nope.
No shotgun?
Because that changes everything.
Can't back out now, helper.
What are you going to do about it?
There's no shotgun, so.
Realize, realize.
No, keep it up.
Yep.
Does it say thank you for all your hard work this summer?
Cool.
My mom will love it.
Great.
And you got the three candles?
Oh, I mean.
Um, man, we spaced on the candles.
Really?
I gave you two things to do and you spaced on one of them.
What if I said to you, duck, because a wrecking ball is coming towards your head,
and jump, because a sword was going to cut your feet off, and you spaced on one of them.
Oh, hey, Pam, did you finish teaching the interns the wrecking ball low sword defense?
Yeah, sure did.
So they wouldn't need anyone calling out a warning or?
No, they'd know exactly what to do.
Great, thanks.
There's no defense for that.
Is there a defense for that?
We're sorry.
Sorry, sir.
Well, sorry's not good enough.
Because you know what?
The cake was for you anyway, idiots.
So enjoy it without your candles.
Seriously, what is the defense for that?
Feet soft, eyes wide, stomach tight.
One, two, three.
Ow!
You'll never guess what I know.
Okay, let me finish this thought.
Eric likes Megan.
He most definitely does.
I've been asking her out repeatedly for weeks.
She finally said yes.
They went out on a group date the other night?
Apparently it went very well.
How do you know this?
People tell me things.
I guess I have a face you can trust.
I think it's because of my low cheekbones.
And boom.
Okay, what is it?
What can't I guess?
I hate, hate, hate being left out.
Whether it's not being picked for a team, or being picked for a team,
and then showing up and realizing that the team doesn't exist,
or that the sport doesn't exist.
I should have known.
Poop ball?
Oh, man, I know how you feel.
Third wheel.
I have been the third wheel so many times in my life.
My mom told me something once that made me feel a lot better.
She said the third wheel is what makes it a tricycle.
What are you talking about?
I am talking about your group date with Megan and Eric.
At Tink's?
Yes.
How did you know about that?
Well...
Did Stanley tell you?
Stanley was on your group date?
No, Stanley was with his wife.
I waved at him, but he didn't wave back.
Does anybody else know about this?
No.
There he goes.
So, what is the scuttlebutt?
Anybody hear anything?
Nothing?
I got a little something-something.
I don't know if I should say.
So, just keep it to yourself then.
Stanley is having a midlife crisis.
Stanley is way past the middle of his life.
I suppose she's considering his height to weight ratio.
Well, apparently, he and his wife were out dancing at a club for young people.
Terry's out of town, Michael.
Who?
Stanley's wife, Terry.
She's at an interior decorating expo in Philly.
Stanley hates crowds, kids, and music.
I think you should check your fax.
You stupid son of a bitch, you set me up.
What are you talking about?
Stanley's wife is out of town.
She was with somebody.
He was definitely with someone.
Oh, was he? Well, who? His sister?
I don't get it!
If that was his sister, then what they were doing was totally illegal.
Drugs?
Making out.
Okay.
Oh, okay. No, it's okay.
Never mind. Carry on.
Stanley is having an affair.
What?
I am very happy right now.
Thrilled, perhaps, to be a part of the office, to be a part of the conversation.
When you have somebody's attention and their eyes are lighting up because they are very interested in what you have to say, that is a great feeling.
And I experienced that firsthand today.
It is wonderful to be the center of attention.
That and that are the same letter.
Q.
No. No.
Okay, he's holding a pencil.
He could be doing a crossword puzzle with that pencil.
What's that letter? Right there.
Same letter here and here.
What haven't you guessed?
T.
T? Yes. Yes.
That is a T.
And there's another one right there.
Just sound that out.
You're almost there.
Hey, Stanley. Where are you going, big guy? Up to no good?
I'm meeting a client. Do you have a problem with that?
No, no, no, no, no. I just had a quick question for you.
I'm casting a movie and I'm looking for a woman who can dance. Beautiful woman. Do you know anybody?
Goodbye.
Pays five million dollars.
Due to the acquired.
You have to stop this.
Did you hear that Stanley's having an affair?
I did. From you.
You gotta stop telling people.
Okay, I get it. You feel out of the loop and you feel sorry for yourself.
And it's really sad because everybody thinks you're a loser.
Do you even know if it's true? Do you have any idea?
Because you might be ruining his life.
Hold up! Hold up! Hold up!
No, no, no, no, no. Time to stop being polite and give him.
Stanley, you having an affair?
That is ridiculous. Of course not. Why would you think that?
So it's not true. Okay. Well...
Oh, those interns. They told me they saw you at the club and they all said it was you.
It was clearly just racial profiling gossip. The little shams.
The little shams.
Told her it was a stupid idea to go up in the club.
It's so stupid.
It's just that Terry's been traveling a lot lately.
I know. I know.
It's been lonely.
Oh, I bet. I...
Cynthia's been keeping me company. She was my nurse when I was in rehabilitation.
We used to go on these long walks on the treadmill.
I didn't intend...
Wait, wait, wait.
So it is true.
Yeah, but Michael, I'm going to go break it off. That's where I'm headed right now.
Oh my God. Wait a second.
Do people often say they're going on sales calls and then go someplace else?
Because that's not cool.
I just need you to promise not to say a word about this to anyone.
Michael, please.
I'm not saying a damn thing.
I'm counting on you, Michael.
Okay. You can count on me.
Yo, that smells good.
Yeah, I might have extra. It just depends on how many I eat.
Did you hear about Angela? That's pretty weird.
Yeah. What do you mean exactly?
Well, the fact that she apparently is dating an 81-year-old billionaire
owns a quiz that was on the turnpike.
Really?
Uh-huh. So, well, right?
How do you untell something? You can't.
You can't put words back in your mouth.
What you can do is spread false gossip
so that people think that everything that's been said is untrue,
including Stanley is having an affair.
It's like the end of Spartacus.
I have seen that movie half a dozen times,
and I still don't know who the real Spartacus is.
And that is what makes that movie a classic whodunit.
Kelly has an eating disorder?
Yeah.
She always eats my lunch.
Anorexia.
She's an anorexia.