Welcome, children of the Scranton Industrial Park community!
Join your gangster pumpkin on his pallet truck of doom.
Don't worry about a thing.
Rest assured you'll see me later.
We are doing a haunted house this Halloween.
Which is actually kind of spooky because as legend has it, on this very site there used
to be a productive paper company.
I am going to scare these kids so bad.
This is the spookiest warehouse in the world, kids.
You don't believe me?
Just take a look.
Whoa, scary, huh?
This is a surgery with an octopus and a burn victim.
Black Widow.
Leeloo from the fifth element.
Nobody told me what people were, alright?
So label yourselves or take what you get.
I want to sell your blood.
It's really not the trend of vampires right now.
Here is an old man and a golf dude and then the old chrome from Drag Me to Hell.
I'm a hobo.
I asked for a list.
And a clown.
I'm Jigsaw, idiot.
You're not as scary as Book Face over there.
Yes, I am the popular social networking site known as Book Face.
Okay kids, you all have been so good and unbelievably patient, so I think you are going to get some
candy.
Yay!
Good!
Ahhhhhhh!
Kids, just remember, suicide is never the answer, alright?
Why is Christmas the only holiday that can have a message?
It is the easy way out.
You are not alone.
What the hell is wrong with you?
Who wants candy?
And then I think I'm going to go to the garlic festival.
Wow.
You guys would love it.
David TCBY booth.
Same stuff you get downtown.
Do you like TCBY?
Who doesn't?
I can't believe it's yogurt.
It will be fun.
I confirmed with Raskin Design and they are expecting the both of you in an hour.
Oh, actually it's just going to be me.
They said the both of you.
That's a mistake.
You should give them a call.
Check that out.
Alright, just clear this up.
Well, there's actually been a few changes in the company and Michael and I are actually
at the same level.
So, I'm going to go to the club.
So, I can...
No.
Nope.
Why would that be a problem?
Jim is a good kid.
He can handle a lot.
But sometimes you have to call in a master.
I...
Why would you date an amateur when you could date a professional?
Great.
See you then.
What?
They said that they would feel more comfortable if you came along.
Why don't they just want you to go by yourself?
Why do they want me to come too?
I don't understand.
I absolutely don't understand you.
I don't want you to feel like I'm babysitting you or something.
Alright.
Let me go get your stroller.
Sure.
Michael is a good teacher.
A teacher is someone who stands right next to you your whole life and never lets you
do anything.
That's what a teacher is, right?
What are you going to call him?
Dave.
No.
What is his name?
Dave.
Mr. Borschard.
They're very formal.
Yeah, I've spoken to them on the phone.
Yeah, well, this is not the phone.
This is real life, baby, and you've got to own it.
Is that what you are wearing?
Yes, it is.
And that is the watch that you are going to wear.
No, it is not.
You should wear this watch.
I will loan it to you.
It is a tankard.
I highly recommend you wear that.
No, thanks.
They are into style.
They are into appearance.
We are selling success.
Hand paper.
That's sort of secondary.
No.
He's trying to microco-management me.
How about the knot on the tie?
Double dimple.
I think we need to go.
No.
Don't touch my tie.
You need to double dimple your tie, Jim.
Come on.
Here we go.
I want you to look good.
I can't turn around.
No.
Come on.
I can only do this in one direction.
Here we go.
I don't want them to think that you are a country pumpkin.
And then up through the rabbit hole.
Around.
And then down.
And then up through the rabbit hole.
And then up again.
Around the bend.
Around.
And up again.
Through the rabbit hole.
And down.
In to the gopher hole.
Up.
How do we look?
That's perfect.
Here we are outside of the Willisbury Industrial Park.
WB.
Industrial P.
Making cold calls.
The two people with the lowest sales in the quarter have to do them.
Pauper Bond reading, where are you?
Dean Trophy, Sweet 100 and doodly-doo.
Sherman Blinds and Rugs, Sweet 202.
Here it is.
Pauper Bond reading.
Sweet 401.
Yeah, I was gonna sing that part.
I know, now you don't have to.
Except it was gonna resolve the melody, so.
Now my head hurts.
Feels like I held in a sneeze.
I hate this feeling.
Sweet 401.
All right.
Hi, any messages?
They're soaking wet.
Oh, well, Jim and I got caught in a little flash rain,
flash winds, flash lightning.
Wow, sounds scary.
It was, it was.
And then in an instant, it wasn't.
Why isn't Jim wet?
I outran it.
I don't think it rained.
My hip would be throbbing.
It rained.
Michael, can I get you something?
A towel, some cocoa.
Nothing.
Cocoa.
I'll just leave that suit in your office then.
Good, yep.
Must be nice to have company on these cold calls.
We're kind of a dynamic duo.
Or trio.
How exciting.
Do you guys know the sex yet?
Oh, no, no.
We're not together.
No, no, no, definitely not.
Definitely not.
No, we just work together.
Looks like somebody's got a case of the definatly's.
Michael, the custodian from Raskin Design is on the line.
He said they found your keys in the koi pond.
Okay, thank you.
Did you say koi pond?
Yeah.
Michael, people are asking questions.
Okay, put them on speaker.
Hey guys, what's going on?
Hey Michael, did you fall into a koi pond?
I can't really hear you.
I think we have sort of a bad connection.
Jim, did Michael fall into a koi pond?
It's like Michael said, it was something else.
It was, okay, this is what it was.
It was these bunch of idiots
that had put a fish tank in the ground
with no cover and no railing.
So you fell in?
No, maybe I was trying to save a child that had fallen in.
So a child had fallen in?
Not yet.
That is hilarious.
No it don't, I'm not gonna bump, I'm not gonna bump.
It was not hilarious.
It was very, very terrifying.
Truthfully, it wasn't the way he fell in,
it was how long it took him to get out.
And we'd like to offer you 15% off your first purchase
as our way of welcoming you to the area.
Well, that sounds like a really nice deal.
Shabow.
And I must say that since we are a family business,
it's nice to see that you are too.
Oh, wow.
You thought that, oh my gosh.
Oh, definitely not.
My mistake, sorry.
It's okay.
Actually, it's kinda not okay.
I date models, face models.
My girlfriend on a scale of one to Giselle, a nine.
That's good for you.
Anyway, we also have a special on on-
Pam's carrying our surrogate
because my girlfriend needed to keep her figure
for Fashion Week.
So we put our baby in Pam.
Doesn't matter what Pam looks like.
Yeah.
You were way meaner to me than I was to you.
No, I wasn't.
Okay, the very idea of us together
made you burst out laughing
like you've just been into a Adam Sandler
and jelly sandwich.
You blew the sale, you idiot.
Let me tell you something.
I was never gonna make that sale.
Erin, do we have any of those clips
that hold paper together?
Staples?
David Wallace called.
Oh, he did?
What did he say?
He heard you made a big splash at the meeting.
Oh my God, that was so mean, what I just said.
And I didn't mean it.
It was Kevin and Meredith put me up to it.
Okay, I'm gonna kill you.
Michael, don't listen to them.
Thank you, Stanley.
You just ignore their carping.
Okay.
Michael. Yes.
Carp is with a fish and a term for complaining.
They're mocking you with work play.
Hey, boss, did you find Nemo?
I could name Pixar movies too.
Toy Story.
Don't you mean Koi Story?
And when you fell in, did you flounder?
Michael, flounder is about the kind of a fish.
I know what a flounder is.
I'm not usually the butt of the joke.
I'm usually the face of the joke.
I wish Jim had fallen into that pond.
Then he'd have to put on my suit
and it would be too short.
And he'd look.
Damn it.
He'd still look good.
Michael, you have some algae.
Okay, you know what, Aaron, enough.
Wait, just go like this.
Oh God, God, that's disgusting.
Okay.
No, Michael.
No, no, no more.
That is it.
Everybody in the conference room right now.