Kaluas Umbrella, please.
All right. So just you tonight.
Actually, I am meeting somebody, but I'm a little bit early.
Leaving my company after 19 years.
I'll drink to that.
I'm starting at a company this week.
Oh, really?
To beginnings and endings.
And to middles, the unsung heroes.
And to moms.
The moms of the troops.
Hmm.
Do not tell my fiancé I'm drinking on a Wednesday.
I won't.
I don't know her.
Moving out to the Burbs.
Actually, I'm moving further than the Burbs.
Moving to Colorado.
Colorado?
Yeah.
Sunshine State.
Yep.
Don't mess with Colorado.
No.
Doing some skiing?
No, no.
I don't want to end up like Sonny Bobo.
Well, that's just a good sense right there.
Yeah.
Everyone I know who skis is dead.
You know what?
I would like to try the luge, though.
Try it once.
You're hooked.
That's my guess.
That's what I've heard.
I'm an Olympics nut.
Oh, yeah?
Me too.
Summer or winter?
Summer.
Oh.
Knuckle.
Actually, I got to come around again.
Come on.
You know, it's funny.
I actually tried to get an animal Olympics going.
Really?
What happened?
You know, life happened.
What are you going to miss most about Scranton?
Oh, wow.
The mountains, where things are.
That's the way it goes.
Man, he is late.
I'm going to call him.
Do you mind?
I'm sorry.
No, no, no.
Where is this guy?
Excuse me.
Hello?
This is Michael Scott.
Yes.
Hi.
You running late?
No, I'm here.
I'm right.
I'm at the bar.
I'm at the bar, too.
You are?
What bar?
I'm at the bar, the bar that's located in the middle of the park.
The bar that's located in the lobby of the hotel.
I do not see you.
How long have you?
I've been here about, gosh, over half an hour.
Okay, yeah, me too.
Sorry.
What are you wearing?
I am wearing a gray suit.
Red tie.
Are we both at the right place?
Which place?
I hear your voice.
I see your lips moving.
I hear your voice in the fall.
Oh, man.
Oh, Michael Scott.
DeAngelo Vickers.
Wow.
That is insane.
That's the right term.
Bar dinner, let's get some vodka up in this cranberry and one for my friend.
Here we go.
Ready?
I am ready.
Here we go.
Well, this is it.
What do you think?
She'll do.
Oh, she'll do just fine.
I am very much looking forward to tomorrow.
It is, it feels like the culmination of a lot of hard work, a lot of good fortune, and...
Come on.
Did that just happen?
We should write a movie or something.
I'm serious.
Michael is leaving, and apparently they already hired a new manager, and we're meeting him
today.
It's a lot to process, paperwork-wise.
Nope.
It's not Ashton Kutcher.
It's Kevin Malone.
Equally handsome, equally smart.
Okay, everyone, as you know, one of my favorite things is fanfare for its own sake.
So without further ado, let's all start clapping.
Presenting the Angelo Vickers.
Hi.
Hello.
Come on out.
How are you, sir?
I'm well, sir.
How are you?
Can I just say I am so excited to be working here.
A little bit about myself.
I love the American Southwest, for starters.
You may call them Arizona, New Mexico, Nevada, Utah.
I call them heaven.
I have a peanut allergy, something I live with.
It's a part of me.
I've learned to cope with it.
What else?
I was just as comfortable at a ball game as I am at the opera.
I was a did-I-want-to-be-made manager?
Sure.
A great opportunity squandered?
Absolutely.
A crushing blow?
Yes.
Will I get over it?
No.
But life goes on.
Not for me.
I'm not that bad, guys, don't I?
I'll help you out here.
No, it's just, you know.
Hi.
Hello.
Have we met before?
No, not officially.
I saw you coming out of the bathroom earlier.
Well, I guess I'm going to go back to my cave.
Okay.
It was really great meeting you.
And that is what they call a meet-cute.
So we talk for like 20 minutes.
I'm not going to tell you the clue.
It's D'Angelo the whole time.
It's kind of embarrassing.
No.
Yeah, that story makes you sound stupid.
I happen to like the hilarious hijinks that I get myself into.
There he is.
D'Angelo, I was just telling him about last night when we met.
Remember that?
That was crazy.
That was great.
Let's see.
I'm going to go back to my cave.