Andy?
Attend the tale of Sweeney Todd, His skin was pale and his eye was odd.
Yes, he shaved the faces of gentlemen Who never thereafter were heard of again.
He trod a path that few have trod, It's Sweeney Todd, The demon barber of Fleet Street.
Did you write this?
No.
Who did?
Steven Sondheim.
Who is he?
Swing your razor wide, Sweeney, hold it to the sky.
Sweeney blows the blood of Elso Morlart.
What the hell is happening?
We're the cast of Sweeney Todd, The demon barber of Fleet Street.
We opened in a couple of weeks at the Loose Group Playhouse here in Scranton,
And today just doing a wee bit of viral marketing.
Attend the tale of Sweeney Todd, He served a dark and avenging god.
What happens then?
Well, that's the play, And he wouldn't want us to give it away.
Sweeney Todd, The demon barber of Fleet Street.
Wow!
Oh, that was amazing!
That was awesome!
I auditioned for this.
When did the cast list go up?
Like a month ago.
Really?
They didn't call me.
Who am I playing?
Andy?
Two comps, for my lady and her Gabe.
It's closing night.
Tomorrow we have to give the theater over to the Scranton's Miss Fitness Pageant.
I am so excited, but I just need one.
Gabe can't come, sorry.
What?
Yeah.
That's awful.
Everyone's doing a Miss Psych guy.
Gabe is not coming, which is huge,
because my plan is to make Erin fall back in love with me tonight.
Women cannot resist a man singing show tunes.
It's so powerful, even a lot of men can't resist a man singing show tunes.
Oh, who else is going?
Everyone.
Gabe seemed to think no one was going.
What kind of terrible rumor monger is Gabe?
He is woefully ill-informed, all right?
Excuse me.
Okay, link, link, link, link, everybody.
You're all coming to my show tonight, right?
Andy, what time does it start?
8 p.m. sharp.
How long is it?
Hour 45.
I can't make it.
They say that no one can take your pride,
but the people who cast Andy's play, they took mine.
Jim, Pam, you guys are in, right?
Oh, we wanted to, but our sitter just fell through.
I'm really sorry.
Dwight?
No, thank you.
Last time I went to the theater, a man dressed as a cat sat on my lap.
It would mean so much to me if you came to my show tonight.
I can't, Andy.
It's too hard.
That's...
I put everything I had into that audition.
Do you understand that?
If it makes you feel any better,
no one who auditioned for the part of Sweeney Todd got that part.
They had to bring in a ringer.
Well...
This guy's, like, world-class.
He should not feel bad.
I'm asking you, thespian to thespian,
will you please stop?
will you please be the bigger man and come to my show?
I wish I could, Andy, but I can't.
I have plans that night.
I'm going to see a friend in a play called Sweeney Todd.
You're that friend.
I'm going to see your play.
Nice!
And scene.
Listen, I would like you to take me to Andy's play tonight.
Please, waste of time.
You know what?
Let's just knock this out right now.
Disrobe.
Angela?
Don't like her anymore.
Not attracted to her anymore.
Just contractually obligated to make a baby with her.
Give me the punch card.
No.
If you want to punch the punch card,
you have to take me to the show.
That is not in the contract.
Well, there's a lot of gray area in that clause.
Do you want to remediate?
Right, fine.
I'll go to your little show.
But I'm not wearing a cape.
Thank you.
Dwight and I have a contractual agreement to procreate five times,
plain and simple.
And should he develop feelings for me?
Well, that would be permissible under item 7C clause 2.
So I would not object.
Hey, how are those salads?
It's my own fault.
My parents used to scramble to find babysitters
so they could take my little brother to do stuff.
I understand how hard it can be.
I just, tonight, I mean, if you could...
We'll keep looking.
Yes!
Really?
I mean, who knows?
Maybe I have a niece my family never told me about.
Oh my gosh, that would be amazing.
Yeah.
For a lot of reasons.
Yeah, I know.
Niche!
I need a lot of people tonight.
Big crowd.
You know, counting on that crowd dynamic to help Aaron love the show.
Like, when I go to a concert and there's 20,000 fans,
I have a great time.
But if I saw Justin Bieber alone at a museum,
I'd probably punch him in the face.
I'm not worried about Aaron seeing Andy's play alone.
She's already getting her actor fixed.
In the third grade, we did Sleepy Hollow.
I played Ichabod Crane.
They picked the play just so I could be in it.
Seventh grade, totally randomly, I played the same role.
Eleventh grade, I played Abraham Lincoln.
And in college, Ichabod Crane again.
I'll be there, but do not expect to stand in ovation.
I am sick of going to shows and feeling like I need to stand
when the show isn't that good.
You hear me, Steve Harvey?
We love culture, but Bob hates New York.
Too many...
Well, he just hates it.