Can I please have your attention?
Ryan and I have a huge announcement.
Oh, my gosh!
Wow.
Over the weekend, Ryan, Bailey, Howard, and I got divorced.
Sweet free ring!
Divorced?
Just so you know, it's totally amicable.
We're fine.
We don't need people here to take sides.
The last thing that we want is any kind of drama.
Wait, I... Can you back up?
What's the story?
We were having a beautiful weekend in the Poconos.
We were making love constantly.
We saw the sunrise.
Ryan was crying a lot.
That's not a relevant detail.
And in the morning, we walked by a chapel,
and we stopped suddenly, and Ryan said,
I don't think I should be married to you anymore.
Wait.
I'm sorry, when did you get married?
Um, like a week ago.
We got really wasted and it just felt right.
You didn't invite any of us?
We are getting divorced, Andy!
This is such a raw time.
God, baby, you know, with people's reactions to this,
I wonder if we made a mistake.
No, with the messed up laws in this country,
I don't want to be married until everyone can be married.
You know what, Ryan?
I talked to the other gay guys, and we're okay with it.
We all agree it's time for you to get married.
No, no, Oscar, not until everyone can.
Ryan, I changed my mind.
Okay, fine.
You know what?
This actually isn't amicable at all,
and we actually do need people to take sides.
Who's on my side?
And who is on my side?
I'm sorry.
Alright, bye.
Bye!
Let's go!
Just a minute!
How long do we have to wait?
For what?
You broke up with AJ weeks ago.
Don't you have a sales call to go on?
I don't understand.
I really don't.
I mean, we know we're going to start dating.
Why not now?
We don't know that.
Sure we do.
Why is it such a certainty that we're supposed to be together?
Why does the sun rise in the morning?
Why do magnets stick together?
Because everybody says so.
Everybody.
Michael, I can't keep getting into a situation
where I date whoever I'm working with.
You can understand that.
No, I understand.
I just don't agree.
Well, you don't have to agree.
Yes, I do.
No, you don't.
No, you can have your own opinion.
I have my own opinion and my opinion is to disagree with you.
Please give me a lot of fun to drive around a car with.
You'll get through it, hon.
Just make a game out of it.
Funny gym game.
That's it?
That's all I get?
Even after all the hard work I put into celebrating your talent today?
Alright, what'd you do?
Well, those things that you consider doodles, I consider art.
Where'd you put it?
Where'd I put what?
Let's go.
Oh, sorry, I gotta go.
Say it, where?
Okay, fine, three hints.
One, when you're getting colder, you're really getting warmer.
The fridge.
Two, you have a better chance if you think Bob Vance.
The fridge, got it.
And a final clue.
Let's go!
You know what, just think about it.
You'll be fine.
Bye.
Holly is ruining Michael's life.
He thinks she's so special and she's so not.
Her personality is like a three.
Her sense of humor is a two.
Her ears are like a seven and a four.
Add it all up and what do you get?
Sixteen.
And he treats her like she's a perfect forty.
It's nuts.
Cheer up, we made a sale.
Just drive faster, I wanna get back.
I'm going the speed limit.
Okay, fine.
My feelings don't matter to you.
It matters to you is your precious speed limit.
Someone's in a bad mood.
No, I'm not.
I'm not in a bad mood.
I'm not, Jim.
Hello?
Okay, fine, ignore me.
Have it your way.
Let's just talk about you, as always.
Sex different after the baby, Jim?
Alright, let me turn on some music.
I need to pee.
No, you don't.