What about this one? It's kind of badass, right?
Just seems kind of crazy in a way I might need right now.
I don't know. Oh, that's not yours.
Stanley just drank OJ out of my mug and didn't seem to realize that it wasn't his hot coffee.
So the question has to be asked, is there no limit to what he won't notice?
Going to the kitchen, Stanley? Need anything?
I'll take a Milano.
Okay. Oh, you should just sign this for me before you go.
Thank you.
Maybe Stanley's just super focused. Maybe Stanley's completely checked out of life.
Maybe we weren't meant to know the answers. And who am I to play God?
I'm just a guy with time on his hands.
What's a seven-letter word for purse?
Satchel.
No, starts with an H.
Handbag.
Hmm, thank you.
Shh, shh.
All right, everybody, take a seat.
As you may have heard, our branch on the planet Jupiter is up 8,000% in sales.
Yay!
Hold up. That clock is slow. It is five o'clock. I will see you all tomorrow.
Bye, Stanley. Love you.
Bye.
It's long, Stanley.
Night, everybody.
So what kind of statement are you making with that costume, Kevin?
The statement that I am making, Oscar, is I kind of look like Michael Moore.
Thunder Mifflin, this is Erin. Happy Halloween. How can I haunt you today?
A lot of people are really getting into Halloween this year.
Six seconds, McRubble. Pan's got a lot of fun stuff planned.
Two seconds, McRubble.
Including a costume contest and bombing for apples and a Ouija board.
Oh, boom! Oh, explosion! McRubble!
People are really into the costume contest this year.
Might have something to do with the prize. Maybe you've heard of it.
The 2011 Scranton Wilkes-Barre coupon book worth over $15,000 in savings.
Stop. Too late. If I was the real Scranton Strangler, you'd be so strangled by now.
If you're out there, Strangler, you will get caught. By me.
Sounds like someone's really trying to convince us that he's not the Scranton Strangler.
To my chickens, I'm the Scranton Strangler.
Oh, ho. That's very funny.
Looks like someone decided to dress up as old Dwight Schrute's mom.
What?
You're only one third as beautiful and about half her height.
I'm supposed to be olive oil. And it makes more sense when I'm standing next to Popeye.
But Jim doesn't want to put his costume on.
I am Popeye. I've never really been a costume guy.
Even when I was a kid, it just felt like something I was too old for.
And then this morning, Pam hands me this little number.
No.
In case you can't read my poker face, we will be reviewing our sales policies.
I have ten seconds to explain them or this whole place blows up.
MacGruber!
Lame. Why don't witches wear panties?
Oh, here we go.
Because they need to grip the brook.