Look at that!
Nice!
I love cycling.
Andy, I feel like a tourist in my own city.
I literally can't wait to wake up every morning.
She is a beaut!
Can't beat a horse. A horse is a bike that pedals itself.
Look at that, smooth roll.
You got it! Lance Armstrong's bike.
His ass was on that seat?
Alright!
It's not his actual bicycle, but it is
the same exact model he uses.
I'm unsure how I'll cross-eyed in that whole thing,
so I feel really weird right now.
Michael!
Yes, I can ride a bike.
I take spinning classes three times a month.
I think I know how to ride a bike.
Are you sure you once knew how to do this?
I did, yes!
I had those extra wheels on the back
that support you.
Michael! Michael!
Just steer more now!
Michael!
You never forget!
How do I look?
Amazing. How do I look?
Normal. Ugly.
Well, I did the best with what I've got.
Let's go. Alright.
Wait, wait, wait, wait for me!
It's weird if I come in slightly after.
We have a big meeting with the chief buyer
for Frame Select, Steve Nash.
He's not the Steve Nash.
He's big though. He's kinda like
Scranton Steve Nash.
Will you stop trying to put it in terms you think they'll understand?
It's condescending. I'm not doing anything.
I'm just explaining.
Who is this the Steve Nash?
Phoenix Suns, point guard.
No. No? Nothing?
No, Mr. Jock Hipster.
Well, neither of those things.
Oh!
Libby Dirkett's got married.
Big red mazel tov to the
Libster.
Ooh, it says here Dan Becker
fell off the side of Kilimanjaro
in a climbing accident.
It appears Dan's Sherpa survived
to tell the tale. Oh my god!
What? Is Dan okay?
No, he died.
It's Broccoli Rob.
You know this guy. I showed you his picture on Facebook.
Yes.
Some Vermont-based alums can hear
Broccoli Rob Blatt, 96,
in the state milk lobby's new
milk awareness song, Calcy Yum,
featuring fishes Trey Anastasio.
It says, Broccoli, Trey and I had a ton of
fun in the studio and I think you can hear it in the song.
That's great news for your friend.
Yeah, yeah, it's great.
You know, I forget about milk. This is a terrific
reminder.
I was the artsy musical one.
And here comes trouble. I had
four solos, Broccoli Rob had three.
Right?
Ugh!
Go tell them we're here.
You're good with receptionists.
Uh-huh.
Dwight.
Crap!
Danny Cordray is the worst.
Well, by worst you mean the best.
The best salesman ever.
He works for Osprey, Paperover and Throop.
Steals more clients from Dunder Mifflin than anyone.
So the situation is the worst.
Also, he slept with Pam. No, he didn't.
Tell them.
Nothing happened.
We went on a couple of dates.
He never called me again.
What? He never called you? I thought you said it just fizzled.
That's fizzling. I mean, someone has to
start the fizzle. Yeah, I thought you started it.
No, I liked him.
For a couple of days.
Four years ago.
You know I
have a kid with you, right?
I'm gonna intimidate him.
Okay? Okay, great. Watch this.
I'm just gonna watch.
Anyways, she says that is the biggest penis
I have ever seen and I said I know.
That's why I brought you to the penis museum.
Where tickets are a thousand dollars.
Well, hello Danny.
Hey, Dwight. Good to see you.
Good to see you.
What are you doing?
Oh, I'm just here for the coffee.
Like hell you are. Dwight.
He's not just here for the coffee, Jim. Wake up.
Brainstorming session
is now open. Anyone
has an idea?
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
Hello. Hey, it's Jim.
Listen, this is important. Are you busy?
Oh, hey, no, I'm not busy. What's up?
You are busy. What are you meeting? It's Jim.
Okay? Yes. Listen,
you gotta get over here because we're pitching Steve Nash
and Danny Cordray's here. You need
the big guns, yes? Yes.
What did he say? What did he say? The big gun
thing. Stop. I will see you in ten.
Bye. Hold tight.
Well, I know a lot of you thought that my sales
days were behind me and to be honest, so did I.
And the only reason I got out
of the sales game was to be reluctantly
called back in. You don't look
reluctant, Michael. You look really eager.
No, I don't have time for this.
Are you kidding me? You don't?
No. Okay.
Oh, I can't believe
I have to go.
Oh, I'm a manager.
I'm not a salesman anymore.
I'm an old man.
Doesn't have time for all of this.