It is 6 a.m. and DeAngelo and I are about to go house to house to give everybody their
Dundee's nomination certificate, just like the Oscars.
Yes.
And this happens every year.
Every year this happens.
You have a lot to learn, my friend.
Well, you know, why don't we try it and if it goes good, it'll be part of my tradition.
Why are you even saying that?
You're gonna love it.
Here we go.
This way, this way.
Oh, nice house.
Congratulations!
Yep.
Okay.
You and Pam have both been nominated for Dundee Awards.
There we go.
Have Pam come down?
No, no, she's not here.
Okay, I'm gonna get her cell phone.
Stay in bed.
Congratulations.
Stanley, we love you.
Have you lost your mind?
Get off my property before I call the police.
Alright, we got it.
Good.
Leave it at the door.
Yeah, that's fine.
Okay.
Hey, Toby!
You suck!
Is this an employee of ours?
Go, go, go, go!
I'm going to the bathroom.
Let's go.
Wait.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Wait.
Let's go.
No.
I'm sorry.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Wait, wait, wait.
No.
Go, go, go, go, go!
I've never seen this place in the daylight.
This reminds me of Katrina.
Here we go.
All right, got it, we set.
Hello?
Oh.
So busted, walk of shame.
Do you usually leave your door unlocked in a jar?
Oh, nice, I got a Dundee nomination.
Yes, that's right.
No big deal.
That's invertebrate.
All right, well, you should head out.
No, no, no, you gotta stay.
No, no, no, I have Vienna sausages and I have napkins.
Let me fix your breakfast.
I'm not going in there.
Go.
["The Last Supper"]
Good morning, Erin.
Oh, hey, didn't see you.
Any big plans for tonight?
I don't know, maybe volunteer at the women's shelter,
go to bed, I don't know.
Maybe I'm going to the Dundee's, woo!
You are getting so funny.
Very good.
The Dundee's are my baby and they need to go on.
When Larry King died, they didn't just cancel the show.
They got Pierce Morgan to come in and do his show
and that way Larry lives on.
Anything can happen at the Dundee's.
They're like the Golden Globes, but less mean
and I just want us to all have a good time.
Just a little announcement, folks.
Remember, the Dundee's is a black tie affair.
Black tie optional.
Every day is black tie optional.
FYI, tonight we will be hosting at Louis Volpe's.
I love their breadsticks.
Oh, their breadsticks are like crack.
I love when people say like crack,
who've obviously never done crack.
Well, the breadsticks are like what then?
Ryan, what can I use?
I don't know, something from your world.
The breadsticks are like scrapbooking.
You're right, you're right.
No, I'm a middle class fraud.
Shh, okay, okay, okay.
Everybody's right.
They're like breadsticks on steroids, right?
Yeah, that's great.
So as you know, the Dundee's are my legacy,
so I'm going to need to train a replacement.
So this year I have decided to have a co-host
and that person is
D'Angelo.
Yeah.
Always the Padawan, never the Jedi.
Thank you, Michael, but I will have to pass.
Think of it as part of your training.
I'm not much of a performer,
unless you count singing in the shower.
Boy, okay.
Okay, we'll work on it.
I'm very, very bad.
Very bad.
Guys, I want you to help us work on some banter.
Yes! I love banter.
But I hate witty banter.
Here we go.
So, D'Angelo, you and I have a lot in common.
You lost 200 pounds, and I lose my car keys every morning.
That is true. We do share some similarities.
I know I can fix one of those problems.
For me, it's portion control. For you, you need a keychain.
Maybe. Hang it on the...
You know what? I didn't actually lose my keys.
This did not happen.
There needs to be what you call a rat-a-tat.
And right now it's all rat and no tat.
Ryan, come on up here.
D'Angelo, if you just want to tap D'Angelo out...
If I can see it...
Just watch this.
Ryan, how are you today?
Why do you ask my therapist? My mom certainly pays her enough.
There you go! Lovely! Regis and Kelly.
Nice. Use that as an inspiration.
Just be funny.
You, sir.