Oh, okay, okay, nobody panic.
Listen up, listen up.
Everyone, follow me to the shelter.
We've got enough food for 14 days.
After that, we have a difficult conversation.
My bad.
Space heater and fan were both on high plugged into the same outlet.
Oh.
It's saying the server went down.
Does anybody know that password?
Because otherwise we can't do any work.
Oh, try password.
Nope.
Try 000000.
No.
Okay, now try 000001.
Okay, I'm not doing every number.
Wait, does anyone remember when it was set up?
Oh, it was like eight years ago.
Lord of the Rings stuff?
I don't know, I'm just trying to think of things that were happening at the time.
Everyone was getting their driver's license.
Why don't we just call the IT guy who set it up?
What's the name of the guy in the glasses again?
Okay, moving backwards, our IT guys have been Glasses, Turban, Ear Hair, Fatty 3, Shorts, Fatty 2, Lossange, and Fatso.
I think Lossange is the one who installed it.
I got it.
Try, um...
You know what, it made me laugh when I heard it, but Pam got really offended.
Big boobs.
Trauma queen?
Nosy.