So, coasting time is officially over.
Big changes are coming and they're coming fast.
If you don't like them, this is called a door.
You can walk right through it.
Alright?
I'm not here to be your friend.
I like my life outside of this place.
I live to leave at five.
Change number one, Daryl, per your request, the company is sending you to business school
at night.
Full ride, deal with it.
Seriously?
Stone cold, seriously.
They are trying to figure me out and I don't like it.
Once they figure me out, they start to tell me what I want to hear and I need to quickly
figure out who's a good worker and who is simply a good mind reader because as soon
as I'm hearing what I want to hear, I'm not going to care.
Change two, Toby, you're getting a new chair.
Thanks.
Don't thank me.
Hey, don't thank me, guy.
Okay?
And I don't care if you like it.
These sound like good ideas.
Why wouldn't we like them?
I don't care what your favorite flavor is.
Here's a bowl of ice cream.
You either like it or you don't.
That's my attitude right now in this room.
That's my attitude on Ice Cream Thursdays.
Alright?
Pinball machine, going to the break room.
It will be quarterless.
You will not have to put quarters in it because I don't want to hear any bitching and moaning
that I didn't bring enough quarters to work to play pinball.
Okay?
You just reset it because I don't want to hear about it.
If there are any complaints, you can direct them to the garbage, specifically my garbage.
This all sounds great to me.
But I could see how some people might think that they're bad.
I don't know what to think.
That is an astute observation, Kevin.
Kev's got me pegged.
Not long before the others catch on too.
I guess that's it for me.
Oh well.
Time to stop worrying and start being happy about it.
It blows away Vermont in the fall.
For real?
Good morning, D'Angelo.
Hold on, Pam.
Okay.
And if you're really serious, you should go in the spring.
Because of the flowers?
No, because the entire state smells like earth.
Dogwoods, or just the earth?
Yes, Pam.
Hey, well, good morning.
I think I have good news for you today.
I found your new executive assistant, my friend Carla.
She's got great experience.
We even considered making her Cece's godmother, but she had this boyfriend at the time.
But here's her resume.
Put it with the rest.
Okay.
Hey, dudes.
Hey.
Oh my god, he hates me.
No, he doesn't.
You just get so nervous and hyper around him.
I know.
Every time there's a silence, your brain's like, ha ha ha.
Is that what he tells you at your little inner circle meetings?
Careful.
There is no inner circle.
Oh, there's an inner circle.
Oh yeah.
There is no inner circle.
DeAngelo just prefers to delegate a few things to a few guys.
Jim only says that because he's in the inner circle.
I also say that because I am also in the inner circle.
Did you get that, Ma?
Your boy, Kevin Malone, is in the inner circle.
Which doesn't exist.
There he is.
Got you a coffee.
Oh, wow.
Thank you.
That was so kind of you.
Not a coffee guy to take it, huh?
It's just that I own the coffee shop.
So once you've seen sausage being made, all you want to do is make sausage because it's
so much fun.
Listen, I've got a sixer, automatic for the people on the jukebox.
It's at the park after sundown.
Come on.
Pick up some sausage if you want.
I think you'll find what you're looking for over there.
No matter how many times I reach out to Dwight, he doesn't seem to want anything to do with
me.
It reminds me of my relationship with my son, except there I'm the Dwight.
So DeAngelo has given us permission to do basically whatever we want in order to get
rid of these 2010 printers.
Any ideas?
You know, I feel a lot more comfortable hearing this directly from DeAngelo.
Okay, well, he asked me to run this, so.
Well, you're not doing a very good job because I don't have any ideas.
Andy.
What?
Okay, we will finish this another time.
Who's the biggest client in the state?
I say we go get them, whatever it takes.
Huh?
What do you guys say?
Yes.
Huh?
Right?
Or my other idea, 50,000 tiny clients.
Yeah, I say that we just go for it.
Is that about lighter than usual?
Is that a Chinatown knockoff?
That's Toys R Us, I think.
No, that's definitely a knockoff.
You can feel the center of gravity is off.
Feel that.
What do you think?
Yeah, totally.
Jim, you got ripped off big time.
DeAngelo.
See what I did there?
Oh, that's what you need to do.
Just add a little English.
The British are coming.
DeAngelo's open.
Okay, so yes, maybe DeAngelo's a little bit of a talker.
He's new, you know?
He just wants to impress.
I get it.
What he doesn't realize is that he literally doesn't have to do anything to impress these people.
Check it out.
Oh, who's Bernard Andrews?
Me?
You want to be DeAngelo's executive assistant?
God, no.
I can barely type 15 words a minute, but I have to change the way that DeAngelo perceives me.
I can't just be the funny guy.
Okay?
So I give him the resume, he checks it out, and he's like, who's this dud?
I got to meet him.
And then I'm like, hey, you already have, it's me, it's the Nard Dog.
And then I'll be his guy.
If you think that'll work, I'll put it in the pile.
Do you think that will work?
Definitely.
Okay.
Hey, there he is.
Here I am.
Hey, while I have you here, my brother squirts in me.
Major Los Lobos tickets in A.C.
We're going to party bus together, heading down there this weekend.
Are you interested?
Can I drive the bus?
Probably not.
No, thank you.
DeAngelo is a fine manager.
I'd give him a B.
The only reason it's not a B plus is he makes my skin crawl.
Don't know why, just quality, I guess.
Hey, Ry.
Your department's killing it, baby.
Hey, my pleasure, my treasure.
Keep it up.
The problem with having it or the X factor or whatever it is you want to call it,
is that it's impossible to put into words what you're bringing to the table.
So to make things simpler for DeAngelo, I just, without lying,
strongly implied that I'm Kelly's supervisor.
It's not even that much of a stretch.
She pretty much does whatever I say.
What?
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Why should I pretend that you are my boss?
Because what would you have done in that situation, Kelly?
I'll tell you what I would have done for you.
I'd lie for you.
Yeah, but you lie all the time.
You lie for no reason.
Ry, you just like to lie.
I'd die for you, too.
You really would?
Hey, Kelly Kapoor, if I don't have those call logs on my desk,
we're just going to have to evaluate your future at the company.
Sure thing, Mr. Howard.
Ooh, I'm glad you're here.
Ooh, glad he's not my boss.
Oh, you're the best, thank you.
You know, I have a cousin who cracked the secret formula
for a certain popular cola that I shall not name,
so I've never had to buy it.
True story.
I just drink my cousin's.
Congratulations on your one cousin.
I have 70, each one better than the last.
You know what?
Straight up, why don't you like me?
I'm just not a suck-up like everyone else around here, okay?
I do my job well, so why don't you just leave me alone
and let me do it, okay?
Oh, no.
What?
Okay?
I'm going to win you over.
No, you're not.
Yes, I am.
No.
Oh, yes.
Yes.
No.
Hey, Pam, where are you hiding that stack of resis?
Oh, right here, and I took the liberty of putting the most qualified people on top to make it easier
for you.
Okay.
Well, I could see why you might think that would be helpful,
but actually there's quite a bit of science to this.
Yeah.
Thank you, nonetheless.
It's fair.
You know what?
I'm done trying.
You can have him.
Okay.
You felt the same way about Michael, right?
Then time passed, and what happened?
He just named his new puppy after you.
Pamela Beagsley.
It's a beagle.
It's really freaking cute.
Uh-oh.
This former administrative assistant misspelled administrative and assistant.
Oh.
Sorry, Bernard Andrews.
Yes.
Sorry, guy.
This woman's last job was in 1995, though she is proficient in both the net and the web.
Sorry, moms, trying to re-enter the workforce.
Not on my watch.
Wait.
This is funny.
This guy.
Now this guy's good.
The winner.
Under special skills, Mr. Don Finer put juggling.
What's wrong with juggling, Daryl?
I'm a big juggler.
I actually perform a motivational juggling routine.
Seriously?
Oh, yeah.
I'd do it for a year, but what would you say this room is?
300 square feet, 320?
320.
It's just free ball in it.
It's a little cramped.
How many square feet out there?
17, 18 hundo?
Oh, I think it's 18 hundo.
Give or take.
Sorry, gang.
I thought my juggling stuff was in the trunk of my car, but it's not.
Oh, no.
Do you think it was stolen?
I got you covered, boss.
Used to play with the parabolas myself.
Got some extra balls.
Hey.
Whoa.
Sorry.
I never touch another juggler's instruments.
You know, we're all here.
I've got the music queued.
Why don't I just do my routine without the juggling balls?
Prepare to go into the danger zone.
Oh, wow. You weren't kidding.
No, never.
Can someone please throw me a fifth ball?
If you dare.
Incoming.
And we're off.
Remember, nothing's impossible.