Sorry mate.
Oh, sorry, mate.
Excuse me.
What are you doing?
English.
You're taking the vicar, you've picked the wrong person.
No, no, no, I'm not picking, I'm not at all.
You're English, correct?
Yeah, big time, yeah.
I'm working on an English character.
Would you mind?
It's called Reginald Poofter.
Oh, David Brent, my liege.
How are you?
Michael Scott.
Oh, there you go.
I do characters as well.
I've got a Chinese fella, not politically correct, but he's called Holy F***.
That's not what it sounds like.
I'm not a Chinese fella.
I'm a British guy.
I do characters as well.
I've got a Chinese fella, not politically correct, but he's called Holy F***.
That's not what it sounds like.
I do things.
I roll.
I pee.
You can't do that these days.
No, no, no.
And people don't understand that it has nothing to do with making fun of a different nationality.
No, comedy is a place where the mind goes to tickle itself.
That's what she said.
Oh, wow.
That's good.
Pleasure to meet you.
Where are you working?
Dunder Mifflin.
Any jobs going?
No, not right now.
Just let me know.
Alright, see you around.
Bye bye.
That nice guy.
Your first student is here, Mr. Bernard.
That's actually Master of Ceremonies, Bernard.
Last year, I went to a seminar called The 10 Secrets of Real Estate.
Turns out it was just a ploy to sell me timeshares in Idaho.
Cut to, you know, I'm spending a weekend in Boise.
Terrible time.
Super lonely.
But I get to thinking maybe I should put on my own seminar to lure clients.
Oh.
Hello, I'm here for the small business seminar.
Michael.
Nine, I'm Greek.
My name is Mikado.
Ooh.
Oh.
Wait, Michael.
Michael.
Okay.
I am the plant.
Every great seminar has one.
My job is to make the speaker look good, and I do this through the techniques of leading
questions and laughing at all jokes.
And the character, Mykonos, is just a little added flavor.
Mykonos is loosely based on another character I do, Spiros, who is more about the ladies.
Thank you so much, Tuna Turner.
You are simply the best.
Listen, this isn't a favor, alright?
This is a good idea.
We all win.
Go higher.
I'm more flexible when I'm nervous.
Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop.
Hey, Andy, I'm really, really sorry to do this to you, but I have a meeting today that
I totally forgot, so I can't be a part of this seminar.
No.
What?
You can't do that.
You are a critical part of this seminar.
You're the charming warm-up guy.
I know.
If this seminar was a meal, you'd be the most bouche.
You're like signal of flavors of the whole night.
I'm really sorry.
I can't do it.
You can't, you can't.
I can't have this go badly.
I'm a terrible salesman, and I haven't been making very many sales lately, or ever.
This is my only idea on how to turn things around.
If it goes badly, I might lose my job, which would suck, because this is the only job I've
ever been good at.
Will you let me know when this whole seminar thing is over?
What's going on?
Do you know that guy?
I just have a meeting outside the office.
Hey.
How are the marks?
What are some of your small business ideas?
I was thinking we could buy up a bunch of abandoned mine shafts.
Oh.
That's great.
There's a big, big future in that.
A lot of mines.
What about you?
Credit cards.
Uh-huh.
My company will act as an intermediary for like .2 cents off every transaction.
Wow.
Some with cell phones, like every time you make a phone call, I'd make .2 cents.
Or anything, like any online shopping, I get .2 cents, basically.
Right.
Okay.
You promised us whales, these are worms.
They're not worms, Dwight.
Okay?
They're just people with tiny businesses.
They're baby whales, which is even cuter.
I'm out.
Stanley, you're supposed to close.
Sales is not hard.
Here's what I do.
I make my pitch, then I stare.
Want me to stop?
Buy something.
I'm out too.
What?
I already lost Jim.
Salesmen are supposed to help each other out.
We're supposed to be a team.
We're no more a team than the people staying in the same hotel are a team.
I just need your help.
Of course you do.
Because you can't close sales.
I would not say I can't close sales, Phyllis.
I would say I cannot close sales.
That's just my personal speaking style.
Closing is about asking for money and not taking no for an answer.
But I was raised never to speak of money and never to ask for anything.
Our needs were anticipated.
Hey, who's this?
Oh, I had to get the rest of my stuff out of AJ's apartment.
That's Fluffy.
Fluffy, I like that.
Hi Fluffy.
AJ named her.
I never liked it.
Oh.
Well, the good thing about Goldfish, they forget everything they know in two seconds.
So you could just rename them.
You'd never know.
Goldfinger?
Mmm.
Goldschlager.
Gold of my ear.
You know what might be kind of fun?
I was thinking, you know, Andy's having the seminar today.
What if we went in as a Greek couple?
Mykonos and...
Oh, I don't know, Mike.
I'm not feeling up to that.
Okay.
Holly broke up with AJ last week, which is the greatest thing that has ever happened to me.
To Holly, it's been the worst week of her life.
And I know for a fact that there was a week for her in high school when she got mono and her first period ever.
Too much information?
That's what I thought.
But you know what?
Here I am using it.
If you change your mind, why don't you talk to Mykonos?
Is Mykonos Greek?
He sounds Italian.
Ugh, you're the fifth person to tell me that today.
Maybe Mykonos ran away to join the Italian circus.
Okay, yeah, like a character history.
Good.
Tom Hanks does that.
Pretty strong start, Gabe.
Yeah.
You want to forfeit?
Say your prayers, buster.
I'd say the same, but even God can't help you now.
Leave, Gabe.
Gabe and I play Scrabble on our phones, and the winner gets to pick the movie we watch.
I have won no games.
So far, I've seen The Shining, Rosemary's Baby, The Ring.
Not really my thing.
Although I do like the early parts of the movies where they have a perfect family and everything.
Bam.
Here.
Is jelp a word?
Jelp?
J-E-L-P?
No, J-L-P.
Like, I jelp you.
I don't think that's a word.
I'm playing Scrabble with Gabe, and I've never won a game.
You want some help?
Really?
Mm-hmm.
I'm not letting Gabe do this.
Jim and I used to play Boggle against each other, and when he would win, he would get so cocky about it.
It ruined Boggle for me.
Ruined words for me.
Boggle.
Um, yes.
I am pretty good at Boggle.
Is that guy still here, by the way?
K-A.
Ka?
What does ka mean?
It means you're playing someone who's going to destroy you.
Why did you play moo?
Because I'm playing to win.
I'm playing moo, I'm playing milk, whatever it takes.
Okay, but look, you could have hit mood.
You would have played a triple word.
Like the cow mooed yesterday.
Ka.
Or moon?
The cow jumped over the moon.
She's stuck on that one thing.
No, it doesn't have to just be cow stuff, right?
Kevin, Jim dropped out of my seminar, and I was wondering if you could replace him as my charming warm-up guy.
Andy, I'm no Jim.
The only way that I'm Jim is in the movie version, when Jim sees what his future would be like if he never met Pam.
Hey, that's crazy talk.
I think you're great.
Then I won't let you down.
In the go.
Hey.
Hi, Ryan, you went to business school, right?
Yep.
I need someone to talk to this seminar about business.
And?
Can you do it?
Okay, I don't like committing to things just like that.
So, no.
No, I don't like committing to not doing things either.
That's just as big a commitment.
Oh, baby.
What do I put you down for, brah, hombre?
Yes.
All right.
Yes, I'll do it.
Okay, thank you so much.
It's gonna be awesome.
And if I flake, I flake.
What?
Kevin, you open it up.
Yep.
Ryan, you come in with your small biz expertise, right?
And then Creed, guest speaker, coordinator.
And then I come in and just close all the sales and stuff.