Hey, how you doing?
I've been thinking about my grandmother a lot.
Yeah.
She was about to turn 97.
At least she lived a very long and I'm sure very happy life.
Got you this card.
When you're ready, we all signed it.
We just wanted you to know we're thinking about you.
Thank you.
Congratulations, Darryl. Let's get wasted.
Have fun today, big guy.
Oh yeah, party time.
Whoop, whoop.
It's possible that some people thought it was your birthday.
Hooray, live it up, big D.
Days like this don't come often enough.
Time to celebrate.
You deserve this.
Birthday punches!
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
Sorry.
Thirty, forty, fifty, sixty, sixty, seventy, ninety, ninety, two, eighty, twenty, one, two, three, two, three, four, five,
Thirty, forty, fifty, sixty, sixty, seventy, ninety, two, eighty, twenty, one, two, three, two, three, four, five.
So I got an early res at Blue Wasabi and I'm taking Rachel.
She's picking me up after work.
Rachel from the party.
Oh yeah, nice.
Do the damn thing.
Blue Wasabi is so good, but get the cheeseburger.
They say they won't do it, but they will if you make a scene.
Okay, bye.
Oh, I'll miss you.
I'll miss you.
I'll be in my office if you need me.
Bye.
Okay, bye.
All right, bye, bye.
One more big one.
Don't go, I don't want to.
No, don't go.
Don't go.
Holly and I are dating.
It's been a week and I still can't believe it.
It goes to show that everything you want in life you get and you can't work for it.
It just comes to you.
And what do we have here?
From my secret admirer.
That's you.
Conn.
I dominate Valentine's Day.
I practically make romance into a science.
Roses are red, violets are blue.
Look in the vase to find your first clue.
Oh my gosh, it's a romantic scavenger hunt.
Close.
It's a romantic treasure hunt.
A scavenger hunt is where you find items from a master list.
This is where you follow clues that lead to a prize.
Come on, misuse.
Good luck.
But there's no clue.
Well, get to work.
I can't because there's no clue.
The puzzle is the clue.
Are these numbers correct?
Numbers are correct, Michael.
Okay.
Are you sick, Oscar?
Do you need to go home?
Because you're grossing me out.
I just need a signature.
There you go.
Thanks.
Thank you.
How much do you give them?
Big tip.
Wait, I don't have my scarf.
What?
I'm missing my scarf.
Oh.
We decided to have a Valentine's Day lunch.
And then that way we could spend the entire night with Cece
and not avoid the Valentine's Day dinner thing.
It's a whole thing.
Yeah, lunch was wonderful.
There was an amazing buffet,
and there was a chocolate fondue station,
and what else was there?
A bottle of champagne.
Yes.
Never found that bottom, did we?
No.
Psst.
What's up?
Are you good at jigsaw puzzles?
Are you kidding me?
It's all I did every summer when my brothers were out sailing.
Okay.
But if this is a romantic thing with Gabe,
I should probably...
Oh, no, no, no, no.
No, it's not weird at all.
You have your new girlfriend, I have Gabe.
This is just as friends.
Well, okay then.
Yes.
At least until Stanley calms down.
Oh, is Stanley...
Don't look.
I accidentally did his sudoku.
Oh.
All right, I will fax over it to you.
Whoop.
I will fax over to you.
Okay.
Thank you.
Okay, my name is G-G-G-G-G-G-G-G-G-G-G-Jim Halpert,
and I will fax it into you.
Under you.
I'll fax it into you.
Oh, excuse me, I just p-p-p-p-pissed my pants.
Not really, I didn't really.
You know, Dwight, I don't tell you this enough,
but I think you're really funny.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
I'm not known for my sense of humor.
That would appall me.
But I have one.
I find inversions of fortune funny.
Upside down houses.
How a man spends his hard-earned money on art.
How a map distorts the size of Antarctica.
Tickling always makes me laugh.
Wait.
You're just filling that out right now.
It wasn't meant for me.
It will not be your Valentine.
Oh, I'm nuts.
I don't know if anyone else feels this way,
and don't get me wrong, I love Michael and Holly.
And maybe I'm being overly sensitive, but the PDA.
Yes, the freaking PDA.
Uh-huh.
Thank you.
I mean, I'm thrilled for them.
No one is more thrilled for them than I am.
Yes, absolutely.
But it's totally inappropriate.
Yeah, it's a little much.
Obviously, so happy for them both.
I don't know, guys.
I, for one, enjoy watching them.
No, stop.
Wait, can I finish?
Can I finish?
Is that okay?
I was saying I enjoy watching them because it makes me horny.
Oh, God.
Kevin?
Do you think they'll get married?
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Huh?
What is this?
What is this thing that you're doing?
Well, it's obvious they're going to get married.
Just look at them, Angela.
They're crazy for each other.
Hey, am I the only one that really liked AJ?
I never let myself get close to him.
That's just, that's on me.
So tell me about your new girlfriend.
She's neat.
I met her at Daryl's cousin's party.
We were the only two white people there.
Aw, cute.
Hey, look at that.
Done.
That's Gabe's boombox.
Come on, we have to go find it.
I wish you well on your quest.
No, come on.
Aw, man.
Come on!
Okay.
I hear them kissing all the time.
It's this horrible flipping sound.
It's like Chinese water tershes.
It's just like it's coming from my own head.
Okay, sit.
Okay, just close your eyes.
Can you get lower?
Oh, yeah.
A little lower.
I cannot keep myself from Michael.
Everything he does is sexy.
He has this undeniable animal magnetism.
He's a jungle cat.
The man exudes sex.
He can put both his legs behind his head.
Thank you all for meeting on such short notice.
Yes.
Yes, Michael Scott Dunder Mifflin.
What is the purpose of your visit?
Michael Scott Dunder Mifflin, what is the purpose of this meeting?
Seeing as it's Valentine's Day, I felt it would be apropos to have a little refresher course on romance in the workplace.
Perfect.
Yes, it is quite aprop-ro-p-ri-ate.
Carry on.
First things first, an office romance is permissible.
Not something you'd expect to hear from corporate.
Well, guess what?
Sabre is 100% tolerant of office romances.
Speaking of, Gabe, I don't see Aaron at this meeting.
I also don't see Andy.
Ooh!
Boom! Face!
I get it. Andy's slamming my girlfriend.
Very funny.
What I do not approve of, however, is public displays of affection, or PDAs.
PDAs are totally superfluous to a happy, healthy office romance.
A perfect example, look at Jim and Pam.
Yeah.
What? Us?
They don't touch. They don't kiss.
You would hardly even know that they were husband and wife.
Did it. Love it.
Keep it going.
Okay, so PDAs, that's going to include behaviors such as hugging, kissing...
Booby honking.
Yeah, booby honking, sure.
Butt honking.
Butt honking, yep, all the honking stuff.
The one where you start in a crouched position and you leap up.
Sure, basically, there's no precise definition, but you know it when you see it.
Are you guys listening to this?
What, are you talking about me and Holly?
Yeah.
Maybe you find your own chair.
So we kiss occasionally.
Not occasionally all the time.
Yeah, and it's not just the kissing, it's the flirtatious whispering.
The flirtatious tickling.
Whispering and tickling have their place in business.
That thing where you softly exhale on her neck.
I... okay, yeah, that's pretty hot. I will give you that.
Look, we can go back and forth all day long as to what is or is not PDA,
and we're not going to get anywhere.
Is coming in and saying hello to someone a public display of affection?
Hmm? Is patting somebody in the back for a job well done?
Is touching a crotch?
I would say no, no, yes.
You are all hypocrites. You all do it.
Kelly, you do it all the time.
Never.
Are you telling me you never kiss Ryan in the office?
I have never, ever, ever done PDA in this office.
It's not something that I would do.
It's not something I would plan on doing just now.
No, Michael.
Okay, you know what? My head just exploded listening to you.
I have no idea how to respond.
Michael, confession. I have done PDA in the office.
Thank you.
I've had intercourse in the office.
All right.
As has Angela.
Dwight?
As has Ryan. As has Kelly. As has Meredith.
As has Phyllis. As has Daryl. As has Creed.
As has Michael and as has Holly.
As has Kevin.
With who?
She goes to another school.
Okay, fine. No more PDA.
Good.
Okay.
You win.