They caught the Scranton Strangler.
They trapped him in his house.
...and then photographing them is believed to be inside.
Police have now surrounded the apartment complex.
Police are surrounded?
And we now see what appears to be a SWAT band pulling up.
SWAT, SWAT's arriving.
It is unknown if he is armed with anything...
They should do that thing where they play the really good music
to get him to come out.
Ugh, we shouldn't televised any of this.
Just say copies.
Why do you have to drag cats into this?
Okay, while this is interesting, we should get back to work.
These standoffs can last a long time.
What if it's another Waco?
It's pronounced Wacko.
Some events are so newsworthy, so historic,
that you have to stop everything to watch.
Balloon Boy, Michael Jackson's funeral.
Uh, things that if you didn't see them live,
you wouldn't really care that you didn't see them at all.
Coming to you, Michael Jackson.
I bet he's wishing he had a hybrid, right?
60 miles to the gallon in the city.
No, I bet he's wishing he was strangling someone.
Okay, that's our street.
That's our street. He's going down our street.
Okay, everybody.
Go, go, go, go.
There it is! There it is!
I saw it!
Where?
I saw it! It's gone!
It's gone!
Where?
He went right by!
He missed it.
Grandpa, where were you the day the Scranton Strangler was caught?
Well, I was there, kiddo.
I was there.
And I'll tell you what.
You go sell these and buy yourself a nice spaceship.
MUSIC
Michael.
Walk with me.
Gabe and I are having a party and everyone's invited and it's at his apartment and we're going to watch Glee.
Glee? What is Glee?
Some sort of television program.
Jim, I need that thing.
Stat.
OK.
Yeah, it's a TV show.
Dwight, sign.
No.
I don't have time for parties.
I don't have time for TV shows.
Stanley, what time is that thing that I have to do?
I...
Cancel it.
Are you still here?
It's just our first party together, so it didn't mean a lot.
Did you hear what I said?
I'm a very busy man.
I don't have time for your TV show.
OK, sorry.
I'm joking.
Wait, which one?
I'm kidding around.
I'm not actually angry.
I'm not busy at all.
I'm not doing anything.
And I know what Glee is.
I am a total Glee.
Oh, me too.
You know what my favorite character is?
The invalid.
Yes, I'd love to come to your party.
Oh my gosh.
I don't know if Michael likes Gabe that much, but there's this thing on Glee called Mashup
where two things that don't go together make one great song.
Take Gabe.
Take Michael.
You make Gabe Mike.
Best friends.
No, really?
Is there time to change this?
That show.
I mean, first they say that Mr. Shoe doesn't know anything about choreography.
And then like three episodes later, he's this fantastic choreographer.
Pick a lane, people.
And what was with Jesse's sudden turn on Rachel between Dream On and Funk?
Where the heck did that come from?
Honestly, that show, it's just, it's irresponsible.
Crossword clue.
Ten letters means time of your life.
Gabe's party.
Well, look at this.
Thank you for thinking of me.
Why the hell I got my own crazy idea for tonight?
I'm going to watch a TV show I want to watch with people I want to watch it with.
NCIS.
By myself.
Are you going?
Not going.
Not because I want to.
Of all feelings, to base a show around glee, thirst.
Now that's a show I'd watch.
I would watch that.
Tonight might be a convenient night for us to have some intercourse.
You're having a party at Gabe's apartment.
I'd love it if you were there.
You would?
You and Michael are always alive at the party.
Try and keep me from coming.
Why would I keep you from coming?
Try and hide it.
I will track this party down.
Why would I hide it?
Kevin.
Hey, you going tonight?
Yes, I am.
Are you?
Yeah, you got to go to the boss's party, right?
Mm-hmm.
What?
No, Gabe, Gabe is not the boss.
No, he's not the boss.
Why did you just say he was the boss?
Because you're the boss.
Guys, do you consider Gabe to be the boss?
Okay, technically Gabe is the boss.
He is.
Fine.
I...
You know what else he is?
He's a big weirdo.
Have you ever seen me jello with those little chunks of fruit in it?
Yeah.
That's disgusting.
He's like, I don't know, I'm not sure of the word.
It's kind of...
I don't know.
I don't know the word.
It's kind of...
He's like a...
A...
Like a...
Fiddlehead.
Figurine.
He's...
I don't know.
He's a fiddly figurine.
I don't really know Gabe.
I know that whenever I hear his name or see him, I am surprised.
And then I remember who he is.
He is...
You know, like when people discover that someone's a serial killer
and everybody says,
well, he seemed like a very nice normal guy.
That's...
I wish he was that normal.
It's a make-your-own-pizza night.
OK.
I think Gabe's place is so nice.
Uh-huh.
Look at the size of those wine glasses, Michael.
They're big.
Those posters used to be real French ads.
Oh, all right.
So, these are your cheeses, your hams, your sausages,
your herbs and your vegetables.
Here's what's been done.
Start creating.
Sometimes it helps to think of a part of the world.
OK, OK.
And then make a piece...
Gabe likes to entertain a lot.
And he cooks in an oven.
And all that jazz.
I just have a different lifestyle.
They have these bags of vegetables
that steam right inside their own bag.
So, I'll get a glass of sangria, sit down in front of TV,
a bag of vegetables.
Before you know it, I'm ready for bed.
Oh, blech.
What else do we got?
OK.
OK, oh, mini pasta.
Oh, those are actually for the kid I mentor.
Well, this is make your own pizza, right?
Yeah.
It's just one of those blood shirt.
So, I wanted to do that.
OK.
Is that good?
Can I do that?
Do you mind if I do that?
No.
Can't open her?
Yeah.
All right.
Maybe Gabe got a taste of success too young.
When I was Gabe's age, I was a junior salesman
just struggling to feed my fish.
I had to sleep on the couch because my TV was on the bed.
I was Tom Hanks in Big.
And Gabe is just so grown up and boring
like Tom Hanks in Philadelphia.
Oh, God.
You don't really toss the dough.
Try to destroy the old ways, Gabe.
I will not let you.
So, welcome to my man cave.
I did my senior year abroad in Japan.
Best year of my life.
Do you play?
Oh, I like to create soundscapes.
Imagine one instant of a song
expanded to be the size of the universe.
I can't even do that.
She's up.
Great.
Cece is reverse cycling,
which means she sleeps all day and she's up all night,
which basically means I'm up all day and I'm up all night.
And if it doesn't stop soon, I'm going to be up all night.
The show's starting.
All right, let's gather round.
Who's that?