Hello?
I need a good worker.
You're strong.
Come on.
What?
We're not going with that man.
I've seen him dating with many others and he's not coming back.
We don't go with that man.
I've seen several men go with that man and none come back.
I've lost friends.
We've lost friends.
I don't know what he does with them.
We don't know what he does with them.
I don't want to talk about it anymore.
I pick up day laborers and tell them that they'll get paid at 6 p.m.
At 5.45, a certain INS agent by the name of Mo's Shroot throws them in the back of a van,
drops them off in the middle of Harrisburg and tells them it's Canada.
Hola amigo.
Hola.
Tu es un bueno worker?
Si, yo muy bueno worker.
Y el exacto, donde are you from?
Scranton.
Y before that, La Philadelphia.
You speak English?
Yes, I'm really good at English.
Okay, good.
Me too.
Get in the car.
Okay.
Who is this guy by our cars?
That is my new maintenance worker, Nate.
And you'll be happy to know that he's taking care of that hornet's nest that you've been griping about.
I got stung up my dress.
Poor hornet.
I've left him all the tools he needs.
This is do or die.
If he chooses correctly, he'll conquer the hornets.
And if he doesn't, he'll die.
What?
Beg your pardon?
When did the phrase do or die become so corrupted?
Is that a blowtorch?
No.
No, no, no.
It's an interesting choice.
Oh, yes.
Very, very smart.
Walking away.
Go away.
No, no, no.
The bats.
What is he doing?
Oh, they're stinging him.
No, no, no.
No.
Good morning, Erin.
Any mustaches?
I mean messages?
Terrific.
There are many reasons a man would wear a fake mustache to work.
He is a fan of the outrageous.
He loves to surprise.
He loves other things as well.
Oh, wow.
Okay.
It's a pimple, Phyllis.
Avril Lavigne gets them all the time and she rocks harder than anyone alive.
That's no pimple, Michael.
You mean cancer?
What?
No.
Wait.
No, definitely not.
Not cancer.
It's just good to catch a Michael train of thought early before it derails into a
town before it derails and destroys the entire town.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
It's just a cold sore.
It is?
Yep.
Just a cold sore.
Thank you, Phyllis.
I don't have acne.
I have a cold sore.
I didn't even have a cold.
I don't know how I got it.
I know how you got it.
How?
Michael, come on.
A cold sore is herpes.
What?
What you should do, Michael, is have a doctor take a look at it because we don't really
know what that is.
I know tons and tons of people who have herpes.
I have it myself.
That's what it is.
I've never seen a herpes, have I?
Because it's on my genitals, genius.
You have a penis?
Michael, have you ever been tested for STDs?
Yeah.
My last physical one was 40.
That was like 10 years ago.
No, it was like four years ago.
Michael, you're at least 46.
Why at least?
If you're guessing 46, just say 46.
Can we please talk about how gross Meredith is?
This is what you get when you treat your body like an outhouse.
You know what, guys?
How about we just chill out a little bit on the herp chat, okay?
I was an RA in college, and I can tell you, number one sexually transmitted disease is
ignorance.
I guess maybe she could marry a meth dealer with crabs.
I don't even want to know about these things.
Hey, guys.
How did this happen?
How did I get this?
From kissing a woman.
Oh, God.
Women, am I right?
And kissing, am I right?
And infected razors, towels, dishes, and shared articles.
Sometimes it can lie dormant in a woman for years.
They may not even know that they have it.
You know what?
I feel like one of those old timey sailors with VD.
Hey, it's me own darn fault.
Girl in every port.
Find out the poop deck.
What port?
The Jan port?
The Holly port?
Don't even.
Holly was clean, okay?
If anything, I gave it to her.
You may have.
Oh, my God.
What if I did?
You need to contact Holly.
You need to notify her.
Okay.
You need to notify her that she is crawling with herpes.
You know what?
Might, might be crawling with herpes.
I might have gotten it after her.
You need to contact every woman you've been with
and notify them of your herpes infestation.
It's the right thing to do.
There's no way I'm going to do that.
Then I will.
All right.
Now, I'm no doctor, but it seems to me that we all have an obligation
to track down anyone who gives us a disease, inform them of it,
and take overwhelming revenge on that person.
Again, I'm no doctor.
I'm just a normal guy who enjoys revenge.
Hello?
Hi, Donna.
It's Michael.
Michael, I didn't think I'd hear from you.
How have you been?
I have a disease for which there is no known cure
that has been sexually transmitted to me.
Oh, no.
I can't even say it.
H-I-R-P-E-E-S.
Wait, you're calling to tell me that you have herpes?
No, I am calling to see if you gave me herpes,
because if you did, I would be able to avoid a lot of sucky conversations.
So you have it, right?
No.
Does your stupid husband have it?
No, he doesn't.
Are you telling me I have to get tested?
Yes, I'm telling you, you have to get tested for herpes.
Goodbye.
So long, Donna.
It's like the Sea Shepherd's worst nightmare
is not the Japanese whalers, but their own incompetence.
Wow, I should really be watching this.
Oh, definitely.
It's always the case, even in Antarctica.
Okay, Jim.
Hey.
No.
No, not at all.
Mm.
Well, didn't go as bad as you'd think, considering the subject matter.
No, once you say the word herpes, that's the hard part,
and then they're the uncomfortable one.
Excuse me, everyone, can I have your attention, please?
Not again.
What do you mean, again?
You're all right.
I'm fine.
Excuse me, everyone, can I have your attention, please?
Not again.
What do you mean, again?
You're always asking for our attention.
No, maybe like a year ago.
Mm, seems recent.
No, that's...
Andy, the reason it seems more recent
is because many of us here have never stood up
and asked for everyone's attention,
and it seems like you've done it on several occasions.
Everyone, I've noticed that we've not been entirely kind to one of our own
due to stigmas and prejudices.
Oh, when you got your new phone,
that's when you asked for everyone's attention.
Again, you kept announcing scores.
To world's only international sports.
This is Holly.
No, this is Holly.
No, this is Michael Scott.
Busted.
So what can I do for you, Holly?
I'm calling because there was a terrible car accident.
Oh, really? Was anyone killed?
A lot of people.
Any nuns?
Three nuns. Missionaries from South Africa.
Were they in the missionary position?
Holly brings out a sense of childlike wonder in Michael.
I don't like it.
Childlike wonder leads to a childlike grave.
Hot pizza, check it and see.
Got a whole bunch of pepperoni.
Yeah. Now you're looking at me.
The diagnosis?