Next up, Secretary Shroot will read the minutes from Sunday's meeting.
Minutes from previous meeting of Knights of the Night.
No, Jim, hey.
Oh, this meeting is for Knights of the Night only.
Knights of the Night are volunteer crime patrollers.
We are often compared to the Guardian Angels, but we could not be more different from them.
Seriously, we are nothing like the Guardian Angels.
I mean, broad strokes purposes.
Sure.
Think Guardian Angels.
One of our many recent good deeds, we set out to capture the Scranton Strangler.
Mission accomplished.
Not by us.
Get the phone.
One, two, three.
Dwight, Dwight, break it up, break it up.
Break it up. He's also a Knight. Break it up.
Listen up.
Every reaction has an equal and opposite reaction.
Go ahead.
Oh, oh, what's this? Oh, oh, what's this? Oh, no.
What do you have this for, huh? What is this?
Dwight, Dwight, Dwight, break it up, break it up.
Pack it in the shirt. Read it.
We are unarmed.
Come on.
I'm actually just looking for my Blackberry, so carry on.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
I see how this movie ends.
You make fun of me, everyone laughs, ha, ha, ha.
Screw you.
Dwight, don't be bothered by your friend's presence.
What are you going to do now?
You're going to make fun of our leader's weird voice, huh?
Dwight, don't be bothered by...
Over the line, Jim.
I'm just looking for my phone, so pretend I'm not here.
Fine.
Minutes from previous meeting of Knights of the Knight.
It's our official name, Jim.
Sounds good.
Reflective strips were glued to patrol jackets.
Knights went outside with flashlights to test them.
Smart.
And the rest was just boilerplate stuff.
Go ahead and read it. Some people weren't here.
Okay.
Knights stayed outside to play flashlight tag.
Oh, come on, that sounds awesome.
It was pretty cool.
It was fun.
It was pretty awesome.
You didn't get me!
I didn't get my key!
My flashlight broke.
Hey!
Yeah.
No, I got it.
Just leaving now.
January 3, 2011.
A day which will live in famously.
Holly Partridge-Flax, otherwise known as Holly,
otherwise, otherwise known as a living, breathing angel,
is engaged to another man.
This is freaking me out.
I...
Okay, let's just switch to the happy video, okay?
No, no, no, no. Let's push through.
We'll do this.
Today we'll either be back in the room,
or we'll be back in the room.
No, let's push through. We'll do this.
Today will either be the best or the worst day of my life.
Holly gave AJ an ultimatum.
He either proposes by New Year's or they break up.
Now, if she's engaged, I'm gonna go crazy,
and I'm gonna start attacking people.
If she's not engaged, in all honesty,
I may just burn this whole place to the ground out of happiness.
Either way, I am going to need some talking down,
and nobody talks me down like myself in a video talking me down.
Michael, I know what you're thinking.
Holly is engaged to somebody else, and you want to kill yourself.
That may seem like a good idea, but it's not.
It's not.
Sorry, it sounded like you said it's snot. I'm so sorry.
Okay, so killing yourself.
I'm just thinking about snot.
Good morning.
Hey, guys. Fun thing.
The index cards on your desk are resolution cards.
You write your New Year's resolution on them.
I'll collect them, and then display the cards on...
Da-da-da-da!
This resolution board.
Wow. Did your baby draw that?
The glitter is blinding.
I think it's good. It's gonna be fun.
I recently met Sue, the office administrator at Vance Refrigeration.
She has this awesome wall full of fun initiatives and morale boosters and stuff.
Sue just goes for it. She's awesome.
I know, Sue. She's not that great.
And you know her husband's in a wheelchair, right?
Okay. Champagne.
Happy.
Sponge.
Sad. To soak up my tears.
Gummy bears and gummy worms.
Bears sad, worms happy. Come on, Erin.
Ugelele's happy.
Sad. Something to break.
Chocolates.
For you. Job well done.
Thank you.
Two bottles of scotch.
Both sad.
And did you get the tickets?
I did. I did indeed.
Two front row centers. A Paula Poundstone live with the Kipsey.
Holly's favorite.
I hope she doesn't call us up on stage. That would suck.
Hey, you think you could do my job better?
I don't know. What's your name, Michael?
I'm really excited for Michael either way.
Because if Holly chooses to be with him, he will be so, so happy.
And if not, he'll be avoiding the biggest mistake of his life.
Oh, hey, guys. I'd like to introduce you to a new little friend of mine.
His name is New Year's Resolution Board.
Sha. Shut up. Hello.
What happened? Is there a ring?
So, high five me. We're back. To a happy new...