I got a delivery for you.
Leave it at reception.
I'm supposed to deliver this one in person.
Clean up on aisle five.
After three years of writing, one year of shooting, four years of reshooting, and two years of editing,
I have finally completed my movie, Threat Level Midnight.
Yes?
What are you doing?
Guys, did you guys know that our own Michael Scott has made a movie and that he maybe will
let us watch it, but only if everybody's dying to see it?
That's, well, don't put words in my mouth.
Threat Level Midnight is the great lost film of Michael Scott.
We're all in it from like years and years ago.
It's like a home movie.
Yeah, if Michael Scott did your home movie.
Michael screened a work in progress for us years ago, and it didn't go well.
We thought it was a comedy.
Everything pointed to it being a comedy.
We'd love to see it.
Sweet.
I will go invite Holly.
Okay, everyone, I know we're really excited to see this movie that everybody's in, but
we have to remember that Michael is sensitive, so let's stay positive.
And no laughing, no comments, just positive energy, and we'll have a pure fun day.
Okay?
Thanks, Mom.
You never told me you made a movie.
It's got actions, it's got hearts, it's got symbolism.
It's got you.
It's got a lot of me.
I can't wait.
Ladies and gentlemen, Threat Level Midnight.
Michael Scott?
Well, that is an interesting story.
He was once the best secret agent in the business.
That was years ago.
Where is he now?
Well, that's also an interesting story.
Okay.
Master Scarn.
Master Scarn?
I play Samuel, Michael Scarn's robot butler.
I wanted Samuel's voice to be like this, but Michael thought that Samuel should be a very
advanced android, almost indistinguishable from a real person.
Dwight does not play a robot.
I'm up.
It's the president.
He needs you for a mission.
Tell him I'm retired.
It's golden phase.