Hey Oscar, big Will and Grace fan, huh?
No. Everybody assumes I am. I always give them as gifts.
Oh. Dunder Mifflin is having our first ever garage sale.
Like many Americans, we realized we had a lot of things that we didn't really need.
And ten cents of every dollar is going into the party fund so we can throw parties for ourselves.
Finally got up. Cut that off the wall.
Looks like we're in the Spice District.
Yep.
Taking a ride on Spice Mountain.
People!
People! Look alive! It's show time!
Doors open in three, two, one!
Ooh, yikes.
It's cold, White. Just shut the door and let people come in the front.
It's good that it's cold. It will drive business inside.
The signs will drive business inside.
The warmth will lure people inside.
This is how business works. I'm not closing the door.
Close it.
Uh oh. Looks like someone's signs a little crooked.
Looks awful.
Need a thumbtack? Sure. Not so fast.
Shrewts are farmers by hobby and traders by trade.
Through the art of the swap, I will walk out of this garage sale with the finest item here.
I will trade you for the used candle.
Forget you.
Come on. It's trash. Like your sign unless you have this.
Fine. Just get it.
That's how it's done.
Whoa. I love her. How much for that?
I, uh, I actually don't know why I brought that because it's kind of priceless.
Ten dollars.
No, I paid five hundred dollars for that.
Two hundred. Five hundred. Twenty. Forty-five. Get lost.
Damn it.
And that is how you do it.
You know, we don't have to sell that if you don't want.
If it's a problem with the neon, I can have my neon guy take a look.
No, but you know what? It's really more for a bachelor pad. I just want to get a fair price.
Well, we could put it in storage in case.
In case? In case of what?
You know, in case maybe something changes.
I don't have it in case. Do you have it in case?
No.
How much for the slip and slide?
Get lost.
Yes. Hello, Mr. Flax. This is Michael Scott, your daughter's boss.
I am calling because I am going to have to fire your daughter Holly
because she's such a terrible employee.
I'm just kidding. I'm kidding.
I'm actually calling because I'm in love with her.
I love your daughter and I have for some time.
And I would like to discuss my intentions with you, which are to ask her to marry me.
And I was just hoping that you would give me your approval.
And this isn't a joke. So call me back when you get this.
I'll take this and I look forward to speaking. Thank you.
Are you serious? A half-used candle?
Get out of here, Dwight. You're blocking my table with your giant body.
Oh, because there's a huge line of people who want your spinster tchotchkes.
Screw you, man. People like my stuff.
People like Ryan?
Let me tell you about men like him.
He comes over and you're like, hey, baby, let me light a candle.
And you pull out this one, half-used.
He's like, who else is she seeing? I better lock her down fast.
You can take my Helen Fielding collection.
And the Jennifer Weiner collection.
Oh my gosh, you have the Dallas board game?
Yeah. When I was a kid, I was on Dallas.
Really?
Yeah. We missed our connecting flight and we spent the entire day on Dallas.
Then we spent a week on Hawaii. I was on heaven.
We should play it.
Well, there's no instructions.
It's Dallas. The game. We can figure it out.
Yeah. I'm pretty good at board games.
Well, shall we make it a little interesting?
Sure.
What is this?
How did those get out? I'm sorry.
Professor Copperfield's Miracle Lagoons?
I was in Jamaica and I got lost.
And it was getting dark this one night and then out of nowhere,
this guy comes with a cart and he's selling these.
Dwight, he told me things about myself that there's no way he could have known.
That's a common swindler's trick.
Probably. Probably.
So I buy some. I turn the corner. I feel like an idiot.
So I go back to get my money. He was gone.
So you want to sell me magic beans?
Correction, I do not want to sell you Professor Copperfield's Miracle Lagoons.
Nice try. No, correction. Terrible try.
Michael called Dad?
Your friend Michael, yes. What's going on?
I think I know, but I'll sound stupid if I'm wrong. Is Dad there?
Hollis? Hi, Dad.
There was a program on TV about India.
Okay. Did you connect with Michael?
You want to watch it?
I'm not there, Dad. I'm in Pennsylvania.
What are you doing there?
I live here. Can I talk to you about Michael?
I'll put your mother on.
No, no, no, Dad.
Holli?
Mom, Dad can't seem to focus on a subject.
Don't you worry about him. He's got me.
Well, who do you have?
I have your father. He's right here. I'll put him on.
No, Mom.
Dunder Mifflin, this is Gabe. How may I direct your call?
I've been demoted.
No, I'm just holding down the fort.
Aaron's job is so easy.
Your mail. Sealed with a kiss. My own personal touch.
And I'm done with the mail.
Oh, which one's decaf?
Michael?
Michael! Michael! Hey!
Hi!
I was just coming out to see what you were doing and maybe stop you.
Oh, you know what? Do you have a siphon? I think I'm going to run out of gas.
Why do you need more gas?
Well, I'm writing a message.
Is it a good message or a bad message?
I'm asking Holly a question in fire.
Are you proposing?
Maybe.
Oh, you know what? I've got gas on my hands and my shoes.
Would you light it? Do the honors, please.
Yeah, yeah, no problem.
Pam?
Yep?
Could you light this, please?
Michael, you've had two ideas today.
And one of them was great. And the other one was terrible.
I am not in the mood for riddles, Pam.
This is terrible.
No, this is romantic.
You know what? I'm going to get a hose and then we'll talk about it.
Okay, we'll figure it out. I'll be right back. Just stay there.
I'm going to ask Holly to marry me today.
Free sample?
My mom makes the best pesto in the world.
And I always tell her, Mom, you should sell this. You'd make a fortune.
And she always says, no, it's just for family.
Well, finally, I was like, f*** it, I'll sell it.
So I'm like, Mom, I need you to make a ton of pesto for a pesto party for all my friends.
She's like, oh, okay. Pesto party? Really?
Anyway, she makes like a hundred bottles worth. It's so good.
And Phyllis just had that mom look I wanted.