We could get D'Angelo flowers.
No, you can't get flowers for someone who's in a coma that won't before he wakes up.
Yeah, that's true.
All in favor of the baskets full of chocolates, teddy bears, and balloons?
Wait, wait. All in favor of the knapsack filled with canned goods, chainsaw, gasoline, and emergency radio in case he wakes up post-apocalypse?
Nope, baskets have it.
So as it turns out, unless you're a young child or a prison inmate, you don't need anyone supervising you.
People just come in and do their work on their schedule.
Imagine that. People like us allowed to sell paper, unsupervised, and yet somehow it works.
Must be because the stakes are so high.
Well, I really appreciate the offer, but I'm just happy the way things are.
Okay. Thank you.
That was Joe asking me if I wanted to take over as acting manager while they find a replacement.
I told her I don't want to mess this up, right? There's a consensus. People are happy.
Dwight Schrute?
Yes, I would.
Thank you.
Jordan, gather my things from my desk.
Wait.
What have you done?
Rose, you'll never guess where I am right now.
I'm sorry.
You can't stay there all day.
I'm coming.
Do I at least get to go with you in this fantasy?
You'll slow me down.
Dwight has been acting manager for three months now?
Nope, a week. Just feels like three months.
Let's see. We all have to punch into a time clock, which is very old, very strong, and has the slot about the size of a finger.
We were all given new business cards, big enough to set us apart from the competition, which is how I learned that our titles are all now junior employee.
Our lunch breaks are staggered to prevent wasting time. Mine's at 10.30, and I find that the first hour of the day goes by a lot quicker than the second seven hours.
Stop stalling.
Come on.
I pledge allegiance to the flag of the United States of America, and to the republic for which it stands, one nation, under God, indivisible, with liberty and justice for all.
Amen.
Excellent. Morning announcements.
There's been a problem with some people sharing copier codes. Your copier code is a distinct 21-digit number that is unique to you, and you only. Okay? Don't share it.
Joe Bennett, our CEO, will be here today for a high-level meeting involving Gabe and myself.
Ooh, about what?
That's on a need-to-know basis.
I thought I needed to know for your calendar.
General meet and greet.
So I expect you to be on your best behavior, which means none of you will be insubordinate, nor will you foment insurrection.
Question. If we've already fomented insurrection, may we be grandfathered in?
Define foment.
You define foment.
Please take note of the new color-coding system.
I will convince Joe to make me permanent manager by raising efficiency. No conference room meetings, no internet.
This is a high-powered cell phone jammer I got off the black market. Although if I keep it too close to my genitals, I could have children with freakish mutations or powers.
Aha!
Oh my God, what is wrong with you?
Gotcha! Why are you late?
It's none of your business, actually. It's very medical and personal.
All right. You stop me when I reach the diseased area.
I was signing up to audition for American Idol. I think I have a really good shot. My only fear is that they say you can't have talent representation, and I do.
In fairness, Daryl did tell me that joke, so I feel like I can say it.
Daryl's funny.
I know, right?
Hey, Andy?
Yeah?
Can I talk to you a second about these client memos?
Sure.
What's going on?
Are you still in love with Erin?
What?
Because I am. I need to get her back. I can't be alone anymore. Andy, do you like being alone with me right now?
No, this is horrifying.
No, I don't like being alone with me either. Okay? I have to get Erin back. Are you still going to date her?
We're just friends, okay?
Do you promise that?
Yeah, fine. I promise. We'll never date again. Can we go outside now?
No, just give me a second. I don't want anyone to know I've been crying.
Hey, hey, hey, hey. What do you think you're doing? What's this? What's the fist?
Oh, it's just a social club. You know, like the French Revolution or the Black Panthers or Communism. It's just a club. Guys talking, you know.
You expect me to believe that you're starting a rebellion?
Nope, social club. God, I hate when everybody calls us a rebellion.
Okay, you know what? I would love to join the fist.
And we would love to have you, but not today. Unfortunately, it's a bad day. What with Operation Overthrow and everything. But I have noted it.
Okay.
One.
Pam, I have to show you this video. You're gonna love it. It's Beyonce falling. The fart mixed in.
Oh.
For ten years, I've been picturing this very moment. And now that it's here, it's exactly as I imagined.
This desk is an exact replica of Uday Hussein's desk. I don't support his actions, but you can't argue with his taste.
And you tried growing up with a father like that. I did. On a smaller scale.
This is a 3D wolf.
The samurai is the most mighty of warriors.
And this is a letter opener. Or is it?
Thunder Mifflin!
It's Beaumont Adams. It's over 120 years old. A.K.A. the Widowmaker.
Isn't he a cute piranha? Come on, boy. Here you go.
No food now? Someone has to do something about Dwight.
He put some snacks in the freezer for us.
You mean the frozen mice for the piranha?
No, the blueberry slurpee pouch.
He means the ice pack.
Well, maybe we should talk to Joe.
And say what?