Well, I'm moving to Colorado to start my new life with Holly.
Just up here getting used to the altitude.
Michael?
Yes?
I've got a treat for you.
Oh, thank you.
Like a butler.
Colorado specialty, Rocky Mountain oysters.
Oh, those do not taste like oysters.
That's because they're not oysters.
They're bull testicles.
I cut them off fresh this morning.
Ha!
Sick freak.
What is wrong with you?
I'm the sick freak?
Yeah.
After what you did?
You expect to be butled after you didn't recommend me?
Wait, I don't own Dermiflin, okay?
The job was not mine to give.
Look, I need your advice on something.
I am told that there are bears in the Rockies.
Where did you hear that?
Obvious XM radio?
Well, I was just thinking that maybe I should keep a salami in my pocket.
Great idea.
In order to feed the bears.
Especially if you think that life would be better without legs.
How do you mean?
Black bears can smell a salami at five miles, Michael.
What are you thinking?
And they run faster than a horse.
So if you were thinking about outrunning them on a horse, I would try a cheetah.
You in tight pants, Michael, are a salami to a black bear.
Do you understand?
You're like a giant walking salami.
Okay, so no salami in the pants.
How about a pepperoni?
Any kind of meat you can possibly name.
Okay.
You're not going to take all your toys, are you?
I mean, you don't have a job lined up, so it's not like you have a desk to put them
on.
Well, I have interviews.
That's nice.
How about that truck?
Can I have this little truck?
It's like I might glue a stapler on top or put a hole here and stick pins in it.
Are you okay?
Yes.
You know what?
Take my favorite truck, sure.
It's your last couple days.
I'm going to get out of your hair.
Oh, you don't.
That's...
I will be in the break room.
Okay.
That sounds good.
Thank you.
Dead man walking.
Sad?
No.
I don't leave until tomorrow, so tomorrow I will be a wreck.
Stay away from Aaron.
Hey, I'm your boss.
Why don't you stay away from me?
No, I'm going to stay away from Aaron one, okay?
You don't want to get on my bad side.
I've seen some horrible things.
I own over 200 R movies.
Okay, that's so weird.
Just go away.
No, you go away.
Hi, Juno.
You guys are filming people when they go to the bathroom now?
How about cupcakes?
Please.
What's wrong with cupcakes?
Everything.
There they are.
Party planning committee together again.
Well, we all wanted to plan your goodbye party.
We thought this would be easier.
We thought.
It's an experiment.
The three of us have all been chairman before.
So this is the dream team.
Hey.
What are you saying?
The dream team and Meredith.
We decided on the ice cream.
Mint chocolate chip, your favorite.
Yeah, that was a surprise.
You know what?
I'm thinking maybe we should get ice cream that everybody will like.
How about vanilla?
Let's get vanilla.
Okay.
Tomorrow I want everybody to have a good time.
No drama.
And as for today, just a typical day.
Alright?
Should we get toppings?
What do you like, Pam?
What?
What kind of topping would you like?
Hot fudge?
Sounds good.
Fudge it up.
I bought this for myself.
And yesterday, they gave me this.
I still need something to drink out of, though.
Attention, everyone.
Before I leave tomorrow, I would like to reveal a secret that I have kept for over 20 years.
Secret about Phyllis.
Please, Michael.
When Phyllis was in high school, she was so cute.
And she still is.
I thought he knew about the baby I gave away.
Look, Michael, it's a going away present so your hands won't get cold.
Ah.
It's almost done, but you can't get them wet and they can't be dry cleaned either.
You have to hand wash without water, ring dry gently, and use a hairdryer on cool.
Sounds great.
I just think it's great.
Oh, I have gifts as well.
And I will start by giving the first gift to Phyllis.
Phyllis, you are shy and sweet.
And you don't often speak your mind, but you should because you have great ideas.
So, Phyllis, I am giving you this so you can always remember to speak your mind.
Oh, gee, thanks, Michael.
You're welcome.
It's cute.
Stanley, I love your sudoku and your puzzles.
I bestow upon you my felt.
May you never lose the fun-loving quality in life.
Where's the rest of it? It's got no balls.
Well, okay.
And Andy.
Andy, who needs confidence that he is a great salesman.
I give you my clients.
Our ten most important accounts.
Wow.
Excuse me, what?
Yeah, wow.
You know I'm no worse salesman here, right?
But you're the best salesman on the inside.
What does that even mean?
You sold us all on Andy.
A product that nobody wanted.
I'm going to lose them.
You're not going to lose them.
I promise you that I will.
Just do your best.
I have faith in you.
Give me those clients.
Do you believe that?
I've given up expecting Michael to do the right thing.
Or the decent thing or even the comprehensible thing.
I used to be obese.
Once you've conquered obesity, everything else is easy.
Life literally moves in slow motion.
I'm not saying I'm Superman.
But let me just put it this way.
If I were shot in the head, I'm pretty sure everything would be fine.
I almost welcome it.
Kevin, I have something for you.
Oh.
You know who that is?
Don't be a caricature, Kevin.
Never be a caricature.
How did that feel when I tore that up?
Better.
Good.
Stand up.
You will be thin.
You won't drool over pizza like an animal anymore.
But...
You will find love.
Michael, I'm pretty much okay with who I am now.
Don't be.
You should never settle for who you are.
Oscar, Oscar, Oscar.
Oscar, you are...
Michael, I just lost Porter Hardware.
I lost him.
Okay.
You know what?
Just do your best, buddy.
Okay.
Oscar, you are very smart.
And you have a gigantic education.
And I think of you as my scarecrow because you gave me a brain.
So that's why I made you this.
Thank you, Michael.
It's beautiful.
It looks like...
It looks like it was made by a two-year-old monkey on a farm.
And he just...
He just accepted that I put all this work into it.
Oh, man.
He has the lowest opinion of me, of anybody.
Oh!
Mr. Lawson, what you need to know is that you're my client.
And since you're my client, I think about you night and day.
That came out weird.
It's not like I masturbate at the thought of you or something.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Please, don't do anything over the phone.
Can I be honest with you?
I'm intimidated by your incredibly deep voice right now.
And I'd just love the chance to come in in person and make a final plea, please.
Yes, thank you.
Bye.
Thank you.
I'll give you a dollar for the rest of your clients.
Think about it.
Was it just me, or did you think we were going to have sex at some point?
It was just you.
How would you have wanted to do it?
I don't...
Okay, okay.
You know what?
Inappropriate, because I am engaged happily, and you, you have landed yourself a senator.
State senator.
Mm-hmm.
Bravo.