I have the best stocked survival shelter in northeastern Pennsylvania, but everything
has a shelf life, so I must eat and then replace everything that's about to expire.
It's nice not to have to plan my meals.
You're eating eight-year-old tomatoes.
They're still good for another week.
You know, I think I might have some type of cheese in the back of my fridge you might
like.
I've got some cheese you might like, too.
I'm between my toes.
Hurty-harr-harr.
All right, picture this.
Snowy ash drizzles from the sky.
A rabid pack of dogs surrounds you as the flame at the end of your stick dies out.
There's only one hope left for you, the door to my shelter.
You pound, you beg, Dwight, please let me in, but I ignore your cries and do not let
you in.
You want to know why?
Because of the sign that says no pounding, no begging.
No, because you laughed at me.
Kevin will be eaten.
Pam will be taken slave.
Jim will be made a warlord's jester.
Meredith will do okay.
Be assured, this day will come.
It's just a matter of time.
Could be one month, could be two months.
Three months.
Could be.
Four months.
I can see that happening.
Yes.
Eight months.
That's a realistic timeline.
Eleven months.
Perhaps.
Okay, wait, now really think hard about this one.
One year.
I could see that as a very real possibility.
494 months.
I could see that happening.
495 months.
That's just...
You are going to love her.
You are going to love Holly.
All I care is if she likes me.
I want to get off the road.
My butt skin can't handle another four hour ride to Binghamton.
Your butt skin is in my hands now.
Welcome home.
Sometimes I'd wake up and not know what state I was in.
New York, Pennsylvania.
I got sick of it.
The not knowing.
The back and forth.
I really thought I was becoming too much of a womanizer.
I realized I had shirts in five different women's houses.
Still not seeing the bra in there.
All right.
Truth is, I got a couple love bumps on my ding-dongs.
I was like, oh, game over.
It was the best of times.
It was the awesomest of times.
And now Packer wants to come home.
And oh, look who's here to sign off on it.
My boo, Holly.
Hi.
You must be Todd.
Whoa.
I'm sorry, Michael.
I thought we were meeting Holly today, not Jennifer Aniston.
Ha, ha, ha.
That's very funny.
Okay, let's get started.
After you.
Okay.
Oh, Michael, this will be just us.
Ah, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Just so you know, he's at his funniest when you've given him like five shots.
Okay.
And it also helps if you've had five shots.
I already have.
Oh.
Why is Packer back?
Was Packer here?
Why is he talking to Holly?
Don't, no, don't care.
Do you have any more questions for me?
No.
I just want to add one last thing.
I spend a lot of time on the road listening to music.
And one of my favorite artists is John Cougar Melloncamp.
He sings about the importance of hometowns.
Holly, this is my hometown.
And this branch is my little pink house.
Well, Michael loves you and your sales speak for themselves.
Oh.
Yes, the Packer's back.
Ladies and gentlemen, I would like to introduce you to a man who needs no introduction, probably
because most of you have done it with him.
Just kidding.
You wouldn't be interested in any of you.
In all seriousness, Todd Packer is a permanent salesman at this branch.
And I would like to invite you now to welcome him with open arms.
Yes.
What?
It's great to be among friends.
And until then, you suckers will do.
Nice.
We got burned.
You did.
You got burned because Packer's back.
Packer is turning in his car for a desk.
He is turning in his condoms for a condom medium.
Although he's probably going to have to use condoms from here on out.
Holly, you approved this?
Yes, I did.
I think Todd's going to make a great addition to the staff.
You did approve it?
Yeah.
What don't you understand about the word approved?
It seems a couple of you don't know what the word approved means.
I have very little patience for stupidity.
Sorry we're late.
Gabe fell in the shower.
Such a clutz.
Man, it took the fire department forever to get there.
Oh my God.
Where did this come from?
Who did this?
I got Erin a new computer because the one at reception sucked.
I should know.
And I don't want to say the other one was old, but its IP number was 1.
I love it.
You can have two boxes open at one time.
It's not hot.
Oh my gosh, there's so much room down here.
I can have crazy legs.
I don't want to say my computer was bad because I was really grateful for it.
But usually it was quicker for me to drive over to the library and do my computer stuff
there and then drive back.
Thank you, Pam.
You're welcome.
My pleasure.
Can I do something for you?
Just help someone out.
It feels good.
Nice.
You know, I cleaned up our daughter for like an hour at 4 a.m. this morning, so.
So you know the feeling.
Special delivery for Dwight K. Schrute.
I didn't order anything.
Man, I don't have anything for you, but I do want to talk to you about something.
We have been thinking about where Packer should sit, and we can't just sit around waiting
for Creed to die.
There's a lot of seats in the annex.
So you wouldn't mind permanently relocating so that Packer can take this desk here.
Thanks, man.
It'd mean a lot to me.
I've been sitting here for 10 years, Michael.
Well, I was there for 12 years.
Plus, my name's carved under the desk.
No, it is not.
It is too.
Where?
Let me see this.
Right there.
Check it out.
Michael, I don't want to move desks.
Don't be a baby.
Okay, there it is.
Packer was here, and so was your mom.
Yeah.
Do I have any say in this?
No.
20 to watch, Albert.
Hey, whose dirt box is this?
That's our Zen garden.
What are you growing here, bullcrap?
Hey, Holly.
Hey.
What's up, guys?
Don't what's up us.
You think you're so cute with your pretty blonde hair.
Whoa, whoa.
Pull it back.
Um, why did you hire Todd Packer?
He's...