Got it.
Alright.
Yeah!
Okay, let's go in.
I'm freezing.
People, wait, wait, wait.
Come back, come back.
One fun one.
We're gonna do a fun one.
Okay.
One Charlie's Angels.
One.
Let's go.
Okay.
This is just a Christmas card from your paper supplier.
No one's putting this on their fridge.
Oh, I got it.
You guys, how about this?
Michael, what if all the boys are on one side, all the girls are on the other?
The boys are like, why-ye-ye-awda, and the girls are like, let's go shopping.
Let's just jump in the air.
That's it.
Let's do a picture.
Yes, jump in the air.
We're gonna jump in the air.
Here we go.
Okay.
One, two, three.
Not everyone jumped.
Okay, everybody jump in the air this time, please.
Here we go.
One, two, three.
Still some people not jumping.
You gotta be kidding me.
Who isn't jumping?
I'll tell you who.
Guys.
Daryl, Phyllis, Stanley, Angela, and Oscar.
I am jumping.
You are?
Yes, I'm jumping.
Let me see you jump.
Oh my god.
This is a store-bought camera.
This isn't one of those special military-grade cameras that would be able to capture that.
I'm freezing.
Also, Erin is jumping way too early.
She's on the ground by three.
I don't want to miss it.
Well, if we all jump really high, we'll be in the air longer.
Here's a question nobody's asking.
Is this worth it?
Don't answer that.
People, listen up and listen good.
We need to just get one picture where we're all in the air at the same time.
Yes?
I believe in us.
We can do this.
Okay, I'm three.
Everyone in the air.
Three, two, one, zero.
Just...
Save the joke.
We didn't get it.
I'm the office administrator now, which means I'm basically being paid to be head of the
party planning committee.
The first thing I did as head, I shut it down.
At its worst, it was a toxic political club used to make others feel miserable and left
out.
At its best, it planned parties.
It hardly looks fake.
It's so lush.
Why does it smell real?
Ah.
Come on.