Wow. Late every day this week.
We signed CC up for this daycare. It's on the other side of town.
The traffic is...
Why didn't I think of this before? Did you know that there is a daycare center opening right here in this building?
Is there really?
Now that I own the building, I'm looking for new sources of revenue.
And a daycare center?
Well, I guess it's not an evil idea. It's just a regular idea.
But there's no good laugh for a regular idea.
Welcome to the Sesame Avenue Daycare Center for Infants and Toddlers.
Ah!
You remember my cousin, Moe's?
Welcome, children.
Were you painting in the dark?
Wait, is this your place, Dwight?
Oh, no, no. I like to think of it as the kids' place.
Would you like a tour?
I don't think we really need...
Oh, let's take the tour, Pam.
Yeah.
Come on.
Here is the language skills and cognitive development area.
These are English, uh, letters.
I see you found our magical toy box, Jim.
These are actually forks and knives from the break room.
Jim, to you and me maybe, but come on.
To a child's imagination, that's Mr. Fork and Lieutenant Knife and Miss Fork.
And a soy sauce packet.
Oh, that's a good one.
Miss Fork.
And a soy sauce packet.
Oh.
That shouldn't have been in there. I'm embarrassed.
Don't beat yourself up.
We come fully equipped with a restroom, feeding trough, play bucket,
and room for a plant in success.
Who will be watching the children?
No one. The door locks from the outside. Escape is impossible.
Prove it.
What?
We're gonna head outside. Give it a whirl.
I just want to see how it works.
Oh, no, no, no.
I'll tell you this.
If this works out, I think we're looking real good.
I promise you, that door locks.
This is the worst. This is the worst.
You were the worst. I hate looking at your face. I want to smash it.
Okay, you know what? I made a mistake.
I committed corporate punishment.
My bad. It's over. It's done.
But my punishment is worse than hell.
Michael's been assigned six hours of mandatory counseling
with a trained professional.
I actually have a degree in social work.
I mean, I know a lot of people would just ask a few standard questions
and tick off a few boxes, but chances are some good here.
I know what you want to ask me.
Do your mom ever see you naked?
We can do this with more privacy.
So you can molest me? Okay, I don't think so.
We're going to leave the blinds open
so everybody can see what a big failure you are.
That's the key.
Boycott the Steamtown Mall!
Everyone, you heard me.
Cancel all your businesses with the Steamtown Mall.
I don't do boycotts. I am done with boycotts.
The New York Duds, 1968.
We had had enough.
A bunch of us got together.
Black, white, color didn't matter.
We marched on Kellogg's.
Two scoops of raisins in my ass.
Those of us still around got together last year and had a laugh.
We were fifth graders. What do we know?
The mall itself or the stores in the mall?
All of it. The mall, the stores, kiosks.
America's one big mall.
Did something happen?
Yeah, something happened. Oh, yeah.
Something happened, Jim.
Tell us what it is.
I mean, it would really help to get some context
so we can get on board.
You don't want to know.
Would you like to imagine a place that you feel very peaceful?
For me, it's the walk from the yogurt shop to my car
after I dropped my daughter off on Sunday afternoons.
I'm glad Michael's getting help.
He has a lot of issues and he's stupid.
Look, I'm not going to tell you that we have lower prices.
Is price something that is important to you?
Okay. Well, let me know if anything changes.
Pam?
I can't do this.
I don't have this sales gene or whatever it is.
Tell me everything's going to be okay.
Everything's going to be okay.
Tell me I'm good at sales.
You're good at sales.
The unfair thing about working in sales is that your salary is almost all commission.
So if you suck at sales, you make almost no money.
I guess that's fair.
Dwight?
What?
Did you call all my clients at the mall and cancel all my business while using the F word?
Yes, I did. And I'm going to do the same with all of your clients.
No, you will not.
Oh, yes, I will. That mall is corrupt.
Okay, they're appearances.
Okay, Dwight, we can't do that. So why don't you just tell us what happened?
Yeah, what happened, Dwight?
Okay.
You guys know me. You know that I'm not one for fancy things, but there was this one thing.
I was in a fancy store and it caught the corner of my eye when I took Moe's down to the mall to get his blood pressure at the Rite Aid.
I thought, you know, maybe I deserved this.
You know, I've had a great crop yield this fall.