I know a lot of us have been feeling under the weather lately.
It's that time of year.
And according to a study done by the University of Arizona,
they discovered that your keyboards have hundreds of times more bacteria
per square inch than a toilet seat.
I heard your mama has more bacteria per square inch than a toilet seat.
That's true, that's true. I dated her mama. And you know what?
Stop.
One of the simplest ways to cut down on the spread of germs
is to use something called the vampire cough.
Did you say vampire?
Oh no, it's just that if a vampire had to cough, you would do it like this.
Cough, cough.
Uh huh, right. And ruin their cloaks.
Do you have any idea how expensive wool is in Transylvania?
Because of the euro.
Well other things you can do to help cut down on the spread of disease
are to wash your hands regularly,
don't come in if you're sick,
and get your flu shot.
Also, I'm going to set up hand sanitizing stations around the office.
No, no, no. They will cost you your life.
Elaborate.
All you can do for your immune system is to coddle it.
They need to fight their own battles.
If Sabre really cared about our well-being,
they would set up hand desanitizing stations.
A simple bowl at every juncture filled with dirt, vomit, fecal matter.
Exposing yourself to germs is the best way to make yourself stronger.
So by that rationale, if I had to sneeze, I should just sneeze on you.
Yes, I would welcome it.
Ah!
You're welcome.
The principle is sound.
To avoid illness, expose yourself to germs,
enabling your immune system to develop antibodies.
Hitch!
I don't know why everyone doesn't do this.
Maybe they have something against living forever.
Jim, Pam, and the precious bundle of God's best everything.
I wish you both a pleasant day.
And you too.
Yes. Praise God.
Okay.
Cece's getting christened today.
Big day.
Everyone from work is here.
We weren't planning on that.
Nope.
Top of the Sunday morning to you.
And the top of the day to you too, sir.
I'm sorry.
Hope you brought your pipes.
We're about to smoke the opium and the masses.
Oh, yes.
Dooby dooby doo.
I invited everyone in the office
because it's not a day for just Jim or Pam or the baby or me.
It is about us all.
And I thought we should all celebrate my joy
and our all of ours joys.
Oh, man.
Does the Nard dog want Nard pups?
Yeah, I want a big old litter of Nard pups.
All jumping around, sucking on the teat,
put them in a box, give them to my neighbors.
Yeah, I want kids.
Yes, I would like to have a baby.
I think I would be quite skilled as a mother.
And I think the child would appreciate that.
And I think in time, the child would realize
that I loved it very dearly.
Yeah, I'm so excited to have kids.
I think that mixed-race babies are beautiful.
They have a lot of identity issues growing up.
You really got to know what you're getting into.
Well, what's so hard about being beautiful?
The girls have an easy time.
The guys have complexes.
It's... I wouldn't take that risk.
Do I want a kid?
Probably not.
And if one more lesbian couple asks for my sperm,
I will scream.
Can we all get together for a quick family photo?
Yeah.
All right.
Just a quick one.
Michael.
Come on.
All right.
Can you actually just take the photo?
The big button right there.
Okay, very good.
Good.
Make a silly face.
No, Michael.
All right, make a serious face, but say banana pants.
Banana pants.
There you go.
And one for luck.
I think we got it. Thank you.
There we go.
So today won't be as small or as sweet as we originally planned.
We're just going to have to settle for smallish.
And sweetish.
Smallish and sweetish.
Like a meatball.
Nice.
For all your paper and printer needs,
for all your paper and printer needs,
for all your paper and printer needs.