Look at me, I'm like I do, nobody can do.
Hey!
Look at me, I'm like I do, and don't you know I'm gonna escape.
I do, ain't nobody do it but believe me.
You're falling behind.
And I'm gonna feel it, I do, ain't nobody do it but believe me.
Nobody believe me.
What's a call?
Ryan, we're doing a dance.
This is how you build a business.
We're doing a dance.
This is how you make it in this country.
Every day nobody, nobody, nobody, nobody, nobody, nobody, nobody, nobody, nobody, nobody, nobody, nobody, nobody, nobody.
You got creative, you jump in front of them.
You make it so hard to love you sometimes.
Still bad.
Oh, for these eyes, then I didn't want to be on the internet.
Go, go, go, go.
Sleepers!
You got creative, you jump in front of them.
I eat...
Why you got to be?
That's crazy!
Toby, how did we do?
Well, that was better.
Yes!
I suppose summer had to end sometime.
It's sad though, because I had a great summer.
I got West Nile Virus, lost a ton of weight.
Then I went back to the lake.
Hey, stepped on a piece of glass in the parking lot, which hurt.
That got infected, even though I peed on it.
Saw Inception.
Or at least I dreamt I did.
Toby, boby, bo, bo, boo, boo.
What, no good morning?
All right.
Sorry, I thought I said good morning.
Well, this summer I finished my murder mystery novel.
Self-published it.
I sold four copies.
Also being sued for plagiarism.
Broccoli Rob, obviously, will be there.
Yes, of course.
And J.C.
We call him Bloorville, because he looks like a black Orville Redenbacher.
Who's the guy who invented the peanut?
Hey, guys.
Hey!
Sorry, didn't mean to interrupt.
Not at all.
I'm going to head back to Siberia there.
Oh.
Ciao.
I started dating Aaron this summer.
It has been, in a word, exquisite.
Gabe is awesome.
He's accomplished so much career-wise and height-wise.
Thank God he's my boss, because I would not have said yes to a first date if I didn't have to.
But it's been great.
Am I angry that Gabe stole my girlfriend over the summer?
No.
I've been through anger management.
Okay, so right now, I am sitting on an ice beach at Cape Cod, gazing out across the White Caps.
Oh, look.
It's a humpback whale.
How pretty.
He's eating Gabe.
Hey.
What are you doing?
From now on, if you're hot, sit on an ice pack.
Well, what if you're cold?
Like you'd ever be cold, Kevin.
Stop asking me hypothetical questions.
Okay, I'm too busy.
Hey, Dwight, I don't know if you heard, but we're supposed to be drinking out of weird backpacks instead of cups like regular people.
Oh, you did hear.
Jim, you have one job to do, and you do it forgettably.
Those of us who are busy require hands-free hydration.
Dwight Schrute, star salesman, beat farmer, bed and breakfast proprietor, aspiring freelance bodyguard.
Add to that list, owner of this building.
Then burn the list.
This summer, I did the Minority Executive Training Program at Yale.
You guys, I'm like really smart now.
You don't even know.
You could ask me, Kelly, what's the biggest company in the world?
And I'd be like, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah incarnation, giving you the exact right answer.
How was my summer?
I was on a new diet where I couldn't eat any red meat.
I lost two pounds, and I'm angry all the time.
What?
Oh, well, last night, Jenny came over again.
She cooked me dinner, and then we had sex all night long.
Gross.
That's awesome, Kevin.
It is.
This summer, I decided to become a liar.
I just make things up.
It's going great.
Coffee monkeys arrived.
I thought the coffee was supposed to be here at nine.
Here you go, big O.
Tiny?
Darryl Hannah.
That says decaf.
You having me decaf?
Ooh, yeah.
Must have been some sort of mix-up there.
You could order just drink it, or should I drive all the way back?
My summer, I blew up my knee playing softball.
Ended up watching CNN most of the time.
I don't know how we're going to get out of Afghanistan.
I hate the new assistant.
He's only been here for a week.
I hate him.
New guy sucks.
Calls me the Nard Man.
I'm the Nard Dog, okay?
Nard Man is my father.
My name is Luke Cooper.
I love cinema.
My favorite movies are Citizen Kane and the Boondock Saints.
There he is.
What you cooking in there?
You know what we call this?
Paper oven.
Any tasty treats coming out of the paper oven?
Yeah, just turn these invoices.
Invoices. Good.