Oh. Oh. What is this? A meatball, really?
It's always more fun to mess with Dwight with an audience. That was usually Pam. So now
that she's out, I had to find someone else.
Turns out that Stanley is quite the comedy fan. But not everything makes him laugh. He
has very specific tastes. Through a painstaking process of trial and error, I found out what
he likes. And it's really weird.
Jim, come on. So juvenile. What the?
You've been meatballed. Are you ready for some meatball?
Oh, man. This is not very clever, Jim.
I know.
Look for your stapler.
Really, Jim? Really? Very funny.
Okay, good day.
What's a haul? 32 meatballs.
Good day.
That idiot's been feeding us for a week.
We'll never have to buy meatballs again.
Dunder Melltham.
Jessica, hi. How are you? Oh, yay. That's so great to hear.
I'm not going to be one of those exes who can't move on. They have their life and I
have mine. I'm taking an Italian class. So far I have learned tortellini, spagatini,
linguini. Well, it's not so much a class as a restaurant, but I do Monday, Wednesday,
Friday from seven to nine. I will patch you through right now. You sound really pretty
today. Okay.
Jessica, I love you. That's a message from my mom. My parents met Jessica and they completely
flipped for her. So they gave me this old family ring to use on her. I know. Whoa, pump
the brakes, Bernard. Too early. I get it. I just, you know, I'm just carrying it around,
seeing how it feels. I haven't proposed to anyone in years. Mom took the main diamond
out. She thought that had more of a my little brother kind of vibe to it.
Oh, it's pretty nice. Got a little bit of the shining vibe though. Oh, who needs a house
that size? Big, stupid, pure chump bait. I'm selling the house actually. You know what?
There's a glare from over here. Oh wow. That's magnificent. It's mid recession in a depressed
area, a faltering state, and I've got the most expensive house in the market. The 1%
are suffering two people. I bought it to be my playboy mansion. A temple to wine, revelry,
sex, intrigue. This was hot on the heels of eyes wide shut, mind you. Then I met my wife.
She moved in, made it her own. Now she's left me and forced me to sell the place. The ultimate
insult, they're calling my speakeasy lounge a rumpus room. Does my turmoil amuse you,
Jim? I'm sorry. I thought you were making a joke. What could you possibly have found
funny in what I said? What was the joke you thought you heard? I guess I thought that
you were approaching it with more of a sarcasm than misery. Kind of laughing at your own
pain. Sad clown thing. Oh yes. How hilarious it is to laugh at clowns, the painted jesters
of a dying circus industry. Very funny, Jim. I get it. I'm getting reports of a serious
outbreak of the grumpies in here. A beautiful monster cost me my 40s and my dream home.
I think I'm entitled to the occasional bad day. Well, please tell Susan we all say hi.