No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh! Okay, fine.
Ryan, something the matter?
Smokey's dead.
Smokey the Bear?
Smokey Robinson. Pam.
He died, like, an hour ago.
I guess I'm the first to know.
Wow, that's terrible. I really liked him.
Oh, you liked him? That's nice.
Did you like when he changed the course of American music
like two or three times?
Did you like the tracks of my tears?
Is maybe the last true love song ever written?
I'm glad you like him, Jim.
I am completely devastated right now.
Well, I second that emotion.
Huh?
I know a few of his songs, but what were his big ones?
Oh, God, Nellie, what wasn't his?
I mean, um, tracks of my tears?
Yeah.
Um, God, so many, Nellie.
No, no, no, no.
Tracks of my tears and what else?
What are some more? What's one more?
Okay, I'm not playing this game, Pam.
Not today.
I don't think you love Smokey Robinson.
I think you're just doing all of this
to prove how deep you are about music.
Okay, I'm sorry that I'm not a fan of Jason Mraz
or The Beatles.
You don't like The Beatles?
That's not the point.
Eleanor Rigby, paperback writer?
Okay, you know, you always think you have time
to see these legends before they go.
What was I so busy doing?
It says here the Smokey Robinson dead thing is a hoax.
It's on CNN as of two minutes ago.
Okay, well, that's a relief.
Wow, look at that.
It says he's actually playing state college.
It's only three hours away.
Oh, my God, Ryan, that's perfect.
You have to go.
Tickets are 250 bucks.
$250 is nothing to the world's biggest Smokey Robinson fan.
Yeah.
Who's opening?
Paul Enka. Paul Enka?
How can they make the Smokeman play with someone like that?
I don't think I can see this.
Okay, he could just show up late, though.
How much is parking? Like, 30 bucks?
That's not what Smokey would have wanted.
Does want.
Tears of a clown.
Don't call me a clown, Pam.
You're better than that.
["Sweet Home Alone"]
Looking good, RC.
Ugh, I hate ties.
I feel like I'm being strangled,
like I'm at some erotic asphyxiation sex club
over on I-84, the Red Room, say, or Dominic's.
Robert, the senator was gonna wear dark brown tonight.
I'm sure it'll be fine.
My husband is sponsoring a fundraiser tonight
for local dog shelters.
Robert, California bought two tables for everyone here.
These people were lucky to get seats
because it is gonna be a who's who
of the Northern 22nd District.