Christmas time is here.
Wow. Thanks, guys. That sounded amazing.
Hi. I'm Andy Bernard,
and I am the first office Santa ever
to make holiday wishes come true.
For the past month, I have been collecting wishes
from everyone in the office,
and I intend to make good on every single one of them.
Now, look, I may not have a great laugh like Santa
or a flying sled,
but I tell you what I do have.
A Prius, a heart of freakin' gold,
this.
All right. You got it.
And an American Express green card.
Who's excited to get their holiday wishes?
Holiday wishes?
What's that, Stanley?
We know exactly what holiday you're referring to.
It is important to be mindful of all belief systems
at our holiday party.
I've been here 18 years
and have suffered through some weird thematic Christmases.
A Honolulu Christmas, a Pulp Fiction Christmas,
a Muslim Christmas, Moroccan Christmas,
Mo-Rocca Christmas.
I don't want it.
Christmas is Christmas. It's Christmas is Christmas.
I got Stanley tickets to see Louis Black for his birthday.
Might not have been the best idea.
I don't want no quandary.
I don't need a dreidel in my face.
That's its own thing.
And who's that Black Santa for?
I don't care.
I know Santa ain't Black.
I could care less.
I want Christmas.
Just give me plain baby Jesus lying in a manger.
Christmas!
What is the status on my wish?
Fulfilled.
Brought my bicycle so I can be your designated driver later.
In the event that you drink too much,
which is by no means required.
What about my wish that we don't have to attend meetings
that degrade our sense of adulthood?
That I cannot do,
but I did get you an acre of property on the moon.
Where, Dark Side or Light Side?
Light Side.
Is it by the Sea of Tranquility?
As a matter of fact, yes. Directly adjacent.
Beachfront.
Thank you, Andy.
So whose wish is next?
Oh, what about Santa's wish?
My biggest wish is that you all get along well with Jessica.
Come on, guys. Jessica?
Jim, tell them who Jessica is.
She's not your grandmother, is she?
GamGam's name is Ruth, Jim.
You should know.
I introduced you on speaker phone that time.
Jessica is my super serious girlfriend
who is seriously awesome and seriously sexy.
Only thing that's not serious, by the way,
our repartee.
Oh, that's great.
When you know, you know.
Hey, what's Ruth's deal, man?
Totally out of your league.
So in summation, ho, ho, ho.
Please be nice to me.
In summation, ho, ho, ho.
Please be nice to Jessica.
And mistletoe is not an excuse for sexual assault.
And don't go near GamGam.
I love Jessica, and I haven't even met her yet.
It's like we don't even need to meet, you know?
I already love you.
Stay home.
I just want you to know that I will be mean to Jessica
if you want me to be.
Oh, no, no. It's fine, Kelly.
It's really no problem.
I was already planning on being mean to her.
That's okay. I don't want you to do that.
Hello.
Merry Christmas, Aaron.
Kelly, happy Panchaganapati.
Ew, what is that?
The five-day Hindu celebration in December
honoring the God Ganesh patron of the arts.
Whoa.
Hey, man.
Hey, ho.
How you holding up?
Because of your wife leaving you?
Kevin?
I actually appreciate the human intimacy.
I feel like a kitten being cradled by a gorilla.
Yeah.
It's been ten days since I had sexual intercourse.
Well, you came to the right place.
No.
This party will cheer you right up.
I hope so.
The corporate party was wretched.
I am so tired of the black-eyed peas.
It's rock and roll for people who don't like rock and roll.
It's rap for people who don't like rap.
It's pop for people who don't like pop.
Where can I get a drink?
Oh.
Oh, well, we thought we wouldn't put the alcohol out
until 11 a.m.
It's just common decency.
Power for the course.
Power for the freaking course.
I'll be in the party room having a cookie until 11.
Oh, fuel log.
Not destroyed.
No.
Not destructive.
Quite.
Off-kilter, sure.
But that's too vague.
Erratic.
Darkly erratic.
Ha ha ha.
That's my mood.
Well, I hate to have to take my Santa hat off
and put on my hard-ass hat,
but this is serious.
It's come to my attention that somebody who shall remain nameless
wants to switch desk clumps.
Fine with me. Jim can leave any time he wants.
Goodbye.
It was me.
It wasn't either of you.
Kathy wants to leave our clump.
Don't look.
Who it was is not important,
but she did say that your constant pranking
and one-up-smanship is driving her crazy.
She or he.