...back orders and you never call them.
Can you believe this?
There's a dog in the car.
You can't leave a dog in a parked car.
Snowboarder, it figures.
Do snowboarders hate animals?
I bet this guy didn't leave his weed in the car.
Okay, we have to do something because this is incredibly dangerous.
Oscar, it's not that hot out.
A car parked in the sun is like a toast oven.
Well, we don't know how long the driver's been gone and it's not in direct sunlight.
So what, Andy? You want to just let him die, you scumbag?
Here, I'm gonna get in my car.
When I start dying, I will honk the horn three times.
That means save the dog.
Okay, you know what? I'm gonna give him something to drink.
Come here, doggy.
Whistle
Come on.
You can't at least aim it.
There you go. Here, doggy. He's not even trying.
Come here, doggy. Come on.
We're losing cloud cover.
Oh, don't try to get in on it now, Michael Vick.
Hey, hey, hey. Vick did his time.
This guy's been gone long enough. He's lost his right to a window.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Hey, Oscar, what are you...
What now? Hey!
Whoa!
Yay!
All right!
Nice job, Oscar.
And one for good measure.
So, who's gonna take the dog?
Why would we take the dog?
What if he jumps out the window and runs away?
Jamie's not gonna sta...
Whoa!
Hey, shh, shh.
Stay, stay.
Nine, six.
Good.
Oscar, what do you want to do? This is kind of your deal.
You want a dog?
There we go.
That should do it.
Yeah, that's pretty good.
That'll work.
Nice job.
Bye, poochie.
Bye, doggy.
Bye.
HONK
DOG BARKING
What's that come to? Like, what did they each win?
Oh, man, it's gotta be over $100,000.
Four taxes.
That's still a lot of money.
The warehouse crew won the lottery yesterday.
$950,000.
And then they quit.
And no one else can focus.
This is it.
This is all on my shoulders.
I'm the one who has to tell everyone to get back to work.
I'm the one who has to tell Daryl to hire a new warehouse crew.
I'm the one who has to say those things.
HONK
Hello.
Justine.
Ha ha.
Nice.