Today is the first day of Sabre's new project to develop a chain of retail stores.
I am meeting my new boss, Nellie Bertram, head of special projects.
Work starts at nine.
Sabre HQ is 30 minutes away driving the speed limit.
Giving everyone 20 minutes to shower, plus 50 for Jim to style his hair, 20 for breakfast,
40 for Erin to get lost between her room and the lobby, 90 for Ryan to do his morning ecstasy.
We're already 20 minutes late.
Wake up!
Hey, hey, hey, hey! Wake up!
Ow!
Why are you sleeping that way?
Oh, I was reading the mattress tag and I fell asleep.
Stanley! Wake up! You've got to wake up! The hotel's on fire!
Stanley, wake up! It's pretzel day!
Good morning.
Hey, wake up. Let's have some fun. We're in Florida now.
Hey, you. I'm so glad this is happening. I actually came to your door twice last night.
Come on in. The water's fine.
Oh, not cool!
I am on the two kids' sleep schedule, so I'm up and at them at 415.
But no kids, so I honestly didn't know what to do with myself.
And then I thought of something.
Here's to why! What the?
Oh, man.
What do you think happened?
Oh, looks like Jim got mixed up with some bad apples.
Oh, no, no, no, no. It wasn't me.
It wasn't me. I got to find Luanda at the alcohol club.
Oh.
Is that a puppet or a stuffed animal?
Puppet.
Cool. I don't know why anyone makes stuffed animals.
Puppets are stuffed animals that can actually do something.
Yeah, you know what? You're right.
Name one thing a stuffed animal can do that a puppet can't.
Ah, make you weirdly angry.
Tishe, Jim.
But seriously, the answer is nothing.
I don't know. If they ever make me do one of those Comedy Central specials,
I'll probably talk about puppets versus stuffed animals.
Cool for your kids?
Yeah, it's weird being away from them. Never done this before.
That weird feeling is called happiness.
Yeah, but I like my family.
Hey, my daughters are my life.
But it's shorts weather and the hotel has free breakfast.
If my daughters were here instead of me, I'd want them eating omelets in their bikinis.
Attention, Dunder Mifflin Group.
Proceed outside.
The vehicle is waiting. Seats have been assigned.
Shotgun goes to Ryan.
Congratulations, Ryan.
I need to make Nellie see me as a leader today.
First impressions get locked in forever.
When I first met Pam, she said something that slightly rubbed me the wrong way.
Since then, I've loved working with Pam and she's frankly wonderful.
But I hate her.
Have a bottle of the antacid?
Also, I want to get a souvenir for my son, but his mother doesn't acknowledge my paternity.
Do you have anything for that? Also, I want it to have a Florida feel.
What is he like?
Power.
Okay, so the idea here is that I'm having a very private moment.
You took this without my permission and somehow it wound up on Facebook.
Okay.
Great. Okay.
So this one is really Florida?
Little obvious, huh? That's the caption.
Unbelievable. I nailed it.
Okay.
And this one is, huh, don't see too many museums around here.
Okay, Twiggy, that's enough. Get in the car.
Hey, are you okay?
I'm fine, okay? It's just stress.
You know, because I care about this project.
And frankly, the fact that none of you are vomiting or diarrheal right now, I find very alarming.
Who says none of us are diarrheal?
Are you sure it's stress? Because I did poison you.
Very funny, Jim.
Oh, no, I'm serious. I was thinking for this trip I have to do something epic, so what should that be?
And then I thought of it. I'll poison you.
What are you going to do? You going to steal my newspaper or put a cricket in my cereal or something?
I'm going to set your face on fire.
That's a good one.
Whoa, Stanley.
Did you just come back from burning down a rival nightclub?
Laugh it up, Halpert.
I'm in Florida for a month without my family.
I'm going to enjoy this.
Want to get in?
You can work the iPod.
Yes.
You're a nice guy, Jim, but you have no idea how to vacation.
Find some Kenny Loggins.
Loggins and Messina.
Did I say Messina?
Ah!
Sorry, I couldn't resist. It's so quiet.
I like it. It's so peaceful.
I've already written like 12 plays today.
It's so quiet,
one might say you could hear a pin.
I thought that would be cooler.
I loved it.
Hey, can you pick up the pin? Some of us like to work on our bare feet.
Of course, I will pick up the pin.
It is right here.
Got it.
Can we see that? Did you really find it?
Yes, right here.
Got it.
In the trash.
Hey, why is it so quiet?
Shouldn't the phone be ringing?
Uh oh.
Erin set the phone to voicemail.
Oh my god.
There.
Oh, there we go.
Pam? Yeah.
Can you get the phone?
Well, you used to be.
I know, but I can't cover reception.
I have a ton of work to do.
Phone's ringing.
Well, why don't you get the phone?
I am freaking out. I know it's for me.
Are you guys kidding me? Stop flirting and someone get the phone.
Somebody pick the absolute phone.
Amy, pick up the phone.
Get the damn phone.
Fine.
Hello, Dunder Mifflin.
Hello, you've reached Dunder Mifflin. How may I be of service?
My hand.
How was the drive?
Fantastic. Stanley drives so fast.
Life is short. Drive fast and leave a sexy corpse.
That's one of my mottos.
I would love to hear the other mottos.
Quick, query Halbert.
No way.
Still queer?
Packer.
You can't put me down.
Too strong.
I tried to get fired, but I landed on my feet down here in Florida.
You see, this cat's got nine lives.
And a nine-inch...
So, who's leading this thing anyway?
Say, I can't wait to meet him.
I can't wait to meet him.
Him?
You say?
Don't think a woman can be a leader?
I...
You poor simple boy.
Expected a man, did you?
Strong...