Oh for god's sake.
Planking is a very stupid and dangerous trend.
Basically you lie like a plank in weird places.
That's it.
Sometimes you get run over.
Welcome to the internet.
Planking is one of those things where, hey, you either get it or you don't.
I don't, but I am so excited to be a part of it.
After you make it, sir.
No, I insist.
The search committee finally decided after a lot of deliberation on Robert California
for the manager position, who took one look around and left.
He drove down to Florida and convinced Joe to make him CEO.
CEO.
Her own job.
He talked her out of her own job and I don't really know how someone does that.
But anyway, then the position was his to fill and he chose...
It's unbelievable.
True, I may have been the second choice, but I was the first choice's first choice.
And about Dwight, I sensed that he might have some resentment about not getting the job,
So I sat him down, we had a talk and I told him, I need a really strong number two.
I want you to be my enforcer.
Smart, right?
Very smart.
This has got to stop.
I can't get down.
Kevin!
Yeah, at first I was really disappointed, but I've got a great daily routine going right
now.
I've upped my karate to eight times a week.
I've added boxing, lunches on weekends.
I do kickboxing three times a week.
I do brahmagav four times a week.
An hour of meditation every morning at sunrise and again at sunset.
So yeah, I'm doing great.
I'm going to need some help.
Pam?
I don't think I should.
Oh, yeah, pregnant.
Right here, little Michael Scott.
Nope, I told you I don't like that joke.
It is a boy, we found out early.
Much different the second time around.
I have to say, it is nice not being the only pregnant woman in the office.
Look, it's little pregs and big pregs.
Wait, when did we start calling them pregs?
Isn't it amazing the difference in our sizes?
Well, I am a few months ahead of you.
I'm having a child with my husband, the senator, and Pam is having a child with Jim, the great
salesman.
Go!
Oh man, it's like hoisting a manatee.
I can't get a grip so fast.
Ryan, a little help?
God, how do whalers do it?
Here's the way trends move across the country.
They start in Japan.
LA and New York get it soon after that.
Seattle looks at it, decides not to do it.
Chicago gets it three months later.
Then it travels down to Mississippi, okay?
All the red states start doing it.
Good morning America does a piece about it.
And then it shows up in Scranton.
Hoist him aloft!
Come on, Darryl, lift, lift, Darryl.
Yeah, I wanted to manage a job, but I got something much better.
This soda, this is mine.
It might be easy if you take a deep breath, lift from the knees, and shove it up your
butt.
I came up with a new thing this summer.
I act like I'm telling someone how to do something.
I go on with a long description, and then I say, and shove it up your butt.
It's stupid, but it's my thing now.
Creed!
What?
Creed, this is a safety issue with you.
There's no way to know if you're dead.
No one should be planking at all.
Thank you, yes.
Dwight, my enforcer, my number two, can you take care of this?
Say no more.
Kids, don't try planking.
It's dangerous.
Especially with me around.
It's called Owling.
You'll read about it.
In like eight months.
Good morning.
Corporate wants me up here.
Dunder Mifflin wants me down there.
What they worked out is Monday, Wednesday, and Friday, I'm here in Scranton.
Tuesday, Thursday, I'm in Tallahassee.
I mean, I feel like Vera Farmiga and up in the air.
You know?
More money, more problems.
Although, I didn't get a raise, so, you know, same money, more problems.
Are you watching that commercial again?
Why do you keep watching it if you know it's just going to make you cry?
Everything makes me cry, so what's the difference?
This dog, he just wants to protect his bone.
He's got a bank vault.
That's a start.
Not enough, though.
All right.
The new CEO works out of the conference room about half the time, but whenever he takes
a break, he does these weird walks around the office, and you never know who he's going
to zero in on for these really intense small talks.
You just hope it's not you, and yet you hope it is you, too.
It's strange.
Here we go.
Hello.
Robert, California.
Let's have a conversation.
Describe your day so far.
Well, I woke up, and I'm listening.
Erin, when you recount your day, never say you woke up.
It's a waste of your time.
That's how every day has begun for everyone since the dawn of man.
Very smart.
Suddenly, I was awake, and I've been doing some...
Hey, Robert.
We have that 9.30 a.m. casual chit chat scheduled.
I emailed you about it last night to confirm.
And again this morning.
First item on the agenda.
Can I get everyone an extra long Columbus Day weekend?
Item number two, connect with the guy.
Robert, California.
What does he think of me?
Don't know.
Super care.
Number three, time permitting, we lost our biggest client.
No, I actually had that on last month.
Oh, sure.
Pam. Pam.
Pam.
Right.
Four, one, two, three, and two of the two.
Sure.
Yep.
Oh.
Chip.
Can I call you right back?
Thank you very much.
Okay.
What is this?
The Friday before Columbus Day.
Thoughts?
What are your thoughts?
Just making chit chat.
Kind of a medium year for women's soccer, no?
I don't think he knows.
What are you looking at?
It's nothing.
It can't be nothing.
Yeah, it can't be nothing.
It's just a list of our names split into two columns.
What?
Okay, just wait one second, all right?
I will copy it.
Do you have a pen?
No.
Okay.
I'll take a photo of it.
Dwight, can you throw me my phone?
Nice catch.
If he comes out, distract him.
We need a warning signal.
We don't need a warning signal, Kevin.
We can see him right there.
We do.
I promise you we don't need a warning.
Warning! Warning! Warning! Warning! Warning!
Ah!
Phyllis! Phyllis!
You okay?
Never touch your neck.
Okay.
You okay?
Yeah.
One, two, three.
Thanks.
Thanks, guys.
Wow.
Okay.
Which side of the list am I on?
Left.
Yes!
Why are you...
How do you know?
What about me?
No, me first.
Just read both lists.
Okay.
Left side, Jim Dwight, Oscar Darrell, Andy Tobey, Phyllis, Angela Kevin.
Right side, Stanley, Gabe, Kelly, Ryan, Old Creed, Pam, Meredith, Erin.
Andy might know.
Maybe it's some team thing they're doing or something.
Really great list of names, guys.
Thank you so much.
Good work.
No, actually, that was in Robert's notebook.
He left it at reception and we photocopied it.
Oh, okay.
I don't want any part of this.
Maybe it's the list of people he's gonna fire.
Okay, it's not that, Pam.
You know, I was thinking it reminds me of those lists Dwight used to make.
This is if we were all on a cruise ship and had to divide into lifeboats.
And this is if we were on a cruise ship and had to divide into life rafts.
Here's something.
Who would eat who in an alive situation?
No.
That can't be it.
I gotta say, kinda seems like the left side's the side to be on.
Me, Jim, Dwight, Daryl.
No offense, Pam, Pat, I don't think that's...
Excuse me?
Pam, come on, don't be such a right-sider.
I...
I was looking for patterns.
I know.
Did you guys figure it out?
We couldn't crack it.
Go in there and just ask the man what it means.
He'll know that we looked at his private notebook.
Come on, just say you saw the list by accident.
I'm already working on this Columbus Day thing for you guys,
and it's starting to stack up.
Feels like a lot, one thing at a time.
Yeah, that's all you had to do today is ask about Columbus Day.
I think it's kinda cool not knowing.
It's like one of those movies that ends on a note of mystery.
Did the buttoner do it?
Are they ghosts?
You know?
It's kinda sophisticated.
Everybody hates those endings.
Yeah, I hate those endings.
Yes, for God's sake, Andy, yes, come in.
What's up?
Weird thing.
Totally awkward.
But you left your notebook on the reception desk.
Great, thank you.
And it was open, and people saw this,
and they're just kinda going nuts and like,
what is this?
Wondering what it is.
It's a photocopy from your notebook.
You read my notebook, and photocopied it,
and distributed it?
No.
They did, and they asked me to ask you about it.
Ah, please.
Here's what it is.
It's a doodle.
What?
Some people doodle at work when they let their mind run.
They draw houses, penises.
Funny how the houses are always colonials,
and the penises are always circumcised.
Don't you think?
Well, I doodle too, but I'm not an artist,
so I draw words and lists.
That is fascinating.
And by the way, I'm not an artist.
And by the way, I am so glad I asked.
People were just sort of, did you just move my name?
Might as well have been sketching a cube.
Okay, Roberts and the Annex, everybody think quick.
What do these groups have in common?
Maybe we're supposed to do it with people in our group.
That's not it.
People in the other group?
Hmm, still wrong.
Stanley, you do puzzles all day.
What do we got?
Well, you take the first letter from each name,
assign it a number, add them all up,
and shove it up your butt.
Thank you, a little much needed comic relief,
but we really need to figure this out, guys.
It's all a mind game.
He wanted us to see the list.
He's a genius.
You guys just don't get him.
I made a list like this for Congress
when I worked in Hollywood in the 50s.
They're meaningless.
Guys, really, it's okay.
Everyone has made a really solid first impression.
I don't think there's any reason for anybody to worry.
I am on the wrong side, and I am freaking out here.
I know.
It's alphabetical.