Hey, everybody. It's closing time.
You don't gotta go home, but you can't stay here.
Whoo!
Closing time
Every office needs an end-of-the-day tradition.
Something to tell you the day's over.
Otherwise, you go home, and the night just feels like more day.
It's weird.
Closing time
W-R-K.
One last call for out.
Uh, no, it's W-R-K.
Finish your whiskey and me.
Oh, my boss is singing closing time. Maybe that's what it is.
Come on, Pam.
Closing time
Time for you to go home to the places you will be from.
Let's see. Andy has been manager for 105 days,
which means I've heard closing time,
105 times.
Still don't know the words.
And when that was home and home and home
I know who I want to take me home
Take me home
You know what? Fine.
I try to start fun traditions for you guys,
but if you don't want to sing, no traditions.
Closing time
Every new beginning
I never heard that song before,
and once I heard it, I did not care for it.
But that song means it's time to go home.
Now, it's my favorite song.
Every new beginning comes from some other beginning,
and good night.
Andy's
Robert, do you want to smoke pipes during our meeting?
Let's wait until we have something to smoke about.
Yes, of course.
Aaron.
I don't think so.
Well, I just thought with my new increased responsibilities and all...
Yeah, I'm still figuring out the two-man bobsled here.
So let's hold off on the D-man for now.
Who's your favorite iron check?
This report is atrocious.
You go first.
The ticketing software paints a picture
of a sloppy, careless, error-brown office.
Well, the monitoring software is a double-edged sword.
Sometimes the information...
Sir, go ahead.
Did you need something from us?
Yes.
Your attention, because...
No, that is all.
That is all?
Last night, I dreamed that the number two
was the most valued number in the world.
The vice president had all the power.
Athletes fought for silver medals.
Women were considered the best gender.
And stadiums of fans shouted,
We're number two!
As with all my dreams,
I'm guessing it was about my fear of immigrants.
Last week, an accounting mistake
resulted in a client getting their order for free.
Oof, that's not good.
Chalk that one up to Tweedle-D and Tweedle-Thumb out there.
Who are they?
They're both Kevin.
Oscar is the Sex and the City gang,
and Angela, if you can...
Sometimes I feel like you don't know me at all.
I would agree with that.
Simply end the mistakes.
End the mistakes? Easy.
When I come back next week,
and this report shows me no mistakes,
we can talk about names.