Oscar, thank you so much for coming in.
I need you to talk with my maid.
Just please. Her name is Teresa.
Say hello. This is Oscar, Andy's friend.
How are you?
So, amigo de Andy, ¿cómo estás?
Bien. She's fine.
How are the kids?
¿Y los niños?
Ah.
The 5-year-old is taking swimming lessons,
and the 10-year-old has braces.
It's kind of cute.
Tell her, thanks for all the hard work,
but it's not working out.
Un momento, Teresa.
I'm not firing your maid, Andy.
I would totally fire your English-speaking maid for you.
Hi, Teresa.
Lo siento mucho, pero el trabajo tuyo ya está terminado.
She wants to know why.
It's not una cosa o dos cosas. It's like Diaz things.
She shrunk my cashmere sweater.
She puts the peanut butter in the fridge,
so it's like impossible to spread.
She says she'll do better.
I've already moved on mentally.
Just tell her that I hired someone else.
She wants to know who.
Tell her that it's you.
Say it.
Teresa. Hi. Eh. Soy yo.
Okay, adiós.
Man.
That is the hardest part of my job.
Oh, she still has my keys. Oscar! Oscar!
Today is the test launch day for the inaugural Sabre Store.
And I, Dwight Schrute, am in charge of the entire operation.
And if I can prove myself today, and the store is a hit with the media,
and Nellie sees this, the vice presidency is mine.
Hey, are you holding this chair?
Because I feel like I'm going to fall off.
Yes. Yes.
I'm not wearing the right shoes for this.
Okay, we went over this, okay?
Your tiny fingers make the best knots.
Hey, strangers. So stoked for the Sabre Store opening.
Hey, my name is Tabitha.
I'm camped out in front of the Sabre Store so I can be first in line for the new pyramid.
Psst. It's me, Erin.
Dwight and me pretend to be hipster to create hype, and it's working.
There's already people camped out behind me.
A line formed already, and the store doesn't even open for an hour.
I hope there's no trampling.
Last thing we need is someone trampled to death.
Can you imagine? All over the news.
I don't know about you, but I went to church to pray this morning.
Oh my god, we have so much in common. I was there as well.
Did you? Which church did you go to? I went.
That was... It was one that was prominently Latino. You've never heard of it.
I went to a Latino church too. Which one did you go to?
La Iglesia de Dios Ciencias.
Oh, I see.
I'm sorry.
La Iglesia de Dios Ciencias Maria E Jose.
E Jose. That's the one I went to.
Yes. What pew were you in?
Jim, you were not there because I just made it all up.
But I was there.
I don't care. It doesn't matter. I've moved on.
I didn't really go to church today. I just said that for effect.
Alright.
Now, I would like to fill you in on a little secret about me to inspire you today.
Now, I know you probably all think I'm this patrician goddess.
But here's the truth.
I was born in the little working class town of Baselden.
And until the age of 32, I taught like this, which was bloody horrendous, innit?
I came from dirt. No, lower than.
What's lower than dirt?
Loam, magma, mantle, outer core, inner core.
Yes, thank you. Loam.
Bloody loam I came from.
I hit rock bottom when I auditioned for the Spice Girls. I didn't even get a call back.
Which Spice Girl?
The black one. I never stood a chance.
Okay.
Now think about my journey here today and let it inspire your journey.
Okay. Nellie, thank you. Thank you so much.
Yep. Yep.
Today is press day and press is going to make or break this store.
And for a tech company, press can only mean one thing.
Bloggers. Dossier on bloggers. Bloggers are gross. Bloggers are obese.
Bloggers have halitosis. You're gonna love them.
Ryan is going to be the main event today.
He is the pitchman who is going to give the feisty yet profound speech worthy of a World's Fair.
Ryan, you ready to do this?
When people see this presentation, they're gonna f*** their pants.
Come on, man.
Come on.
Seriously disgusting.
Cathy, you will be the hot girl who talks to bloggers.
Kill me. That's my idea.
Packer, you will be the sexual predator who has come to prey on the trendy teenage girls who are obsessed with the pyramid.
Ah.
Ah, that is excellent.
I don't see that gets us, but I'm a team player.
Perfect casting, right?
Sure it's out to get me, but I'm playing the long game.
As soon as he messes up, I swoop in like a sexual predator.
Aaron, you will be the disfected hipster who has learned to give a damn because of the pyramid.
And Stanley, I'm gonna need you to pretend to be renowned singer-songwriter Lenny Kravitz.
Oh.
Jim.
Stanley looks nothing like Lenny Kravitz.
Jim, must you undermine every single little...
This is Lenny Kravitz.
Oh dear God.
I would believe that he's Al Roker's brother.
Done. Thank you.
So Jim and I had an experience in his hotel room.
So awkward.
We just need to have a conversation to clear the air and figure out what it is that we both want from this.
Do you remember that crazy girl in high school?
Well imagine if she went to college and majored in crazy.
And then she went and worked real hard to get her doctorate in bonkers.
And then after her internship at the loony bin, ended up working at the desk next to yours.
And her name's Kathy.
Well, that's Kathy.
Has anyone been part of an opening before?
There is a chance today could be total chaos.
If we get everything right, we need people to believe anything is possible.
The square is a very entrenched form.
I want to create a sense of wonder and enthusiasm.
As if at the end of ET, candy poured out of the screen.
Do you understand?
I want to get goose pimples.
Speaking of pimples, let's release the bloggers!
Morning everyone.
Oh Andy, guess what happened to me this morning?
Don't care, tell me later.
Listen, it's important. You've got to hear this.
What do you got?
Oh my god.
Do you have a black eye?
Yes I do, Phyllis.
I woke up at 4 a.m. by accident in time for the paper to be delivered.
Guess what? It's not a kid on a bike. It's a man in a car.
Andy, who punched you?
Hey, I was on the can. What's this about a black guy in the office?
Black eye, Meredith.
Will someone please explain what's going on here?
Since the interesting thing happened till now, so much time has passed.
It's like my life is buffering.
Here's what happened. Pam and I were arriving for the day
and there was a gang in the parking lot on bikes, on motorcycles.
And they just were hassling Pam.
That's true.
They had weapons.
I just stepped in to talk some sense into them.
But these were not the kind of people who use their words.
Punches were going and I ducked a few, landed a couple, and I was fighting them off.
It was a totally like, like senseless crime.
Thank goodness he was there.
Good job, Andy.
Bernard. Hey, I'm your hero.
I didn't do anything any of you wouldn't have done.
Open the gates!
There's plenty for everyone. No need to panic.
There's plenty for everyone. There's plenty.
Don't stampede. No need to stampede, sir.
I was kind of you.
Okay, okay, hey, hey, it's going to be fine.
It's going to be fine. There's plenty of pyramids.
Come on, I was in line before you.
So you're a blogger, right?
Yeah, blogger.
God, stay away.
I always get in trouble around bloggers. I'm trying to be a good girl for once.
Yeah, I already bought my pyramid, but I don't want to leave yet.
I haven't had so much fun since seeing Zuri Desh channel at the Coucherilla Music Festival.
It's so fun.
How can we feel safe knowing that there are gangs here?
We should call the police right now.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
We don't need to call the police.
Let's just ask everybody questions, get up in everyone's business, right, Pam?
Police are a hassle. We settled this on the street.
And my eye will heal, but if the police come,
then we will forever stay in our neighborhood as a troubled area.
Why would you care what the police think of our neighborhood?
Because I have neighborhood pride.
18505.
Guys, guys, that's so vague.
You got to do the zip plus four.
18505 dash 7427.
Look, I don't feel safe. I think we should call the police.
Yes.
Exactly. We need to feel safe, which is why Toby is teaching us self-defense.
Me?
Toby, will you teach us self-defense?
Yeah. I can't believe you remembered. I knew self-defense.
I'll go put on my cup.
Great.
Yay.
Okay.
I wasn't sure which one of you was Chuck.
Yeah, no, it seems to be going great.
Andy got beat up by a fifth grade girl.
Look at that guy. He's got his zebra phone on him. He's not even using it.
This is a perfect photo for my daily fail blog.
I got to go. Okay.
Dwight, what is a fail? That sounds bad.
No, no, no, no. It's good. It's really... On the Internet, that's a really good thing.
Are you trying to sabotage this entire event?
I'm very sorry.
We gave you an arrowhead for free for the day.
How hard would it have been to do this?
Hello. Hi, sweetie. It's Jim.
I'm calling you from the new arrowhead, which is one of voice's crystal clear.
And my hand will never get tired because of the ergonomic shape.
I'm really sorry. Is there anything I can do? Maybe pretend to be...