This is Pam.
Oh my God, are you sure?
Okay, okay, we'll be right there.
Everybody, the balloon is falling!
There's this balloon that has been floating in the rafters of the warehouse for like, ever.
And, okay, it doesn't sound cool, you just have to see it.
Well, I guess it doesn't look that cool either.
But, it's been up there a long time, so it's become a pretty big deal.
Wow. It's the end of an era.
You did a good job, buddy. Now it's time to come home.
I remember when that balloon went up there. I was still with Gil.
We were so happy.
When that went up there, I had hair like Rapunzel.
How long do you think it's been up there, Kevin?
I just remember pushing aside my silky bangs to say, look, a balloon.
My Warcraft clan was still on speaking terms.
My kid didn't have a face tattoo.
I was still thinking of going back to school.
And I was still just a paper salesman.
Well, this has been fun, Pam. Thanks for calling us all down here.
Kill the balloon!
Yeah!
Hey.
So, they accidentally gave us an extra egg sandwich just to make us feel better.
Hey. So, they accidentally gave us an extra egg sandwich this morning.
Who wants it?
Oh, right here. Yes!
Allow me to solve your problem, then.
Ellie.
Hmm.
Oh, that is disgusting.
Do you call that a King James breakfast pie?
What brings you to town?
Certainly not the Harry Houdini Museum.
What a nobody.
Oh, look, some Hungarian just found their way out of a sack.
Let's build a shrine.
No, I've come to work here.
What? How could Robert transfer Nellie here after the saber store debacle?
She stinks of failure.
The fact that she could show her face around here is an embarrassment.
I should know. I'm in an identical situation.
Robert did say you'd be joining us. Welcome. I'm Tony.
Oh. What?
I said I'm Tony.
Okay, I made a mistake. I thought it might go unnoticed.
But I'm Toby.
You messed up saying your name?
It happens, okay?
So, let's just find an empty desk for you,
and I'm sure Robert will be with you as soon as he gets in.
That one looks empty.
No, it's Andy's office.
Oh, is it?
I have one simple philosophy in business.
If the seat is open, the job is open.
It's how I came to briefly race a Formula One car.
The three slowest laps ever recorded.
Another beautiful day in Tallahassee.
Good morning, Alonzo.
Good morning, Erin.
How are you? How's your family doing?
This is my house.
It has five rooms, not including the garage or the roof.
It takes me most of the day just to clean it.
Oh, I'm a maid now.
Like in downtown Abbey.
Did I not mention I only watch PBS now?
Because we don't have cable.
We have cable.
You just have to turn the TV on three and use the other remote.
This is Irene, the world's best boss,
slash roommate, slash cantankerous old coot.
I taught you cantankerous, and now you use it against me?
See, she's given me everything.
A job, a house, a new life.
And a suitor.
Erin, are you going to help me study for the TSA exam later?
You said you would.
Yeah, okay.
Tallahassee.
Nellie.
Robert.
How are you adjusting to life in Scranton so far?
So far so good.
The water pressure in the hotel is marvelous.
It is astounding what a difference that can make, isn't it?
Now, let's find you something fun to do here, shall we?
Oh, I've already found it.
I am manager.
A natural next step. It fits like a glove.
We have a manager.
Do you really? Because it is ten.
I've been in this chair for an hour,
and no other manager has come and sat in my lap.
Excuse me, has anyone seen Andy this morning?
Oh, yeah, that's weird. He's usually here by now.
Right, guys?
Hello?
Andy, it's Robert.
Why aren't you at work?
Hey, Robert.
I really wish I could come into work today, but I'm super sick.
I don't care. I don't care.
Please come to work immediately.
Okay, I'll try to come in, even though I'm really sick with the Florida flu.
He just hung up on me mid-sentence.
I'm in Florida to get Erin.
As soon as I heard she wasn't coming back to Scranton,
I jumped straight in my car and drove straight down till I hit the ocean.
My heart is my map.
Turns out Tallahassee is about 200 miles inland,
so I overshot a good amount.
But still not bad for a heart map, right?
No.
Thanks a lot, BP.
Not much we can do about this until he gets here.
Can't you do something about this?
Sometimes the flowers arrange themselves, Jim.
Right.
What is going on?
And where is Andy?
And what is going on?
This is insane.
Has anyone talked to Andy?
He's not returning any calls.
I checked his Facebook status, said, pump for Wednesday.
Today's Thursday.
I hate to take you to this place, but, Rea, Andy, has anyone checked the morgue?
Checking the morgue isn't a real thing.
That's a real thing.
You're a policeman.
No, anyone.
You're just like, hey, can I look around?
Anyone?
Yeah, and they have names on everything.
I didn't know you were a police officer.
Then you go to the graveyard.
Okay, okay, okay.
Look for a cemetery plot.
Guys, shh.
Andy's fine, all right?
Last time he was this late, he just lost track of time
watching a Today Show segment on men's shorts, so it's fine.
Well, what's Nellie like?
She's a classic case of failing upwards.
That's how cantaloupe got popular.
I'm gonna text Andy.
Brian, will you put my phone in text mode?
What's this, then?
Everyone okay?
Just some casual conversations?
Yeah, exactly.
Let's all follow Mama Goose into the meeting room, then, shall we, Ducklings?
Nellie.
Yes.
Robert.
Come on.
You heard her.
So this is what we're doing now, then?
We're just...
So what is going on?
That does seem to be the question, doesn't it?
Hey, this is messed up, bro.
Who is this weird lady?
I know.
It's a lot.
So who knows what's going on?
I don't know.
Anyone?
You, yes.
Wait, I am very good at intuiting names.
Is it...
Chumbo?
I think it's a cross between Dumbo and Jumbo.
With a hint of Chubby.
It's not a name.
Erin, you got a package!
I'm in the bathroom!
Where's the postage?
There's no shipping label.
Did you wash your hands?
Yes.
Here I am, sun-sealed, delivered.
I'm yours!
Andy, what are you doing here?
It's great to see you.
I am here to take you back to Scranton.
Because I love you and I want to be with you.
Where's the ring?
Where's the ring, Lancelot?
Would you mind if we talked privately for a second?
Sorry, Glenn.
Andy, I am so happy to see you, but I'm not coming back with you.
Why won't she go with him?
I don't know.
Maybe it's because he's not that handsome.
Hey, don't listen.
Well, this is not what I expected.
Especially after driving here all night.
I'm sorry. You must be tired.
No, actually I'm not tired.
I had a 12-pack of this energy drink called Up Yours.
It has a picture of a hyena giving you the finger on the can.
I feel weird.
It's just...
Can I stay for lunch?
Oh.
As a friend?
Well, I'd have to boil another hot dog.
But yes, of course, yes.
I'm not going to give up that easily.
Let me tell you something.
If a long drive was all it took to win over a girl,
then supermodels would be married to long-haul truckers.
That's where I keep my spices.
Cumin, saffron, paprika.
I bought everything you need to make a paella.
She means papaya.
I mean paella.
Great. The maid has a visitor.
Maybe he'll use my exercise bike too.
So no one can tell me what's going on.
Well, let me illuminate things for you.
We are getting to know each other.
But why?