Hey, so we saw the new billboard.
Yeah, pretty cool, huh?
What better way to announce our new slightly lower prices than with an ad campaign?
And what better face for an ad campaign than our new regional manager?
How'd it look?
You've seen it, right?
No.
Andy somebody defaced it.
What? How?
Morning, Stanley.
There's this thing that people tend to do with billboards.
How do I put this?
If there's an opportunity for a graffiti artist to work in a phallic shape, interacting with the artwork, it'll happen.
And Andy gave them that opportunity.
Erin, how long do we order those billboards for?
Six months.
Oh, good. I need you to call the billboard company.
Great billboard. Funny, edgy, right up to the line without crossing it. Loved it.
Which one did you see?
Washington Street, the one with like 20 dogs on it.
Okay, don't be gross.
What's going on?
Somebody defaced the billboards we just put out in an inappropriate way.
Oh, that's funny.
Wade, from the photo shoot with you and me?
Yeah, Dwight.
No. No.
No, no!
Shrewd Farms is very easy to find.
It's right in the middle of the root vegetable district.
If the soil starts to get acidic, you've probably gone too far.
Just give us the address.
We'll look it up online.
It's simpler this way.
It's really not.
Now, stated arrival time is 3 p.m.
I don't get the reason for this party.
Yeah, what's the reason?
What's the reason, Andy?
What's the reason?
It's just a garden party.
Sheesh.
You don't need a reason to throw a garden party any more than you need a reason to throw
a birthday party.
It's a garden party.
You don't need a reason.
A few other super simple reminders.
No burping, no slurping.
When eating, take small bites and chew thoroughly with your mouth closed.
Yes, Daryl?
What happens when we're done chewing?
Do we spit it out on the floor or keep it in our mouths the rest of the time?
I get it.
I'm being a little overbearing.
But I promise to be underbearing for a week if you guys just all step it up.
Andy, we understand basic table manners.
We're not children.
Yeah, it's just a picnic.
This is not a picnic, Phyllis.
It's a garden party.
There's a grill in the warehouse I can bring.
Oh, please don't.
Not a barbecue.
It's better than a barbecue.
It's dignified, quieter.
There are rules.
How is that better than a barbecue?
What's the dress code on this?
I'm glad you asked.
Connecticut casual.
Any chance Connecticut casual is Pennsylvania business?
I.e. this is what I'm wearing to your party.
Guys, my family just threw a garden party to celebrate my brother's promotion.
It was a huge success.
Check it out.
There's a video online.
Heartwarming, impromptu father-son duet.
Oh, yeah.
Oscar, you show me this.
I've seen this.
That's not you.
Yeah.
Who's the sausage?
It's my dad and my brother.
I would have joined in, but this melody doesn't really support another harmony part.
Check it out.
That's my brother's boss.
Look how psyched he is.
He's having an awesome time.
And did Robert, California get an invite to your party?
Yeah, of course.
Yeah, I mean, yeah, I think he did.
Why didn't you just say this was to impress Robert, California?
I cannot believe that Andy is throwing a party like this just to impress the CEO.
Classic Gabe move.
Hey Andy, how about you don't steal my business strategies and I won't dress like my life
is just one long brunch.
See you all there at 3 p.m. Connecticut casual.
Remember your manners and have a wonderful time.
And please refer to the map.
Stay off of the web.
Thank you.
So we've typed in the address.
Now let's take a look at the street view.
They don't warn you when the cameras are driving by.
Why do you keep reading that garden party book?
I mean, how hard are finger sandwiches and tea?
There's so much more to it than that.
I've been wanting Shroot Farms to break into the high end event hosting industry for some
time and this party is a great opportunity.
Plus, I've got a secret weapon.
I've only one copy in the world and some sucker on the internet sold it to me for $2.
I'm actually really disappointed in how poorly my book is doing.
I've only sold one copy.
I cannot believe how condescending Andy's being.
He gets condescending when he's nervous or when he's excited or sleepy.
Not an easy person to be friends with.
Well, I just hate being treated like some bum with no class.
I'm a lady.
I'm a mother.
I'm a former boxer.
Hey guys.
Getting psyched for the party?
Ryan, can I count on you to wear an understated satirical outfit?
Can't wait.
A faux colonialist gathering when unemployment's at 9%.
I wouldn't miss it for the world.
Awesome.
Stanley, what about you?
I am really looking forward to it.
Is it alright to bring a plus one?
Yeah.
Now that's the spirit.
That's what I'm talking about.
I'm telling you Stanley, don't bring her.
I'm breaking up with my current girlfriend.
I like to break up with women in a public place like a restaurant.
But I also don't like to pay for a meal that will not lead to sex.
So this party is a great opportunity.
Is there anything you wish you'd done differently to avoid cankles?
Nope.
I've already gone up another cup size.
The senator is grossed out.
When do you start feeling it kick?
Cece was around 22 weeks but Phillip was much earlier.
Phillip?
Oh, oh my gosh.
Yes, but don't say anything, okay?
It's after my grandfather.
Phillip is the name that we're using.
It's after my favorite cat.
Oh wow, funny.
It's after my grandfather.
It's after my cat.
Andrew, I've picked up two possible gifts to bring this afternoon.
One pot of marmalade.
Oh, that sounds great.
That is what you want then, the marmalade.
Sure.
You don't want to hear the other one.
You love marmalade.
I'll hear the other one.
It's a basil plant.
You know, the marmalade sounds great.
I also mentioned the marmalade to my sister and she's very interested.
Then the basil will be fine?
Well, you clearly want the marmalade.
Gretchen, I need another marmalade.
Alright.
Hey, where do I park?
I'm the valet, you have to give me your car.
You know what, I can't park in my sun.
This is probably a valet.
I think it's quite better than I thought.
I'm the valet, you have to give me your car.
It's a finicky car.
Get out of your car.
Get out.
Have a good time at the thing.
It's a little tricky.
You might want to be careful.
Aaron, the receptionist.
Mr. Ryan Howard.
Chapter 2.
Announcing guests as they enter is the height of decorum.
The more volume displayed, the more interesting the event is.
The more volume displayed, the more honor is bestowed upon everyone present.
Stanley Hudson and his mistress Cynthia.
James Pamela and Pee Pee Halpert.
Oh, oh, oh, Kevin.
I am reminded of a lame but useful saying I learned as a kid.
What is the difference between hors d'oeuvres and the animals on Noah's Ark?
What?
With hors d'oeuvres, we only take one at a time.
Oh, okay.
What's the difference between a vacuum cleaner and a blonde?
Mm-hmm.
How's it going over here, guys?
Andy, stop hovering, you're being really annoying.
Didn't mean to bother you, Mabel.
Mabel, Mabel, if you're able, keep your elbows off the table.
Wow.
Mr. and Mrs. Walters!
Mr. and Mrs. Walter and Ellen Bernard!
So you all work with Andy?
Well, technically for Andy.
Technically for Robert California.
He's our CEO.
I thought you were the CEO.
I don't know how you got there.
You said you were running the company.
This branch. I'm the regional manager.
Yes.
That makes more sense.
So you're all regional managers?
Did I throw this party to impress my parents?
It's crazy.
Now, if they wanted a garden party, they could throw one themselves.
Which, as a matter of fact, they did last week.
They threw one for my baby brother.
And it was totally amazing.
But I couldn't care less.
My parents are used to a certain type of class.
The people that I work with are a different type of class.
One is not better than the other.
It's just that...
Maybe one's a little...
Higher than the other?
Can I introduce you around now?
Uh, yeah. We don't have too long.
We have theater tickets.
What are you going to see?
Moneyball.
Those?
Walter Jr.'s choice.
Oh, there he is.
What, Bronard?
I didn't know you were going to be here.
I wouldn't have missed it.
Okay.
There, we actually need you to do...
I'm Walter.
I'm Andy's younger brother.
Oh, hey, how you doing? I'm Jim.
Tuna, right?
And this must be your lovely wife, Pam.
No.
Hell no. She wishes.
No, no, no, no.
Stanley, Cynthia is a delight.
You've been yakking it up like a couple of old hands.
How long's she been a physical therapist?
Don't go making any ties. I want a clean break.
Chapter 7.
The host should always present something spectacular
to draw the eye of his guests.
When all this is over, I'd love to actually go to one of Tricking's
parties. They sound like a blast.
Ladies and gentlemen,
I present to you
the Alamo!
Little Cece asleep?
Yeah, she just went down.
Such a precious little angel.
Aw.
Cecilia.
And Philip. Yes, after my grandfather.
Philip is wasted on you.
Jim is never going to take the time to call him Philip.
He doesn't even take the time to get a haircut.
And Phil, ugh,
it's just something you do to a hole.
Well, I'm having my baby first, so that's that.
You know what? It could go either way.
My doctor said my hips are so dainty
that I'll most definitely have a C-section, so...