Hey, Jim.
Stanley's back from the hospital today.
Can you sign us a card?
Oh, great.
Glad they didn't mix up your tonsil
ectomy with a mustache ectomy.
Oh, that's not good.
Well, because your jokes are all hilarious.
It's nice. It's funny.
It mentions his tonsil ectomy
and makes a funny little joke about his mustache.
Stanley doesn't have a mustache.
Yeah, he does.
Pam, hit the brakes.
Stanley does not have a mustache.
I misspoke.
I'm not sure.
I think he has one.
Now that...I think he has a mustache.
Okay, Phyllis sits across from him every day.
Phyllis, does he have a mustache or not?
Oh, I don't know.
Um, now I think he doesn't.
Phyllis, what are you talking...
The whole card depends on this.
Okay, the man has worked here for 25 years.
How can none of us picture his face?
Because we come here to do our jobs.
We don't stick our noses in other people's business.
Okay, which one of these looks more right?
Neither of those looks like any person
that has ever existed or been dreamt of
in the history of human insanity.
That said, the one on the left.
Guys, that's the elevator.
What if it's him?
Okay, quick.
Who says mustache?
Yep.
Who says no mustache?
Ah!
Hey!
He does have one.
Yes!
Super beep-bop.
Welcome back, Stanley.
Mm.
Good morning, Robert, says no one,
because our receptionist is in Florida.
Pam!
Oh.
Is this a video conference you're having
with Drake featuring Swizz Beats?
Um, no, I was just, um, just having a cup of coffee
kind of warming up for the day.
People, you should come to work already warm.
Nine to 10 a.m. is the most productive potential
that a human being...
Sorry, sorry, everyone, I'm late.
But you are all here,
so no harm done at all by my lateness.
Now he really 9.50.
Oh, here's what happened.
7.46, my alarm clock goes off, I hear it.
Whack the snooze.
Nine minutes.
Off it goes again.
Whack.
Seven more times I did that.
By the time I got up, it was 10 minutes ago.
No willpower!
That is my curse.
You've never believed willpower
was very important in a woman.
I don't think you would have shown up to work
nearly an hour late for no reason.
Oh, I assure you I would have done.
I did.
And I will keep doing it.
No, no, no, no, there's something going on,
some stress in your life.
Well, yes, there is the whole
moving to Scranton nonsense.
30 boxes arrived yesterday from England
and two trunks from Florida.
Then I have to move into my apartment
in this dreadful, God knows where it is,
backwater suburb of a suburb.
I mean, no offense, but are there a lot of
Irish people living around here?
Yes.
Oh, hate that.
No offense.
None taken.
Actually, Nellie, this monologue you're
delivering is very offensive.
Oh, I caramba!
The natives are getting restless.
Who's a native?
Excuse me, the tone here is getting quite hostile.
I would appreciate it if you would keep
that stuff on the basketball court.
What does that mean?
Okay, okay.
You'd let me finish
or the squash court or the supreme court.
Nellie.
Yes, Robert.
You're clearly under a lot of stress
with the moving and the work situation
you've found yourself in.
Yeah.
Let's help her out, shall we?
Go above and beyond today to show her
some of that warm Scranton hospitality.
Jim Dwight, take the day.
Help Nellie move those boxes into her new place.
Why Jim?
The rest of you, let's throw a party
at the end of the day to welcome the newest
member of our little community.
I'm sorry, we're throwing a party for someone
because they're being horrible?
I'm sorry, we're taking work time to move
someone's personal belongings into their new apartment.
I'm still not sure why this woman is even here.
Why is she here?
Two crazy kids on the journey of life.
Going to Pennsylvania.
On the road with my new girlfriend.
But first, a small pit stop to break up
with my current girlfriend who is at her parents'
cabin in southern Pennsylvania.
That must be nice.
It's a beautiful place.
Great place to let her down easy.
Oh, no, no, I meant that must be nice to have parents.
Oh.
Time to have a little kiss.
No.
Sorry, right.
No kisses until the breakup is official.
I believe in that.
Yes, so do I.
That's important.
Bummer, but important.
Important.
I can't believe he's making us throw a party for her.
I know, right?
She's always late, she's always rude.
Kind of makes me want to throw a really bad party.
Yeah.
On purpose.
Phyllis.
We should do it right here in the break room.
Arter carrot cake.
And Jessica, just so you know,
this is way more about my love for Aaron than anything wrong with you.
Well, Andy, I'm upset, but you did this in the best way possible,
and I knew you as a lover, and I'll remember you as a gentleman.
Okay, that was one minute and ten seconds.
Consider it nailed.
Bam.
I think we should try it again, this time worst case scenario.
Okay, here we go.
Jessica, I'm really sorry, I just need you to know something.
What?
I just need you to know that...
That I didn't sleep well last night.
You guys, we serve the carrot cake with orange juice.
My mouth is puckerin' just thinking about it.
But you know, none of these really seem mean enough.
I mean, can we put some soda cans in a pillowcase?
I got one.
Let's pretend that we thought it was her birthday
and get her a cake with a few too many candles on it.
Like, 49.
Bam.
That is brilliant.
LAUGHTER
Oh, this is new.
Since when are we a geisha?
What the...?
Don't put the boxes down.
I want to get to know my potential neighbours.
Don't put the boxes down?
No, I want to get to know the building.
I mean, it would be a shame to move all this stuff in
and then move it all out.
KNOCKING
Are you an abortionist?
You see these news stories from America,
everyone's a firebombing abortionist.
Go ahead, it's a free country, all of it.
No opinion on abortions or firebombing.
Just not in my building.
Okay? Thanks. Bye.
Ah!
Ow.
Nellie, that reminds me, do you want this chair in the bedroom?
Cos, to be honest, I don't think it's gonna fit through the door.
Don't listen to Jim. Have you ever seen him play Tetris?
Oh, I think I'll just use this line horizontally.
Nellie, oh, I have no idea what a gift this line is.
That was one time.
I will get the chair in.
Watch the great Shrutini work his magic.
Oh, no, really? Magic? No, no, no.
Let's not go there.
No, nothing is more repellent than magicians.
Bunch of grown men waving wands,
pulling bunnies out of body crevices.
Magicians are a pulsive next topic.
Excuse me. One second.
PHONE RINGS
Hi. Hey, what's up?
You know how they just haul in some cube with Dwight?
Hauling cube!
That's moving boxes. We just came up with the term to make it sound cooler.
So we're planning this party for Nellie,
and we're gonna make it really bad.
Sounds like every other party.
No, we're gonna make it like a prank.
Like, order bad food, give her this passive-aggressive card.
Oh! Hire a magician.
What? Trust me.
Okay.
Wow, there's a lot of cars here.
This is just weird.
KNOCKING
Andy!
Hey, what are you doing here?
Hey, Lauren. Look at you.
Look at me.
I was just on my way back from this business trip,
thought I'd stop and say hi to Jessica.
Aw.
Why is Erin with me? That's a great question.
She is my coworker, and she needed a ride
because she totaled her car.
Oh, God.
Hi, I'm Erin. Hi.
Nice to meet you.
Well, Jess went out for a run,
but she'll be back soon.
Mm-hmm.
Hey, ladies. Andy's here.
Okay, Andy.
That is a bachelorette party.
This is Jessica's friends,
and they've been drinking during the daytime.
Should we go?
You know, we had such a quick window to make this work,
I think we should probably just...
Oh, Jess!
We're going to have a biopter's business trip.
Andy!
Hey!
I am just stepping out.
There's a bloke in Unit 5
who's on the sex offenders registry.
I'm just going to check out his side of the story.
We'll be here moving boxes.
I wonder if king-sized sheets
are called presidential-sized in England.
I really should have a tweet or account.
Yes, you should.
Ooh.
Nellie, don't open stupid.
Love, Nellie.
I have to see these shoes.
I doubt that they're shoe...
Whoa.
Who is this guy?
Here's the two of them taking a hike.
I'm guessing he's some kind of friend.
Boyfriend.
Here's the two of them kissing at a beach
and kissing at the Eiffel Tower.
I'm guessing he's some kind of close romantic friend.
Like a boyfriend?
You read my mind.
Whoa.
Who's the one with his face whited out?
Hmm.
Maybe someone threw a pie in his face.
New theory. He's a hated Italian politician.
Better theory. This is her ex-boyfriend
and they went through some kind of painful breakup.
Oh.
I'm so sorry. We were just...
I see you've discovered Benjamin.
That's what I call my box full of photos of Henry.
Why not?