Hey, Angela, you want to see a picture of Philip
wearing those little booties you got us?
So cute.
Hey, you guys want to see a picture of Gerald
wearing galoshes?
He refused to go out in the rain until I bought these.
Now going out in the rain is all he wants to do.
Oscar thinks having a dog is just like having a baby.
Newsflash, if you didn't carry it around in your belly
for nine months, it isn't your kid.
Exactly.
Unless you adopt it, of course.
That is where we disagree.
Hey, are your little dudes crawling yet?
No. Three month old humans don't do that.
My Philip is crawling.
Angela is such a liar!
It's maddening!
Exactly, that's just like crate training.
All night long, all night long.
Well, count yourself lucky.
Wait until you have two.
That's two sleep schedules, two naps that don't coincide.
I mean, you'll never sleep again.
No one said you must have two.
Like her jeans are so important.
The world just needs more Pam Jim DNA.
Thank you, no.
No, thank you.
Check this out.
My brother just got a new sailboat.
He has no idea what he just got himself into.
There's nothing harder than taking care of a boat.
Am I right?
Unbelievable!
Un-be-lie-va-ble!
It is the end of the day.
It is the end of the week.
We managed to fill 40 hours, somehow.
That's not bad, is it?
That's great.
Pretty good.
Well, thank you.
This is very helpful feedback.
Dwight, I am still not ready to name a VP.
That's not what I was going to ask.
Gosh, you jumped to conclusions.
Come on, I know.
You've got so much on your plate.
It's right now you're like,
What's more important, Dwight's question?
Figure out who's the VP.
Dwight VP, Dwight VP, Dwight VP, Dwight VP.
I can't be hypnotized, Dwight.
I tried it, I ended up smoking more.
Can we at least eliminate those that are not in the running?
Free them up to focus more completely on the menial.
Like stacking and sorting or...
Catching butterflies.
That's a hobby, unless it's for food.
Theatre.
Waste of time.
Dragging.
That's just a verb.
Dragging sticks.
Yes, nice, perfect.
All right, I'm going to eliminate three people right now.
Okay?
You three.
No.
Not good enough.
English people's main use today is judging American talent.
You're crap.
You're wonderful.
They're mean, but they're incisive.
Everyone meet in the hotel bar at seven.
I'm not allowed to say it's mandatory,
so let's just call it compulsory.
I'll be there at six.
We're going to have those crazy nights, aren't we?
Maybe we'll see the real Tala-nasty we've been hearing so much about.
Tala-nasty, very clever.
Thank you.
Wait, wait.
You think she meant the Tala-nasty?
No, no, no, no.
Kathy, it's been great.
Fun, normal.
I thought I was going to be hanging out with Stanley on this trip,
but he's turned out to be kind of a loose cannon.
My friend and I are new here in Tala-nasty.
Would you like to get a cocktail?
Maybe go out for a little dance.
Beautiful day, now.
Okay, everybody, five o'clock, workday's over.
Put your pencils down and bring them back up,
because now the late-night work jam begins.
Yes, the conference room is set up.
I've got pens, I've got paper, I've got a whiteboard.
We are good to go.
Say what?
Good to go.
Stop it.
Say what?
Stop.
Tonight we're staying late to service the accounts
of the people who went on the Florida trip.
Yes, of course, we could have just been doing this the whole time,
but someone dropped the ball.
Ball droppings can be beautiful.
For example, when it turns an awkward soprano into a rich, full tenor.
I have gone to the trouble of arranging a couple of surprises,
which I think is going to make tonight a lot more bearable.
And I'm not talking about bears, grr.
Grr, I'm talking about berries as in blueberry pie.
Kevin, come on, I know you're down, right?
I knew you were going to say me.
You just couldn't help yourself, could you?
Picking on the big guy.
Well, I'm going to eat it, Andy, and I'm going to eat a lot of it.
But I don't want it.
Andy, surprise number two, better read that we can all go home.
It's not.
It's another pie.
Rebarb!
Jason Bourne would kick Bond's ass.
Jason Bourne has no support staff.
His own government's out to get him.
Genghis Khan could take them both down because he's not afraid to kill children.
What? It's true.
He would eviscerate babies and hang them from poles outside of the villages.
Okay, drinking game.
Count of three, take three sips.
That's a stupid game.
I got a great drinking game, okay?
Everyone, empty your pockets.
Whoever has the most seeds is the king.
Whoever has the least buttons is the hunchback.
What happens if you're the hunchback?
Oh, you get kicked.
How many buttons do you have?
Forty, always.
May I see?
Sure.
So I get to kick you now?
No, they're not transferable just because I handed them to you.
Well, that's how I played it in college.
College rules.
And he lost at his own lame game.
Oh, double meaning.
The game was lame and now he's lame from the kick.
Quick, a wick.
Thank you.
I will have a glass of your okiest chardonnay, please.
And I will have a waffle with your maple-iest syrup.
Sorry, no waffles.
Oh, okay, just forget it then.
Forget it. Forget it.
A waffle?
A hotel waffle. I know what I want to eat.
Is that crazy?
Huh?
I'm moving down here, you know.
Oh, no, I didn't know.
I'm young and I can.
And if I can't, I'm still pretty young.
I guess I'll always be young.
You come with me.
We're gonna get you that waffle.
Why would Erin confide in me that she's staying here in Florida
if she didn't want me to make some sort of last ditch,
nothing to lose, Kelly kahoo run at her?
Hey.
Watson, carpet and tile.
One order.
Order of reference number 00983-126.
Eight cases, bright white inkjet.
Paid.
I'm dying!
Processed.
And delivered.
Sometimes I get so bored, I just want to scream.
And then sometimes I actually do scream.
I just sort of feel out what the situation calls for.
I will be right back.
I will be here.
Hey, I see what you're doing.
It's futile. The V.P. position is mine.
Oh, please, you're through.
She's going to give it to me.
She's going to give it to me as I'm giving it to her tonight.
The cowgirl has chosen her saddle.
Well, saddles...
sometimes fall off,
especially if you don't properly cinch the girth.
What? That's a joke, right?
You see the way she's all over me.