Approved.
Chef from South Park. It's genius.
Just some chef.
I've decided to pre-screen all of the Halloween costumes this year.
I have three simple rules.
Don't be offensive, don't be cliché, and don't take the first two rules too seriously.
The gorilla from Rise of the Planet of the Apes?
Huh?
The one who sacrifices his life.
Whoa! Oh!
Spoiler alert.
It's been out for ages, man.
Costume vetoed.
Yeah, it's, uh...
Somebody's already called that.
Who?
Kevin has a gorilla suit you could borrow.
This is ridiculous. Why can't there just be two Kate Middletons?
Guys, I know. I mean, I wish there could be two.
It's like...
I can't choose. They're both amazing. It's just...
Look, I stayed up all night and I watched that GD wedding,
and then I came to work and I made everyone else watch it all day.
Meredith wasn't even here.
Because I was there.
You're the people's princess!
Diana was nothing!
I thought you were at your sister's funeral.
What I said was, my sister's funeral is this weekend.
Didn't say I'd be there.
Why is it such a shock that I followed a royal story?
Warms my heart.
Thinking about them two kids.
Doing it.
Can I maybe squeeze through?
There we go.
Thank you.
When they talk about all the nice things about dating a coworker,
they don't mention one of the best parts.
After you're done dating, you still get to work together.
Every single day.
Jim, put it on.
Put it on, man.
I don't know if I can.
Come on, the three amigos.
Three kings.
I know, I know, I know.
But Darryl and Kevin needed a third.
They bought me this jersey.
I said no.
Kevin started crying.
So I am Chris Bosh.
If you can't into season one, you know, really.
Oh my God, what the hell is wrong with you?
It's called a costume.
What are you, some kind of Jamaican zombie woman?
Ryan, will you please tell her who I am?
Whoopi Goldberg.
Has no one here heard of Kerrigan from Starcraft?
Queen of Blades?
It's all Toby's fault.
Every Halloween I tell him the same thing.
You can't bring weapons into the office.
And every year he says the same thing.
As soon as I get my weapons back, I'm gonna kill you.
But there I am at Thanksgiving, alive, you know.
I'm a lucky turkey.
Everybody looking good?
This is the best we can do?
I'm not judging.
I think you guys look great.
I just...
I want to make sure this is the best we can do.
I just got a text from Broccoli Rob.
Boo!
Scared me.
And then I got this text from Robert, California.
Looking forward to Halloween party.
Expectations are high.
Scared the **** out of me.
Good day, Pam, all right?
Could you shoot this off for me?
Yeah.
Australian accent.
What are you doing?
I just wanted to see how you do it.
If you're doing something I don't...
Are you...
That Andy, so hot and cold.
One day he's like, fax these documents, please.
The next he's like, Pam, you fax them.
Who cares what Erin's feeling, right?
Oh, Erin.
Pam, how would you rate me as a receptionist on a scale of one to three?
Um, two?
That's like the second to last thing I wanted to hear.
No, I mean, you're doing great.
And Andy put you in charge of the whole party, right?
Yeah.
Send completed.
You are the best in the biz, I can't deny.
Bob and I are doing this granted haunted walking tour.
I always wonder what kind of people want on that thing.
Oh, hey, if you go by the Banshee Pub, tell the man in black I say hello.
What happened, Pam?
Okay, when I was 22, I worked there,
and everybody said the place was haunted.
I didn't believe it until one day before we opened,
I look up into the mirror, you know, behind the bar,
and I see this old man dressed all in black.
But when I turn around, there's no one there.
Oh.
So I tell the cook my story.
Wait, they have food there?
And he said, that's what everyone sees.
That's the man in black.
No.
My wife does not believe in ghosts.
Hey.
Oh.
This man in black thing, what do you think that was about?
What do you mean?
Was it like trickery in the lights,
or maybe you were so primed to see it, then there it was?
I saw a ghost.
Mm-hmm.
What I'm saying is, like, do you ever wonder what it was?
It was a ghost.
I told you this on, like, our first date.
Yeah, I just told you about the day that I met the Blue Angels.
I figured you had to top it.
I don't know what to tell you, Jim, but I saw a ghost.
Hey.
Uh-oh.
Looks like we're under a jack attack.
Yes, Andrew.
And you on this day of fantasy are a laborer.
Yes.
Everyone, this is Bert, my son.
Bert, this is a paper company.
A paper company.
Paper.
Hello.
Can I use your computer?
I need to check a hurricane.
Here, use this one.
All right.
Oh, look.
Pin the word on the witch.
How did you know I was bringing my son?
Oh, I didn't.
It was for us.
But he can play.
Bertie Boy, would you like to play this game?
That stuff's for babies.
Well, perhaps this party will awaken the baby in all of us.
Wow, who shot our grown-up party with the Kitty Ray gun?
We're still getting it set up.
It's going to be really cool.
Extraordinary.
Did you plan this?
Well, Toby and I did, yeah.
And I overheard and thought, hey, that'd be fun.
Don't mind if I do.
If you turn off the lights, we'll do a little dance.
A one, two, three.
Bones, bones, bones, bones, bones, bones.
Now we're the Skeleton Crew.
Delightful.
Thank you.
Now then, how are we today?
Fine.
Great.
Just fine, Kelly?
Everything all right?
Mm-hmm.
You feeling fulfilled in your life?
I guess.
You guess?
So there is something you want that you do not have.
Try not to think about it.
Because it's too terrifying to imagine.
Now we're cooking.
What is it, Kelly?
What is this great fear of yours?
Never marrying.
Yes.
Dying alone, that is very scary.
And how are you, Toby?
So great.
Oh, I put those up.
I know.
I'm taking them down.
I almost wonder if putting nothing on this wall,
this is more Halloweeny.
I don't know about this, guys.
Andy put me in charge of the Halloween party, so.
Well, Andy sent us in here.
So which is it?
Oh.
So can we speak our minds now, or are we still sparing feelings?
Because I hate all of this.
Very low pressure on our sarcosso sea.
Warmer from South America.
Cold air from Greenland.
All signs point to the perfect storm.
Perfectly mediocre.
What are you, anyway?
I'm a Jamaican zombie woman.
Leave me alone, ghoul.
I'm a zombie from Walking Dead.
It's a show.
I know what it is.
OK, I have like 1,000 people over every week to watch it.
OK?
We all kind of hate it, though.
Who's your favorite character?
The city of Atlanta.
If you had too many big wings with blades on the end,
you'd kind of look like Kerrigan from Starcraft.
Oh, you're it.
I'm like M. Kerrigan from Starcraft.
I've been censored.
If you're going to be a Zerg, at least be a lurker.
Not some girl.
Kerrigan is ruler of the Zerg swarm.
Yeah, she also has boobs.
Yeah, but no nipples.
Hey.
What's up?
November sure creeping up, ain't it?
Can't stop that one.
Yeah.
Hey, what's the jive with Angela and Phyllis helping with the party,
you know?
Um, I just thought you could use some help, you know,
because Robert came in and thought the party seemed a little kiddy.
And I guess I agreed.
And maybe we could mix a little more 13 into the PG.
But that's it?
Hmm?
There's nothing about me or I.
Can we talk about it at the end of the day?
I gotta call.
I gotta make a call.
Oh, yeah, sorry.
Yes, we can.
Yes.
I don't know.
Hmm?
Gabe?
Sweetheart.
I'm throwing the Halloween party and I just want to amp it up a little.
I think it could use some extra pizzazz.