Hello, my name's Oscar.
I'm an accountant in Scranton, Pennsylvania, and I'm gay.
And I'm here to tell you that, yes, it does get better.
When I was younger...
What?
What's he doing?
He's searching out younger gays.
No, it's just a way to tell young people no matter how hard it gets for them, there's
a brighter future ahead.
With you?
No matter how hard it gets for you.
Kelly, seriously, I...
Just keep turning.
I'm just taking my makeup on your webcam.
Do you not own a mirror?
Webcams make me look the way I look in my fantasies.
I know, right?
What is it?
You always look so good in those things.
I'm throwing out all my mirrors.
Okay, as you can see, I now have a cool job at a dynamic workplace.
Being gay is a celebration of life.
It's a simple...
I'm sorry.
You can't sit idly by and have the gay youth of America misled by some reductionist pep
talk.
Sexuality is a spectrum.
It's a paradox to think of any sexual activity as normal.
It gets better, but it also gets vastly more complicated.
Hey, Robert, that guy, he looks just like you.
Oh, damn it.
Damn it.
God.
You okay, Robert?
Fine.
Put some ice on it.
In any case, it gets better.
Maybe not much better, but better.
Holy...
One, two, three.
I wanted to give a nice gift to the tenants in the building.
At first I thought muffin basket.
Then I thought, what's even more precious to people than muffins?
Can you just smile, please?
I don't want to!
Their own children.
We got that?
Just give it a homework.
Okay.
How is that?
For safety.
Okay.
Wait.
I'm just worried about the framing.
So if we could do maybe just another round of...
Totem pole.
We're the Native American symbols for success and confidence.
Sorry, folks.
This is going to be a while.
Okay?
Just hang tight.
Okay, Robbie, you know, let's just go to that photo booth at the arcade.
Do we have to get our photo taken today?
We got it taken yesterday.
Yeah, no, it's important.
These are memories.
My own parents never once photographed me as a child.
Live to 13, fit to be seen.
That was their motto.
Until that point, it's just a waste of film.
Hey, everybody.
Just a few hours left for the Free Family Portrait Studio.
Daryl, we'd love to see little Jada come by.
Angela, why don't you bring by your little angel?
No, thank you.
Jim, you've got those two cute kids.
We sure would love to see them.
I know why you're doing this, Dwight.
Last week, I may have gone too far.
I'll explain it quickly.
Basically, I found out where he gets his clothes dry clean,
custom ordered the same suit, made with Tearaway Velcro,
and you can film the rest.
What?
Damn it, Jim!
Now he's trying to get me to bring my children into work.
I think it's fair to be cautious.
Let me get this straight.
You lost all of it.
All your winnings.
$150,000.
But economy.
But investment.
You mean to tell me no one wanted an energy drink for Asian homosexuals?
They did not.
And you got half a million of these?
Well, I gotta try it.
I wouldn't.
Come on, it's still hard.
Flavor of that?
Coconut penis.
Coconut is pretty subtle.
Come on, man.
Can't you just give us a yes or a no?
I don't know, man.
Y'all quit with a lot of confidence.
I mean, it was like y'all came up in here dancing and everybody was...
Ooh, hold on a second.
If I were Val, I would break up with Brandon.
Then I would date the hell out of me.
I wouldn't give in to me too fast.
Let me buy myself some nice dinners and such.
But when I finally did give in, I would go crazy on myself.
Next.
I know.
Baby, let me get a few singles, all right?
What?
Let me get a few singles.
All right, can we clear some of this kid stuff out of here?
Sweet.
This is a promotional shop for my restaurant.
I'm selling three things.
Food, sex, and laughter.
Hold up.
Get that on again.
You like it?
No, no, no.
Hold on.
Hi, guys.
How's it going, man?
I'm good, thank you.
How are you?
Great.
Yeah, good.
How's it going, man?
I'm good.
Thank you.
How are you?
Great.
Yeah, good.
Oh, how the mediocre have fallen.
Oh, God.
Look, I'm not here to get my old job back.
I had my opportunity.
I blew it.
I'm moving on.