The Sabre Code of Conduct outlines the governing principles key to establishing and maintaining trust with our employees, clients...
Oh my god, kill me.
Hey! Alright. Obviously we all want to die, but we have to get through this, so...
Gabe? Go ahead. It's okay.
Oh, is it okay with you? Because it's not your work for me, so...
Comply with all applicable laws, regulations, policies and contracts governing our business. Be honest, fair...
I'm gonna do it.
...trustworthy in all your business activities and relationships.
Treat one another...
Oh! I'm going into labor!
Oh, okay, she's going into labor. Make way, everybody!
I know it's wrong to fake going into labor just to get out of things, but sometimes it's necessary.
I'm going into labor!
Should I have corn dogs? I mean...
Okay, three reasons you are wrong about True Blood. Number one.
I'm going into labor.
Here we go!
Hey guys, uh...
Can't keep saying you're going into labor. Everyone knows you're full of it.
Yeah. It's not fair, you guys.
Pitiful.
Never cry wolf.
Okay.
Oh.
Oh! Oh! Oh my god!
Oh my god!
Damn!
I'm really in labor! This is happening!
Okay, guys! Here we go, we'll see you!
How do you feel?
Good luck! Good luck!
False alarm.
Ow!
Everybody beat it!
Don't beat it. Stay where you are.
There you are. Bill and Joe Grafick said their shipment is late.
What'd you say?
Nothing. I just said that...
What would you say?
That it'll be the first shipment out today.
That is exactly the right thing to say! Do it! Get her done!
Phyllis, you just married Joe Order. Your new name is Phyllis Order. Get it?
I don't get it.
Jim, in regards to our high five scheduled for 4 p.m. today, it has been moved up to now.
We didn't have one scheduled.
What?! They took another client from us?!
Okay, bye.
Man! Business is war!
Customers, clients, it's like a war out there!
I am a leader. But you can only inspire people so much in a place like this.
So today, I'm turning the inspire factor up to 10, with a little help from my friend,
America's Bloodiest Battle.
Why even read business books? We should be studying war!
Going to places like Gettysburg, where is that?
It's right here in P.A.
Ah! Well, we should take a field trip there. I mean, that would be so cool!
I wonder if that bus downstairs is...
Okay, Andy, we get it. It's a trip to Gettysburg.
That sounds super inspiring! I'm in!
Gettysburg? Hmm, could be interesting. Second most northern battle in the Civil War.
Actually, it is the northernmost.
Ha!
The Civil War history industry has conveniently forgotten about the Battle of Shrewt Farms.
Whatever, I'm over it. It's just grossly irresponsible.
Charge!
Isn't Gettysburg like three hours away?
No. It's like two hours and 46 minutes.
Kind of a haul, so we should probably get going.
And Tuna, I made a special sandwich for you. Guess what kind?
Tuna?
Yes, Tuna of the land. Turkey with pesto.
And to drink?
Water.
Ho ho, I am in.
I'm excited. I've actually never been to Gettysburg.
My family was going to go once, but then my brothers convinced me that it was full of dead soldier zombies.
So I freaked out and we turned the car around.
But I'm older now. I can outrun a zombie.
This could be fun.
Yeah, well, the bus has free Wi-Fi, and I made special low sugar lunches for everyone.
Is anyone kosher or halal?
What's the halal option?
Dates, tabbouleh, and bagel with cream cheese.
Out.
You know, it's the same as the kosher option.
There's a lesson in there.
I mean, I can't force you to go. You're not my slaves, thanks to Gettysburg.
But who's coming with me?
I'm in.
I'm in too.
I guess I'm a sucker for historical fiction.
Anyone who's not going, you're dead to me.
You're uninvited. I don't want you to come.
But FYI, there will be leftover turkey and pesto sammies in the fridge.
Yes.
One for you.
Cool, thanks.
And one for you.
Thanks.
Oh, you missed your head.
There you go.
Phyllis, think fast.
Getting everyone on the bus? Check.
Giving everyone hats? Check.
Sexiest Eastern European girls? Check.
All right, guys, a little foreplay before we do it.
Fans of Ken Burns' jazz will most certainly enjoy Civil War.
You know, I just got Limitless on my iPad. I bet I can get it on the TV.
Isn't that the one where the guy becomes limitless?
It's just not appropriate.
I mean, if we were going to visit Bradley Cooper's birthplace,
I'd be the first one suggesting. I'd be rooting for it.
Limitless, limitless, limitless, limitless.
All right, all right, all right.
Knock food and stuff.
Here.
You like it?
Oh, you buy the picnic table? Then you've got to get the fire pit.
I can't get a fire pit. I have two babies.
The fire pit is a no-brainer.
Oh, hi there.
Hi, Robert. Hey.
How are you doing? Good to see you again.
Where is everyone? Where is Andy?
Andy took some of the other people on a corporate retreat to Gettysburg.
Well, I was hoping to talk out some ideas with Andy.
But what we have here is perhaps better.
By not going on the trip, you've shown you're the free thinkers of the office.
Robert, you got your sheep, and you got your black sheep,
and I'm not even a sheep. I'm on the freaking moon.
So here's what we can do.
Game changers.
Changes to the game such that the game can never be played the same way again.
Everyone, brainstorm some innovations.
Don't be afraid to get weird with it.
Meredith!
Get excited!
Okay.
You guys! Get excited!
Shh! Movie's almost over.
All right! We're here. Limitless can wait.
Fun fact, in France, they call Limitless the man with many capabilities.
Whoo! Ladies and gentlemen, the 1800s await you.
We can watch Limitless on the way back.
I got a source code on the way back.
All right.
Whoo!
So incredible.
Such a beautiful place could have seen so much pain.
You don't really know what you're talking about.
Really?
You're not appreciating it in the right context.
Hey.
Where are you going?
Visitor center. Can I grab a map?
Of the memorials?
Yeah, we're not going to the visitor center. We're not tourists.
No, of course we're not tourists. We're just people that aren't from here who are taking a tour.
Yeah, sign says, begin tour here.
Well, what it should say but doesn't is, unless you're going on the very specially created
and meticulously researched Andy Bernard tour.
Oh, that must be what it says in Chinese at the bottom.
Come on, we got a lot of ground to cover.
Gabe, what's up? Don't be shy. Come on.
What's with all the kids? Isn't it a school day?
Excuse me, do you mind if we get a picture?
Uh, yeah, okay. Quickly, quickly.
In the center, Chancellor'sville, Lee brought his army up the Shenandoah Valley right through here.
They stopped in this field for a picnic, which they called lunch.
Yeah, but I'm confused.
Total Deaths belongs to Gettysburg, but when you're talking about DPA, that's deaths per acre,
nothing beats the Battle of Shrewt Farms.
Oh, DPA sounds way more important than Total Deaths.
Oh, it is. And you should read some of these letters that the soldiers wrote home.
I mean, it makes the Battle of Gettysburg sound like a bunch of schoolgirls wrestling over a hairbrush.
I'm telling you, they're heartbreaking, too. So beautifully written.
Dwight, what are you telling this girl?
The truth.
Stop filling her head with nonsense, okay? She doesn't know any better.
Oscar, I'm so glad you just got here. I would have believed everything he said.
No, no, no. You're filling her head with nonsense. You and the history books, I'm telling the truth.
Interesting.
Yes. Thank you. All of history has been whitewashed.
Really? Why don't you tell us the real history, Gore Vidal?
Okay, I will. I don't know who that is, but I'm going to tell you this.
He's a historian.
Gettysburg was very important. Credit where credit is due, okay? Big mad props to Gettysburg.
Was it, however, the most northern battle of the Civil War?
Not by a long shot!
Yes, yes, yes.
No, it was not. No, it was not. Was it the second most northern?
Sure. I will cede it was the second most northern most battle.
Was it the northern most? No. Get out of here!
Get out of here!
I am so eager to hear your game changers. Let's dig in, shall we?
May I go first?
Absolutely.
Raw fish. The disgusting food from Japan that Americans would never want to eat.
Now we can't get enough of it. From movie stars to construction workers, sushi is what's for dinner.
Let me throw another idea at you. Origami.
What?
The crazy art of paper folding from, that's right, Japan.
Don't you wish you could go back to 1980 and open the first sushi restaurant in Manhattan?
We can do that with... origami. It's the sushi of paper.
This idea hasn't gripped me. What else did you come up with?
Well, I had to memorize the presentation, Robert, and it took a long time to build the swan, so...
That was bad.
If your woman is like mine, I bet you come home to hear the same thing all the time.
This paper is so hard. It scratches. Why can't there be a paper just for me?
Well, now there is. Paper. Paper for women. It's pink, scented, and silky soft.
Now you can watch the game, and she can write a letter to her sister.
The situation you described...