Hey guys!
Hey!
Pam!
Look what I can do now that she's no longer pregnant!
Bam!
Are you glad to be back?
Yeah.
Yeah, I mean I could have used another week or three.
You still had eight weeks more than we did.
Well, it's not exactly a vacation.
Hello everyone!
Remember?
Little old me.
Hi!
What are you doing here?
You just had our baby!
Our collective Dunder Mifflin family baby.
Four days ago.
I wanted to come back to work.
Not everybody needs some long, luxurious Parisian maternity leave.
Damn, girl!
Your body!
Angela!
You look amazing!
Really?
I feel like this big rhinoceros.
Anyway, I wanted to thank you guys for covering for me, so I made some treats.
I've got brownies and magic cookie bars.
Oh, Angela, those brownies have walnuts in them.
And I think Kevin's allergic to walnuts.
You're allergic to walnuts, right Kevin?
Extremely, but I'm gonna fight through it.
Aw, it's okay, Angela.
I have mommy brain too.
I don't know what that is, Pam.
I made a batch with no nuts, special for you, Kevin.
Sit here.
When did you find time to do all this?
Babies sleep a lot, Pam, if you feed them enough.
Brownie, Pam?
Thank you.
Oh my gosh.
It's really good.
I wouldn't know.
I'm watching my weight.
So you guys, you know what's an even more useful treat is cash.
So, we wanted to say thank you.
Nope.
Okay.
Dwight, I have exciting news for you.
What?
I think you're going to like it.
You can't tantalize me.
Oh, maybe I can.
I got an email from corporate that told me that you got a promotion.
Right?
I mean, that's not the kind of thing you want to read quietly at your desk.
If you make me head of sales one more time, I swear.
No, this is legit.
You will be assembling a team to go to Tallahassee for three weeks to develop and launch a chain
of Sabre stores.
Yes!
Yeah!
The Shrewts have a word for when everything in a man's life comes together perfectly.
Perfektenschlag.
Right now, I'm in it.
I finally get a chance to prove myself to corporate.
I am assembling a competent team.
I am likely a father.
I am so deep inside of Perfektenschlag right now.
Just to be clear, there is a second definition, perfect pork anus, which I don't mean.
I guess your little trip to the sunshine stage paid off because Robert asked for you personally.
Well, my passion for the pyramid is well known in the industry.
But tell me, was I on a short list of some kind or did he just pick me outright?
No, you know, forget it.
Forget it.
Don't even want to.