I mean, my doubts are blasted.
I wish they had a chart for how much protein powder to scoop
for a 180-pound man with no fat.
Protein powder, huh?
Cut it with water?
Why don't you just take estrogen?
There you go, boys.
See how Papa takes care of you?
I remember when people thought biceps were all that.
They'd flex them all night at the discotheque.
Oh, I bet you think it's all about core, huh?
Yeah. Core's critical.
There are four tenets of Pilates that I live my life by.
One, lengthen.
Two, elongate.
Listen, guys, I think we all want to know the same thing,
right? Who's the strongest?
There's only one way to solve that.
Thigh curl contest.
I'm not sure I can do that.
All right, here we go, everybody.
May the manliest man win.
Go.
Feast on this, Lewis.
I love the burn.
Burn is where I live.
Come on, Gabe, you can't handle his hamstrings.
You're getting hypnotized.
Speed set. One.
One. Two.
Here, this is for your elbows. For your elbows.
You're welcome.
Six.
Quick phone call from you guys. Keep going.
Eight. Nine.
Ten.
We got it?
Very funny, Jim.
Yeah, Jim. Way to mock us for perfecting our bodies.
Everyone, conference room now.
Is he there, Grandpa?
I don't need your help.
Just...
Morning. Good.
Somebody left in such a hurry this morning
that she forgot...
these. Oh.
You know, the only thing more delicious than your feet
is the feast that I'm going to prepare for everyone.
Andy, if you're going to hang out for a while...
uh...
What's this?
This dumb new rule Robert made.
He just wants visitors to sign in.
Is this Robert's attempt to embarrass me?
No. Of course not.
It's just, I think it's like if we make an exception for you,
then we have to make an exception for the water guy,
and then it's like, where does it end? So it's...
Why is it when other people spend all their time at the office,
they're rewarded for it?
And when I do it, I am told it's a little much.
Is it because I'm not an employee anymore?
Because that's what it feels like.
All right, well, enjoy the alumni game. Good.
We have a deal? Thanks, Jeff. Thanks so much, Earl.
Wow, simultaneous sale.
And they said it couldn't be done. Screw them.
A lot going on, guys. What's happening?
Binghamton branch closed last night.
All the clients are up for grabs.
That was a fine branch.
Things are really bad under Robert, California, I guess.
It's like a festival of poo.
Hey, come on, language.
Yeah, and we're not interested in your sour grapes, okay, Jim?
Tell him where he can stick his grapes.
In the fridge.
No, Jim, the butt in his butt.