You
Oh
Yeah
I knew it Kevin soon as I heard that rapper you really have to say oh, yeah every time you get a candy bar
I can't help it Oscar. It's just really good. Oh
Yeah, my hands are tied. All right, not bad at all. I think we can beat 20 minutes though
So let's try again get it all out now if you have to it was a raccoon eating a hamburger like a person
You need to stop banging your pen on your desk or it's gonna drive me insane
Okay, does anyone have a first-aid kit check out this song?
I mean it looks like a little hamburger. All right, here we go. Everybody get ready in three two. Good luck one
Love letters. Yes, I
Love it. What else can be done with paper? You can write a book about chairs books
Excellent Jim Andy, please please just stop you can do infinite things with paper. Oh
Did you hear that
Infinity there is an infinity of things that you can do with paper now who wants to buy some paper
Very nice very nice sales pitch for our clients that don't know what paper is I'm talking about you guys
Who in this room right now wants to buy some paper
Let's get high on our own supply Andy. You want us to buy our own paper?
Yes, Robert said that we needed to double our sales growth to 8% by the end of the quarter
That's today and we are eight hundred and thirty dollars short and I can't afford to keep buying paper from us
So today we need to sell eight hundred and thirty dollars of paper and the next quarter
I need to sell the twenty two hundred dollars of paper that's in my garage
All right
If you're not gonna help us out by buying our own paper then
Could you try to sell eight hundred dollars more paper than usual today? That would be amazing
And he's the last day of the quarter. We've already called all our clients
So making that much in a day is gonna be tough not helping tuna. Yeah, I'm sitting on 2500 in sales
I could make it any time but those are my way till the separation is legal sales
We got to figure this out
Think of the look on Robert's face when we tell him we met our 8% goal. Oh, well we get to see that look
No, that's why that's why I said think of it
And we're gonna do our best but you know what at the end of the day seven point whatever percent is pretty good
Have I mentioned that it's also quite good for amateur animation
Took me two weeks
Animals machines vast virtual armies all of these things I have successfully managed
The only thing I haven't managed is people I
Saw an ad on the Sabre website for an open manager position in their printers division
I spoke to Robert, California about it and he said for me to come by and see him sometime
So like a Spanish conquistador, I have come to Florida to claim what is rightfully mine
Dwight's route for Robert, California
Hello, mr. Shrewd. I'll tell him you're here. Can I get you anything at all? I'm not here to be given anything
I'm here to take what is mine. Oh, I'm glad you're on our team here. Please have a seat
Dwight
What are you doing here?
You don't know of course I know
Hmm impressive office you have here
Surrounded by shrubbery like a squirrel's office
Corporate says to me Gabe we need you in Scranton Scranton says Gabe go back down to Florida. You're needed there
So Tuesdays and Thursdays, I'm up there Mondays Wednesdays and Fridays. I'm down here. I
Can think of no better way to confront my deathly fear of flying?
Dwight Robert you made it
Impressive initiative. I don't know what's worse the
trip or the destination
Well
Let me settle in and I'll be with you shortly very good
C-SPAN
So my dad says an accountant can really help you out if they're willing to play ball those were his words
Gosh, Andy, you had a great quarter
Okay, Robert will understand $800 isn't a rounding error so make that error
I can make that error
Well, it's just I know that making errors sounds like your kind of thing
But it's a little more complicated than that. I just I really need a real accountant on this
What do you say
I'm leaving early today because tonight I have a trivia contest in Philadelphia
And the other crunch time I would love to stay and cook the books for you
So you can save face in front of your CEO but tonight is trivia. Calypso
What it's only the biggest night of trivia of the year. There's a thousand dollar prize
I'm committed to my friends. They're committed to me. You know what?
Go have fun
There's a trivia contest at a bar in Philadelphia stuff right there I love it I mean I didn't even say what it is
It's trivia in Philadelphia
But here's the best part the prize is a thousand dollars and if we win we can use that money to buy paper here
Close the gap on our 8% profit increase. That's a great plan. Yeah, you like all right
All right, good stuff. I'm so psyched
You guys are into it cuz I thought I was like this sounds really stupid
You just made a good idea a great idea. There is one problem with this plan
What we'd have to leave work like right now to do this
You can reduce your prices by 10% or we're gonna be finding a new source for our morning bagels. All right
Gabe I always wondered what it is you did around here now I found out you're the bagel guy. Yeah, but not just bagels all unwanted problems
Question what's the most important appliance in your house meat grinder too slow. It's the toilet and
I am the toilet of this office. I flush away annoying problems
So others can keep their hands clean and just like a toilet I am essential
You know Gabe
You could have gone with garbage disposal
Incinerator or eraser and instead you chose toilet. God bless you. You are an American classic Dwight
Today is not my day at all. I'm afraid I'm not gonna be able to meet with you
But I'm leaving you in the very capable hands of our CEO but I can give you this pitch in one minute
With you later. No, no, no, I I don't want you to rush it. Okay
Trust me meet with Bill. He's a great person to know I'll dialogue with him tonight
CEO to CEO. What a difference a letter makes still an important position still a chief
You're really gonna like Bill. He he has me toilet a lot of people for him
I'll be phone Gabe Lewis speaking
Don't bother bill with this. He used to go put out a fire on the home front
Just wait 20 minutes and then I want you to listen to Dwight's pitch make him feel valued make him feel heard
Your wish is my command. It's a command
There's a funny law of business known as the Peter principle
Every employee it gets promoted until he reaches the level of his incompetence
Right now Dwight as a salesman has reached his highest level of competence
Now he's feeling the pull of moving up or moving on my job is to make sure that neither of those happens
I don't believe this
What are you doing here Andy you left us no choice, but this should put a smile on your face
How would you like to be captain of the Dunder Mifflin team?
Although I reserved the right to overrule you. No, I got a quota to hit
I don't care how I hit it and you guys thought this was a good idea
I thought it was a fun idea
There were times on a two and a half hour drive when I experienced doubt that's the thing about long drives
You know, you always gonna this is a gay bar. Wait what?
Everyone in here is gay. Yes, it's a gay bar. So you guys want to go home now?
What does it say about you that you followed me here
That you think you're gonna win your sales quota at a gay bars trivia night
It says that I believe in my staff's intelligence and that I'm willing to try anything
Not that anything good luck
Oh
All right, we need to divide up into teams but it's winner-take-all so no need to divide evenly
We need an a team a backup team and a just have fun team
So you guys all know yourselves good timers follow me
Backups
Go on kids, you know, you don't belong here
Agey, okay. All right everybody nice self-awareness
Except
Hey
I'm just a woman
All right. First question everyone Ray Charles famously had this state on his mind
What is its capital? No, we got this
Let's reverse engineer this you're a black singer