Oh
Who put this away empty is it empty it's not my job to order coffee I order tea
Andy corporate is faxing you something huge what?
200 pages yeah, but including the cover page, and it's not reading it mostly looks like forms. You need to follow like a matlip
That's it
There are so many things that happen throughout the day that really get you down. How do I deal with getting down I get down
Yeah
Specifically down to the warehouse where I really get down to business what business the business of getting down
Val I need the space
All right guys clear out everybody out promise me you're gonna clean up
I can't promise what I'm gonna do or not do promise me that obviously I'm gonna clean up
Stress is like the uptight mayor of a town who's saying hey, we're uptight you can't dance
And then you have to be like oh yeah mayor stress. We'll watch this and then
We dance
How we dance
Oh
Sex also works
Hey James back from jury duty hey Tuna back
Oh look at this tuna wrap okay?
Handroll yeah
How is jury duty pretty uneventful actually can't believe that lets someone like you serve on a jury
Let's be questioned the whole judicial system. What was the case hit and run?
Case of the hit and run that's exciting. Did you send him to the slammer?
No, not guilty of course you found him not guilty. Oh
He apologized, and I just really want him to like me hmm. We're best friends actually
We're going wine tasting next weekend if you want to come not coming half plans
Okay, I did get called into jury duty and
They released me around noon, so didn't think it was worth it to come back to work for a half day
And then the next morning Pam was a little overwhelmed with the kids so I took an extra day to help out
And then three other days happen
Is it black because that would be hilarious why
You know would it be more hilarious than Angela having a Chinese, baby a little bit yeah
Right guys back me up
Oh
Did I win the pool?
No right month wrong year well no one won the pool Angela wasn't due for another month
We should all go to the hospital visitor. Oh, I'd love to but um
Oh man, I would but I can't miss any more work
Well Kevin and I have to go because accounting is its own little family
Yeah, Oscar's the dad I'm Oscar's dad and Angela's my mom
Everyone our very own Angela we all got the email some of us are gonna. Go visit. Oh, I am so in I
Love maternity wards. It's the perfect blend of love and horror things can go so wrong or so right
Come on judge Judy tell us your case. What were the deets?
I was actually a pretty boring case that could be boring you were there for five days
That could be boring you were there for five days till the latest yeah, you owe us
I had to stay until six twice to cover for you my wife got to the TV first had to sit through damn
Rizzoli and damn miles yeah my car got smashed visiting one of your clients, and I had to have it detailed
And they took my meter change
Wow, I'm really sorry yeah, I never considered that my week off would make everyone else's job harder
At least I could do is give him a good story
So if he was here, and then the car came and did things like that
Yeah, so it had to be a double backflip actually you know when I was on a J duties
Triangle case we used to recreate the various stranglings with empanadas from at Ernesto's
Oh man Ernesto's that was our favorite restaurant, too
Even food truck Ernesto's was the food truck
Toby shut your hole about the empanadas nobody cares about the empanadas
I was in Los Angeles last year Jim tricked me into thinking I'd want to walk on part on NCIS
But that's not important while I was being kicked off the lot
I saw food trucks everywhere everyone in Los Angeles eats from them and nobody calls them restaurants
Guys I don't know how many of you have seen game bring it in
I don't know how many of you have seen a premature baby before it's gonna be really tiny so please don't say anything offensive
Got that bimbo?
Got it bimbo
Yes?
Knock knock
Hi
Hey
I don't I don't want what are you guys doing here?
You wanted to say hi to the newest little dunderbufflinite?
Well meet our not so little bundle of joy Philip Halstead Lipton
Philip is so fat
Kevin
You warned me not to say anything if it was tiny Oscar but you didn't prepare me for a big giant fat baby
Yes he's substantial
He's more than substantial he's a monster
So this whole hit and run thing there's this one part I can't figure out you said it was at a four-way stop
Uh huh
And the victim rode his bicycle into the left-hand turn lane but the perp was already in the left-hand turn lane?
See that's what I'm having trouble with because the fact is you never said he was on a bicycle
Busted Halpert yes Andy get out here
I never said he was on a bicycle I just said I wasn't listening to you
I am making a citizen's arrest you have the right to remain silent you have the right to beg for mercy you have the right to request judgment by combat
Dwight's rights
What's up gangsters?
Jim was lying about jury duty he was lying the whole time so he could go do yoga or go canoeing I don't know what this pervert likes
Fire him
Dwight not everything is a conspiracy theory
I have Jim on the record saying that the victim
Dwight I have me on the record saying to you take a chill pill
I don't need to take a chill pill
Right there
Down the hatch
I really don't want to take the chill pill
That a boy good now
Jim
Okay okay
But let's just say that Jim was lying about jury duty you would have to fire him right?
Yeah sure of course and fire him to ten bucks too
Good enough for me
And Pam was just going crazy trying to take care of Philip because Cece has been out of control recently
And look Andy it doesn't matter the truth is I just feel terrible lying to you
I feel terrible getting lied to
No one has ever lied to me before
Okay I think the best thing to do right now is just come clean and tell everybody
No not after what I told Dwight about firing you no here's what we're going to do
We're going to have ourselves a good old fashioned cover up
Have you ever heard of a Connecticut cover up?
No
You know why you never heard of it?
Covered it up
Are you sure you can keep this under wraps?
They used to call me King Tut because I'm so good at keeping things under wraps
My nickname was actually King Butt because I had a king size butt
Where you want to go?
Okay everybody gather around I've got a real special surprise for you
Ernesto
Hola Tommy
Hey
I remember Mr. Toby very well he was a very good client
I'm going to say I when I'm talking for Ernesto so instead of he says blah blah blah
I'm going to say I say blah blah blah but that's for him
Anyway it was something like he remembers Toby
I remember Toby
Oh Jim
Hey this guy look familiar?
It's the empanada guy
Holy **** damn it Toby
No I wasn't asking you
Ask him if he remembers Jim
Do you know Jaime?
No
He says no
He says no, boom!
Yeah but who remembers all their customers I mean I can name like three of our clients
He remembers Toby the most forgettable man in the known world
I don't want any problems I see a lot of people they come from everywhere to eat my empanadas
He doesn't want any trouble he sees lots of people
They come from all around to eat his delicious meat pockets
You guys are going to love these so empanadas on me you guys got to try them
Usually I'm a burrito guy but you won't tell I won't wink wink
Great and while we're enjoying these delicious empanadas Jim why don't you tell us your story again
Why everybody's heard it
Walk us through it what time would you get there every morning
He murders you out