Oh. Little help.
Wow, your hair is really thinning.
Standing has proven to be healthier, increases productivity, and just looks cooler.
Picture someone doing something heroic.
Now, was he sitting or standing?
Not counting FDR.
Every second you sit there is an hour off your life.
Look at all of you. I feel like you're in a suicide cult.
No, no, no. You're way off on that one.
Are you really comfortable standing there? I tried one of those, and I just couldn't find the sweet spot.
Hey guys, let's just all admit it, okay? Dwight's better than us.
He had the guts to stop sitting, and he's never, ever gonna go back on it, right?
That's right, Jim.
Hey, man. Hey.
Taking the load off, huh? No, putting the load on, more like.
Good luck with that. Last thing I need is luck.
Thank you so much.
Mm-hmm.
I'm gonna go get some water.
I'll be right back.
Thank you so much.
Mm-hmm.
What are you up to? Oh, just, what are you doing?
Give that back. Come on. Prank.
Oh, that's real creative. You know what? You're right.
I'm not gonna do this. It's not my best,
because you could easily just bend over and pick that up, right?
I could. I just don't feel like a lizard. Because you're sitting?
Standing. Okay. Don't. Because you're sitting? Standing.
You know I have to do this. I know.
Ah!
Andrew Baines Bernard.
I think you could just do Andrew Bernard.
I love filling these out, because it's like, oh, I'm taking a test,
but I know the answers.
In four seconds, my wife is going to be coming through that door.
I told her she can work here under no circumstances.
She cannot be allowed to happen.
Thank you so much.
I'm not gonna be allowed to happen.
There you are, honey. How on earth did you miss the elevator?
What was that? I don't know. He wasn't talking to me.
But if I were you, I wouldn't hire his wife.
That's why my foundation, the Dream for a Wish Foundation,
is gonna put them out of business. They're not gonna know what hit them.
Everyone, I'd like to introduce my wife, Mrs. Robert California.
Mrs. California, this is everyone.
Hello.
Susan, please.
Last night at dinner, Susan and I were talking about her returning to work.
So she's here today to see if there's a good fit.
Something tells me it just might work out.
This is Andy Bernard, the regional manager.
Hello, nice to meet you.
Hey there. It's a pleasure. Welcome.
Andy, would you be so kind as to show Susan around the office,
introduce her to various departments, find a place where she'll shine?
I would love to, but I have to be completely honest with you guys.
We're 100% staffed up.
Andy, let's see if there's a good fit first.
Then we'll talk.
All right.
So Roberto California doesn't want to work with his wife.
I get it.
And he wants to give his wife a job.
Totally get it.
What I am struggling with is the part of this that's impossible.
I love my wife.
Knock, knock, knock, knock, knock, knock.
You don't have to say it if you're doing it.
Remember how you said that you were looking for a place in the office
to do calisthenics and aerobics?
Weightlifting, yeah.
Well, today's your lucky day.
I have opened in this very office building Dwight Schrute's gym for muscles.
Want to take a look?
I'll take a look.
Your path from obesity begins right here.
I've been meaning to join a gym for my health.
I used to say I wanted to live long enough to see a black president.
I didn't realize how easy that would be.
So now I want to live long enough to see a really, really gay president
or a supermodel president.
I want to see all the different kinds of presidents.
Obese people in my office building are a drain on resources.
Chairs wear out faster, takes more freon to keep them cool,
they flush the toilets more often,
plus their massive BMs bust the rivets on my pipes.
But a gym turns fat into cash.
All right, the DM Express is pulling out.
All right, well, it's really nice to meet you, Brian.
It's actually Ryan.
Oh, Ryan.
Bitch.
We will start here at Aaronville.
Hi.
Perception, your classic one-man operation.
Although I was watching a movie and Meryl Streep had two secretaries.
I was watching a movie and a bunch of apes took over San Francisco.
Just saying.
Two secretaries could convey a sense of importance and success to our clients.
Certainly worth exploring, wouldn't you agree, Andy?
I'll explore exploring it.
Good.
I have this under control,
so I'll just duck out and run the company for a while.
Okay.
Okay, next stop on the tour, sales.
Here we go.
Station stop, Jim Halpert.
Oh, boy, a resident truth teller.
All right, have at it.
Let it rip.
What do you hate about this place?
Well, it's sales,
so you have to be able to live in the world of rejection.
Maybe you do.
Hi, I'm Dwight.
Sales is really not so hard, okay?
It's paper.
We have it, and they want it so bad, they are willing to pay for it.
Jim.
Well, it's not that easy.
It's kind of sometimes difficult.
It's the second easiest job in the world, being a mom.
I love shopping, and sales is just the other side of that.
That's true.
You know, if you joined our sales department,
you would be working very closely with our department head, Mr. Dwight Schrute.
That's me.
Dwight, why don't you tell Susan about some of your hobbies?
Oh, survival skills, ranking of animals.
Maybe over a beer after she's closed her first sale.
Well, make that a red wine, and I'll tell you my animal rankings.
Oh, how am I supposed to pull this off?
The entire office is being nicer to her than they've ever been to me.
What I wouldn't give for one of Phyllis' classic room-clearing farts right now.
Ready?
What do you think? Huh?
Um, no. No, this is not a gym.
This is like a scene out of Saw 5.
You haven't even looked around yet.
Look.
Gravel bucket squat yoke.
Right?
Hmm.
Dedicated phone book ripping station.
You ever cut tin before?
No.
Five yards in, and your forearms will be on fire.
Plus, I will buy the tin back from you that you cut for two cents a yard.
Now, let's go over membership.
I'm gonna need the first months and the last months up front for $49 a month,
but every third month is $59 a month.
But the fourth month is a discount month at $19 per month.
Obviously, you know how a gym works.
So you know I'm not gonna pay money for this.
You want people to come to your gym?
Make a real gym.
Daryl.
Ah!
Make a real gym.
I was thinking accounting might be a good fit,
because I really clicked with Oscar, and I do have some experience with bookkeeping.
But we already have a surplus of accountants as it is.
I would work in customer service, um, HR even.
Those are fully staffed as well.
Are you telling me that there is no one in this entire office
that could use an extra pair of hands?
Yes.
I am the CEO, and I am telling an employee of mine what to do.
Let me beat around the bush for a second.
Our chairman of the board has some very strong feelings.
Well, it's all right. This is very uncomfortable.
Obviously, there's no place for me here, so thank you for trying.
Why don't we just let it go?
No, absolutely not.
Andrew, there must be something you can do.
There must be. Think.
Well, there are a lot of considerations.
I would be eternally grateful.
It's not a bad thing to have the CEO owe you one.
All right.
Well, then welcome aboard.
So what happens next?
We get you over to HR and then get you set up with accounting.
Hang on. Hello?
Say hello, Grandma.
Hi, Gam Gam.
Hold one finger up to Susan. He'll just be a second.
You numbskull. You were given a very simple task.
I could not have been more clear with you.
Now, say, are you taking your medicine?
Are you taking your med meds?
Why can you not say exactly what I tell you?
Undo this. Undo it.
You didn't say goodbye to your grandmother.
We promised we'd never say goodbye.
Attention.
I am now accepting memberships for the Dwight Schrute Gym for Muscles.
First 20 members can take advantage of our pay what you weigh promotion.
All I need is another gym, as if I don't have enough drama.
We have a gym at home. It's called the Bedroom.
Who's spotting who? Don't use the bike in the corner.
That's Bruce's. Jeremy says.
Enough, Oscar. Enough.
Kelly?
I have these sneakers, which are basically just like a gym for your feet.
I'm not sure I'd wear them.
I don't know.
That's OK. I know how to build a business.
You gotta get the black people to do it to get the white people to do it.
Then you gotta get the black people to stop doing it.
One step at a time.
Did you bring your passport with you?
Who walks around with their passport?
Well, I do. I was ready for adventure.
Have you had any?
No.
Hey, guys.
So Robert doesn't want his wife working here,
so now that she is, we have to drive her away.
Andy, if you didn't want her working here, then why did you hire her?
Oscar, it was a mistake.
But one that can be fixed by all of us being mean to her.
How can we do that? She's simply wonderful.
This is all pathetic.
I am not asking. I am ordering.
How mean are we talking about?
It would be great if she were gone by lunch.
Aaron, you're up. Find her a place to work, but not too comfortable.
Got it. I know exactly which stapler to give her.
Here you go.