Hey, so this isn't matching up with this,
and I'm not sure which one's right.
Can you just hunt down the original for me?
Yes, me too. All right.
Hey, Kev, what were you saying before about the paperwork?
Me do it now. Go. Stop worrying.
Kevin, do you feel okay?
Me feel good. Body strong.
Sleep big last night.
Yeah, I think we should get him to the hospital.
Yeah, all right, Kev, why don't you come with us?
No, no, guys. He's fine.
He's fine.
He's always been like that.
No, he hasn't.
I mean, he's gotten worse over the years.
He's making a statement.
It's an ironic comment on our expectations of him.
A funhouse image of our model of Kevin.
You keep thinking that.
Me mechanic, not speak English.
But he know what me mean when me say car no go,
and we best friends.
So me think why waste time say lot word when few word do trick.
Kevin, I appreciate what you're trying to do.
Thank you.
Here we have a word code, the same way we have a dress code.
And what we're talking about is basically the speech equivalent
to just wearing underpants.
Sometimes words you know need to be said.
And words you know need use, but need need for talk talk.
But save time, more success.
Does it save time though?
Because we've been here for about an hour.
No me fault.
Kevin, at most you're saving a microscopic amount of time.
Many small time make big time.
And what are you going to do with all this time?
See world.
Kevin, you can't possibly save enough time to see the world.
Kevin, are you saying see the world or see world?
See world.
Oceans, fish, jump, China.
No, see right there.
That's the problem with your method,
because I still don't know if you're saying see world or see the world.
And it's taking a lot of time to explain it.
Fine, fine.
I'll talk normally.
When me president, they see.
They see.
When you're a kid, you picture a pilot going like this.
But then you learn that's crashing the plane.
The right way to do it is more like this.
Or better yet, like this.
Now that I'm manager, I think about that a lot.
I let Dwight run the meetings.
I let good people do good work.
And I stay out of the way.
This week we are rolling out the brand new Sabre tablet, the Pyramid.
Why is it shaped like that?
So you can tell your clients, unleash the power of the Pyramid.
It's huge. How much does it weigh?
Oh, no, no, no. Without the battery pack and the optional memory booster,
it's barely three pounds.
How much memory does it have without the booster?
How many L?
I'm sorry, L?
How many L to a K?
You're really going to want the booster.
How on earth are we supposed to sell?
I'll take five.
Andy, don't make us sell this stupid thing.
Oh, no, no, no, no. This is Dwight's meeting.
Thank you.
I just wanted to pop in and get your opinions on ties and tie clips.
Which combo do you think Robert's going to like more?
Just wear one of your bow ties.
No!
I mean, let him just, he should just explore other options.
Bow ties, no offense, are a black thing.
They're for rappers and NBA players.
I cringe when I see Tucker Carlson trying to pull off a bow tie.
It's like, yeah, Tucker, you're so street.
What do you think, C-span?
C-span?
Yeah. C-span, Cocker Spaniel.
Spaniel because of your Spanish bloodline, Cocker because...
Is this really the best use of our collective time?
I am still forming a first impression with Robert.
Once it is formed, we can all relax, okay?
I'm sorry to hijack your meeting, D-dub dog.
Had to pull rank.
Okay, let's look at some ties.
Here's how I'm going to help out from now on.
I'm going to not care, and I'm going to sit around quietly waiting for Andy's inevitable demise.
This is combo number seven.
No.
Ew.
I don't like that clip.
You're right. You're right. You're right.
Ugh. So hard to find an occasion for this clip.
I'd hang on to it though, because I can think of a bunch, like a 70s themed party.
Or like a 70s themed meeting, or 70s themed convention.
Sure.
1870s.
Thanks, T-dog.
Yup.
T-dog?
I thought I was T-dog.
Nope. He means tuna dog.
Tuna dog!
Look at me and Jim.
One of us is total blind ambition.
The other is, whatever dude, I just want to smell the flowers.
And we're both in exactly the same place.
Do you know that I have never smelled a flower?
I live on a farm, and I have never smelled a flower.
I just, I want to enjoy the people around here.
Everyone has a story, and I can't wait to hear them.
Your friend Neil Patrick Harris really made me laugh the other night.
Um, T-dog, you have a message.
Aaron, you don't need to call him that.
Andy wants us to, T-dog.
It's okay, E-dog. Who called?
Justine. She said she's coming by later.
Your ex-wife?
Wait, I thought she was a c*** and you c*** hated her guts.
No, no, no, no. I like her.
Well, I'm just quoting you. I would never say that about her. I don't know the woman.
No man, we get along now. Real well.
Wow. Alright, can't wait to meet her.
I'll introduce you.
Yeah, we had a few fights I suppose, but last night we put a lot of that to bed.
I can't tell you what I did with my ex-wife last night.
I have to sing it.
We took a shower, we were naked, we scat-dap-dap-doo-doo-doo-doo-doo-doo.
Hi, Dad.
Uh, oh boy. Hello, Andy. Excellent tie.
Would you be requiring a cold beverage while you're here?
I'd love some coffee. I was looking over your projections and I think we can do better.
Are you factoring in the whole national economy declining and all that?
Andy, do you know why I chose you?
I think I can sum it up with what I think is your favorite ice cream flavor? Vanilla?
Vanilla? No, no, no. You'll never guess. In a million billion years, you'll never guess.
You were saying you chose me. There was a reason.
Andy, can you inspire? Do you have that skill set? Can I inspire? I don't know. I don't know.
Oh, thank you.
Oh, sorry.
You'll just put it down.
That is very cold.
Yeah, it's old.
Why would I...
I asked if you wanted a cold beverage and you said coffee.
Why don't we get Robert a nice hot fresh cup and I will have this.
Andy, you don't want that.
I've been craving a freezing cup of old coffee.
Sorry.
You like her?
I do, yeah.
She likes you.
You know, we've both been into each other at different times and just never really synced up.
Now we're in this weird dance.
I'm afraid you've lost my interest.
Let me call you back.
I gotta go.
If the office superstore was supposed to put us little suppliers out of business, why are we still here?
This is where we go.
You'd go someplace else. That's not it. That's not the answer.
It's a answer.
It's a wrong answer.
There are no wrong answers.
Take a look at where you are. Where you once worked in a dying industry, you now work at its birth.
Those superstores are terrified of us.
Anybody know why?
Wait, they're terrified?
Let me tell you how I buy something these days.
I know what I want. I go on the internet and get the best price.
Or I don't know what I want and I go to a small store that can help me.
The era of personal service is back.
You are back.
You'll find that customers will pay our higher prices and then they will thank us.
And we will say to them, you are welcome.
Andrew, I chose you for a reason.
Leave these people.
Show me the best numbers this place has ever seen.
Last quarter we saw 4% growth. Double it.
You got it.
Double.
Done.
I'm not kidding.
Neither am I. It's already done.
I'm just kidding. It's going to take some time.
Double.
I thought the plane was flying pretty well on autopilot.
And then Robert California ran into the cockpit with a gun and he was like,
Fly this plane to Cuba and on the way bomb Texas.
Well, I don't know how to get there.
Or even how to fly, even.
And I don't have any bombs.
Hey.
What's up, guys?
Just thought we'd have a little rap session, talk about business, see how things are going.
Why don't you start?
If no one else wants to.
I was just thinking about Robert. Man, what a boss.
Just throws down goals, you know.
Anyway, how's the sales doubling project going?
How are we supposed to do that? We can't just press a magic button.
Of course not. There's no magic button.
You have to summon that.
If we could just double our sales, we already would have.
You're not making any sense.
He brings up two good points.
Do you have any new leads? Any new territories you want us to look into?
Maybe have an inn with a big client that we could get our foot in the door?
Dwight, anything?
We could talk about how fast children grow up and before you know it, they're out of the house.
You know what? We need to get our heads out of the box.
If we did have something, what would it look like? What would it be?
Tuna.
New leads, a new territory to look into, maybe an inn with a big company that we could get our foot in the door?
Fart.
Good zish.
Bad legs asleep.
Hello. I'm looking for Darryl Philbin.
Don't. Oh. You must think...
I'm not. I'm using the facts. This isn't... No, wait.
I'm not supposed to represent the company, right? There's usually an errand here.
Okay.
So... Darryl! A girl!
Revident in the Apricots Square.
What's up, darling? Everybody, this is Justine.
Hi, Justine.
Hello.
This is Jim and Oscar.
Hi.
Everybody.
Hello.
Kevin.
Can we go someplace private?
Follow me. I got a space.
After you. I've been thinking about you all morning.
I don't know what you did. I can barely walk today.
Jada called me. During recess. She asked me when you're moving back in.
What did you say to our daughter? That we're getting back together?
I just... Calm down.
One night together, and you think it's on.
You're an idiot! I told you it was a one-time thing.
Last night was good, right?
I said, touch and go, Darryl. You get a little touch, and then you go.
Stay the hell away from me.
She was very excited to meet all of you.
She's really great.