Oh, wow, it is raining cats and dogs out there.
Holy moly.
Phyllis says the same 12 cliches every time it rains.
So I promised everyone that if she says them all by noon today,
I will send out her hot chocolates.
So how's the drive in?
Nobody knows how to drive in the rain.
You don't say?
Yeah.
You know, the roads are actually the slickest in the first half hour.
The plants are going to love this.
Yeah.
I actually sleep better when it's raining.
Tell me about it.
Time's almost up. How many are left?
Just one.
This weather makes me want to stay at home curled up with a good book.
Phyllis, this rain, does it make you want to be doing something?
What do you mean?
You know, like, aren't some things just so nice and cozy in the rain?
Hey, come on.
Lots of things are cozy in the rain.
And that's noon. Exactly.
I mean, normally the rain would make me want to stay at home curled up with a good book,
but everybody's being so nice to me today.
I'm really happy being here.
My girlfriend's back and there's going to be trouble.
Hey, la, hey, la. My girlfriend's back.
Anyway, I know it's the end of the day. We just wanted to stop by and say hi.
Welcome home.
Thank you.
Hey, Kev.
Yeah.
Nice sweater.
Thank you. Nellie was nice enough to give it to me.
She's sweet.
I just wish there was pockets.
What happened to old Salty?
Nellie, let me Bob-alize him. His name is now Captain Mutato.
I've written quite a bit of X-Men fan fiction.
Captain Mutato is half man, half mermaid,
so he can fight crime as a man and make love as a mermaid.
Most of my writing involves the latter.
Eew, eew.
Yes.
Whoa.
Well, you must be the famous Nellie Bertram I've been hearing all about.
I am the famous Andy Bernard you have been hearing all about.
Oh, yeah.
I just want to thank you for jumping in and minding the store
during my temporary absence.
You are most welcome.
Anyway, now that I'm back, I would love to have my office back
whenever you get a chance.
No.
Obviously, we'll figure out the logistics
of moving all of this stuff out of here.
But, you know, the sooner the better.
Get back to normalcy.
No.
You know, just lay him in his crib and then bicycle his legs.
And then after Jim quiets down, you do the same thing with your baby.
But if he keeps having problems, just give me a call.
Oh, my gosh. Thank you so much.
But seriously, we don't want to bother you any more than we already have.
That's it.
We don't bother you guys. You're our friends.
Robbie, our amazing pediatrician, was asking us if we knew any girls.
And I said, I know the perfect girl.
Yep. Because Kelly is Indian.
And...
Oh, that's it.
Race had nothing to do with it.
I just knew they'd be good together.
Kelly has been a handful in the past.
But she's had a bad influence.
She's like an addict, and I just had to get her clean.
Get lower.
Also, little tip, never shake the baby.
Sorry, just to be clear, you're saying do not shake the baby.
Don't shake the baby.
A lot of times parents get frustrated because the baby's crying
and they shake the baby, and you got to...
You can't do that.
Don't shake our baby.
Yeah.
Okay. I'd never heard that before.
So thank you.
Oh, my God.
Yeah, I'm glad you said something.
Me, too.
Kelly and I broke up, and she can do whatever she wants.
And her new boyfriend seems oddly friendly.
Her new boyfriend seems awesome, if you're into Indian people.
I'm not.
Hey, um, what's the deal with this guy?
He's really into Kelly, huh?
Yeah, they're really great together.
Maybe we weren't right together, but it's weird.
I'd rather she be alone than with somebody.
Is that love?
That's about it, yeah.
Nellie, you've been terrific in your interim capacity,
but Andrew is the rightful manager,
so if you would just give him his office.
No.
I'm sorry.
This is what I was trying to tell you.
I'm not accustomed to people saying no to me.
Well, Bobby, get accustomed to it,
because then it feels so good when they finally say yes.
You're both adults.
I'm sure you can...
figure this out between yourselves.
I never allow sexual desire to influence a business decision,
so I find it best to recuse myself temporarily
until I've had a chance to make love
and then go back and analyse the situation rationally.
Buffett operates the same way.
I'm going to count down from five,
and if you are not out of my office,
I'm going to dock your pay $100.
Okay.
Five, four...
You can't dock my pay.
Angela!
Dock Andy's pay $100!
On it!
Great!
Um, five, four, three, two, one.
Angela, please dock Nellie's pay $100.
Angela?
Do you want to go again?
Angela!
Let's go again.
Five, four...
Oh, she's counting again.
Three, two, one.
Angela, $200!
On it!
Seriously, Angela?
I got a little bit of an anger problem.
Got me in some trouble a couple years ago.
When I see him start to get mad,
I just put my hand on his arm like this.
I know what. Let's go.
$10,000!
Five...
You're just saying numbers.
Four...
It's meaningless.
Three...
It's literally like...
Two...
There you go.
Hey, we're gonna have a nice hot date.
Hey, so last night was so not a big deal.
Oh, yeah, I was just tired.
We both were.
Plus, I was definitely not my normal sexy self.
What? No.
Are you kidding? You were so sexy.
Just the thought of you last night, like, crazy, turns me on.
It just didn't last night.
But really, it's not a big deal.
Yeah.
I know. It's not a big deal.
I found these the other day while I was journaling,
and they reminded me of you.
Oh, those are from our weekend at the Timeshare.
Yeah, the fractional ownership property.
Oh, we took this one right before we got in that huge fight.
God, I don't even remember what that fight was about.
You were being really bratty about where we would go out to dinner,
but all I remember is how pretty you looked taking those pictures of me.
Anyway, if you want to order prints of your own,
I can send you the link.
I am in love with Kelly Kapoor.
Again, that could change.
When you lost the manager job,
they didn't affect you outside.
I don't know if it's the next day or the day after that,
but I do know that right here, right now,
all I can think about is spending the rest of my life with her.
Again, that could change.
When you lost the manager job,
they didn't affect you outside.