Aaron. Yeah?
Hey, in two minutes, I want you to come into this meeting
and tell me that I have a really important phone call.
I'm not gonna take it,
because I want him to know how important the meeting is to me.
Who's calling?
Nobody.
Just say that I'm... just make it up that I have a phone call,
and that I'm gonna refuse to take it.
You're not gonna take it? Just make up a phone call.
It's not a real call. Oh.
Just make it up. Oh, oh, oh, okay.
And then come in and tell me.
Okay.
It doesn't matter what it is.
You're not gonna get it, though?
I'm not gonna take it.
And then he's gonna be like,
well, no, this is a really important meeting.
Copy that. Okay.
Okay, so tell me exactly what kind of deal
you are getting right now,
and I'll tell you how we can beat it.
Uh, well, we've been going with...
Andy. Yeah?
You have a very important call.
I'm sorry, I'm with a very important client.
They'll have to wait.
Are you sure? It's really, really important.
There is nothing more important to me right now
than this meeting.
Really?
Because your mother is dead.
Oh, my God.
I don't think she's dead.
She's dead.
She was hit by a bus.
She's not dead.
This is exactly the kind of thing my mom pulls.
This isn't one of those times.
It's the police.
They said it's the worst they've ever seen.
Andy, I'm really sorry about your mother.
My deepest condolences.
Oh, you must take this call.
It's...
Yeah, um, line one?
Line two.
Uh, okay.
Hi.
It's Darryl.
Aaron told me to pretend to be a cop
and say your mom died.
Oh.
Gosh.
Thank you, officer.
Look, man, this is a bad idea.
Did she have any last words or...?
Really? That is messed up, man.
Oh, make sure that your client gets the best deal possible.
You're a bad man, Andy.
That is so mom.
Your mom and her stuff can come back to get you.
It's no karma.
You do not want to be messing around with your mom.
All right, but thank you, officer.
I got to...
Aaron, please hold all my other calls.
Where were we?
Opposing'
Ass coefficient
Do we have to switch the late?
Oh, no, I'm fine. No, I should go fill out my paperwork.
Okay.
Oh, that was just me. Pregnant Pam.
And I make sounds much worse than this.
Oh, we know.
I'm training attempt to be my replacement
while I'm on maternity leave.
Oh, I should have mentioned I'm pregnant.
You probably didn't notice,
because it's impossible to tell because I'm so small.
But, yeah, I'm pregnant.
Oh, come on.
Hey, asking for a friend.
Do you happen to know if that new girl is single?
Mm, doubt it.
Yeah, me too.
You doubt it.
What's that?
Why do you doubt that she's single?
Honestly, I have no idea.
I just figured we'd save her from Ryan, right?
What are you doing with my lunch?
I'm delivering it from the fridge.
It's like a porno. Hey, did anybody order a pizza?
It's not pizza.
Yeah, and we're not about to make love.
I just thought maybe you'd want to eat lunch at your desk today
so that during lunch we could go down to the warehouse
and bang out a few tunes.
I like the sound of that. Is Kevin in?
Uh, you tell me.
So word on the street is she has a boyfriend.
Oh.
Well, she's probably a drug dealer.
That's the best way to land a hot girlfriend.
You just, uh, you get her hooked on blow.
It's gonna be nice to have just, like,
a healthy young, fit presence in the middle of the office.
Yeah, that's subtly speaking, strictly.
Yeah, she adds a nice presence. Good energy.
Yeah, it's gonna be nice to have someone hot at Pam's desk, huh?
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm not gonna do that.
I'm kidding. Oh, my gosh.
You guys, she's obviously super cute. I get it.
But I'd like to point out that there is 50 pounds more me to love
if that's your thing.
Pam, you look more beautiful now than ever.
Radiant. Thank you, guys.
Really, thank you. Very sweet.
Yeah, you have this sexy glow.
It's one of the most common fetishes.
Really? Well, thank you all.
No, it's not just pregnant women who don't get their due.
You know who's gorgeous?
Helen Mirren.
Helen Mirren. Yes, yes.
Have you seen her in a bikini? Amazing.
That would be the highest thing ever.