Okay.
Bye.
Everyone, stop what you're doing.
I have terrible news.
Dwight is no longer with us.
What?
He's gone, damn it.
He's been promoted to VP of Saber Retail,
and he's staying in Florida forever.
So he's alive?
Yeah.
That was him on the phone.
He sounds wonderful.
Well, the way you said it made it sound like he was dead.
How could I have been more clear?
He had a massive stroke of good fortune,
and he is now in a better place.
If Dwight's not coming back,
does that mean we can open his treasure?
You guys, we've gone over this.
There is no treasure.
When the team left for Tallahassee,
Dwight told everyone not to touch his treasure.
Don't touch my treasure.
Okay, you understand?
Obviously he wants us to obsess about it.
There's nothing in there.
Which is obviously what he would want us to think,
making it the perfect place to hide a treasure.
Oh, God, I'm Walsh on in the Princess Bride.
I think that Dwight wanted us to realize
that this conversation among friends is the true treasure.
Oh, no, no, no.
I am dying to know what's in there.
Yeah, I know, Oscar, we all are,
but nobody's gonna open it.
You'd have to be insane.
Hi, hello.
Now carefully open the box.
It's a photo of all of us.
Oh, that's so sweet.
Ah!
A dart? Are you kidding me?
Who would put a poison dart...
Well, I mean, I don't know that it's poison.
I mean, I just have to imagine.
God, I'm glad he's okay, though.
Kind of sounds like he deserved it,
opening another man's treasure and all.
Wow!
Well, Mr. Ball, it's been a pleasure.
Now give my regards to hell!
Ah!
All right!
Well swung, my VIP VP.
I am loving the chemistry between you two.
I am so happy Dwight is gonna be working alongside me.
We are a regular Archibald and his man George.
I bet. I'm excited.
Trick. There's no such thing.
It's not even a real English duet.
I just made you look like the Goat of Dover.
And that doesn't exist either.
You think you're excited? You should feel my nipples.
Bang!
Oh, that reminds me.
A little something from all of us.
Oh my gosh.
Thank you, Jim. That's so thoughtful.
Four!
Oh, yeah!
He doesn't even care.
Don't even care!
This is the last time I'll ever see Dwight.
It's a weird feeling. It's, um...
It's the word. It's not bittersweet.
It's, uh...
Sweet.
Yeah.
Hey, man. Selling cookies for Jada.
Want the same as last year?
What if I could? And I can, so I will.
Put me down for a one box.
Don't care what it is. Dealer's choice.
I'll put you down for shortbreads.
Damn it.
Knock, knock.
Hey, Sasha's first year in the troops,
and I'm selling cookies for her.
Would you like some?
No. No.
What? I've been selling here for five years.
This is my spot.
You can't claim territories.
This is the only place I interact with people.
Can't you sell it?
Your church, your barber shop?
Or chess club?
You know what?
It's your first time.
Let's put the office.
You can have sales, the annex, creed.
And I don't know, I'll just take accounting.
That's it?
Yeah, well, okay.
Thanks, Tara.
Okay, great.
All I need is Kevin.
Dude buys more cookies than everyone combined.
And then some.
When I first started selling him cookies,
he was a relatively thin man.
Not a thin man, mind you.
Relatively thin.
Hey, Lucy.
I'm home. Bye, Baloo.
Oh, here, let me help.
I'm so glad you're back.
It was so busy at the store today.
Really good cheese samples. I had like a hundred.
Irene hired me as her live-in helper.
We met at the store launch.
I told her I was moving here and I needed a place.
And it just sort of made sense.
I basically do everything for her.
I run errands, I do chores around the house,
I cook and clean.
Honestly, I don't know how she survived without me.
When can I introduce you to my grandson?
He's a wonderful swimmer.
Shallow and deep, and he does it all.
Well, today might be kind of tough, Irene.
I have to talk to my old boss, Andy,
and tell him I'm staying in Florida.
Thank you.
What kind of tea is this?
Oh, I boiled some Gatorade.
Oh.
In England, they put the holes a little bit
to the right, you see.
We'll just two of them, and then we'll just
If I may.
Try holding the putter.
You know, with your wrists here
and your thumbs here.
Oh.
That's right.
Your little finger.
Would you like to buy some cookies?
Cookies, eh?
Mm-hmm.
Oh, the springtime thinks that it's the best.
And falltime thinks that it's the best.
Coldtime has
kind of a strut.
And valentine's thinks that it's the best.
But gather around, peeps,
I'll tell you the truth.
Nothing beats the cookie season.
That's the truth.
It's not a scratch or sniff, Kil.
I know, but sometimes you still get a little something.
Hey, you tricked me.
You just wanted Kevin.
You're a good gang. You learned a lesson today.
See you next year, sport.
No, no, no, that's not fair. What if Kevin wants to buy cookies from me?
I do.
See? Doesn't mean anything.
Kevin, do you want to buy cookies from me?
Oh, I definitely do.
Huh. Hit the road, Jack.
No, you hit the road, Jack.
Hey, guys, come on.
Don't fight over me.
Why don't we split the order? It's only fair.
No, wait, no, I'm buying. I make the rules.
I actually do want you to fight over me.
I want to be wined and dined at 69.
Oh.
Metaphorically 69'd.
Ew, perverts.
No offense, Oscar.
Hop in. We have places to be.
No rest for the wicked.
All right, so...
I guess this is it.
Well, Jim, I just want to say that we haven't always gotten along.
And at times I've even hated your guts.
I'm sorry.
Bye-bye. I win.
It's fine, Dwight.
Robert! Race you to the clubhouse.
The gentleman's back. Woo-hoo!
Well, he's floored his problem now.
Oh, let Dwight have his fun.
Today will not be his day.
What's that?
I'm gonna tank the car.
I'm gonna take the car.
What's that?
I'm gonna tank the Sabre store at the presentation to the board.
I thought you liked the store.
No, the store is lovely.
You created a wonderful space to showcase our product line.
Great job. Cheers.
Thank you.
But there's a reason we sell our products online and over the phone.
Have you ever used Sabre electronics, Jim?
They're cheap. They're unintuitive.
The Sabre store would work if we adopted the carnival model of leaving town,
once everyone's wise to us.
Wow. You put it that way, I guess it does sound pretty terrible.
I couldn't just kill the project from the start.
Joe Bennett endorsed it.
Shame, though, I did like Dwight.
Robert! I'm gonna win! Ha-ha! I'm the gentleman! Suck it!
Bravo, Dwight! Very good.
Shame.
The math is simple, folks.
Deeper market penetration plus greater visibility will raise Sabre...
To the power of two!
How did that look?
I'm not just saying this.
That was the best thing I've ever seen.
I told you.
When you guys do that whole power of two shebang, how about I pop up also?
I guess we had to say power of three.
Hmm. Actually, you know what? Yeah.
That actually works. You'd spin off right.
You know what? That is a great idea, Kathy.
Write that down and print it out.
It's gonna make some really good toilet paper.
All right. There he is.
What are you doing here? I thought I got rid of you.
Can I just talk to you for one quick second?
What, your stylist ran out of messy spray?
Um, actually, it's for your own good. I think we should...
You wanna do something for my own good?
Turn around, walk out that door, do not stop till you get to Scranton,
find my cell phone charger, mail it back to me, and then go to hell!
Nice.
Hey, Halpert, anyone ever tell you you look like Wooly Willy?