What the hell? No, this is not happening.
Didn't you get the memo? It's Stare-Mageddon. Come on Stanley.
Dwight is having maintenance done on the elevator today, and he was really on top of it.
Weeks ago, he started the Stare-Mageddon Awareness Campaign.
The idea was to get us prepared, both mentally and physically, for a day that hopefully comes once in a hundred years.
It's a...Mageddon! Come on! Come on Stanley, stay in it!
I put 17 damn years into this company, and now they're making me climb Stare Mountain!
Our office has an unusually large number of unusually large people.
This is an abomination!
So when something as routine as elevator maintenance happens, and people are forced to expend cardiovascular effort,
we have to compare it to the end of time.
Red alert! Red alert! The reviews are in, I repeat, the reviews are in.
What? I just got a text from my brother, ScrantonTimesTribune.com. There's a review of the documentary.
What does it say? I don't know, Phyllis. I just got the text and started screaming red alert.
The alert was already set to red because of Stare-Mageddon. You think I should set it to double red?
I think we should.
The Office, an American workplace airing on PBS next month, is a documentary following the employees of Scranton's own Dunder Mifflin Paper Company.
In the series, which will air starting in May, we get an in-depth look at many interesting local people.
There's Kevin Malone, the full staffian accountant, Dwight Schrute, the head salesman, forever chasing a manager position he will never get.
What does Josh McAuliffe know about the paper business? He works for a news... thing.
Auntie Bernard, the rudderless trust fund child slash middle manager, whose incompetence is emblematic of a declining American economy.
Ouch. Sorry, Andy, that's...
It's okay. What the hell does he know?
A possible explanation for his lack of career focus is his surprising musical talent.
I want you to print that out for me.
I will.
Now that this documentary is coming out, my days at Dunder Mifflin are probably limited and, you know what, good.
Because this is not what I wanted to do with my life. I wanted to be my generation's Lisa Loeb.
Though it mostly focuses on the daily realities of office life, a lurid subplot reveals the hypocrisy of a local public figure, embroiled in a gay affair while preaching family values.
Oh, which public figure?
I bet it's Katie Corrick. I've been saying this for years.
No, I think they mean more like a politician.
You own the building. Why can't you fix the elevator in the middle of the night? Who do I look like? Jackie Joyner, Kersy?
Well, I did say it would be an inconvenience. You should have called me from downstairs. We could have met in the lobby. It's time to go out on a sale. Here we go.
Son, you lost your mind. I'm not going anywhere until you fix my elevator.
The buyer is your sister's friend. This is the printing paper for the entire school district of Lackawanna. You are coming, and that's an order.
You are not my damn boss and you never will be. Guess what? Never gonna happen. Pete, iced tea, three sugars, five creams.
Good morning, 3x5. Coming right up.
Well, we won't be late. I love you, Mom. Thanks.
Thanks.
Oh, your mom's watching the kids tonight. So what are you two up to? Oh, embassy suites. Do not disturb sign on the door. Mommy and Daddy are on the floor.
I wish.
What then?
Oh, nothing that exciting.
Marriage counseling? Do you know, that is the only kind of counseling.