Hey, Brian. You got a sec?
Yeah, I know what you're gonna say. It's all right.
No, I heard you got in trouble. I feel awful.
It's fine. It was my first slip-up in nine years of micing you.
Well, thanks for being a good friend.
Sure. Anytime. How about you and Jim? Everything squared away?
Yeah. Mostly.
Pam, phone call.
Um, I'm sorry.
Um, hey, say hi to Alyssa.
Will do.
Okay. Thank you.
Sure.
Hey, boom guy.
Oh, hey, Meredith.
When are you gonna boom me?
Uh, listen, they're cracking down on us talking to the subjects.
It's a lame rule, but you know, I wanna... I'll see you later.
Got it.
Okay.
Hey. So I hear you're bringing in some people to interview for the sales job?
That's right. Couple old friends.
Ballers only must be this cool to ride.
Well, uh, see, you raised it.
Did I? Oh, yes, I did.
Wallace is letting me hire a junior sales associate to sit at Jim's desk while he's away in Philly.
Finally, I'll have someone at my desk clump who gets me.
It's like, really, Jim?
You don't understand the difference between a slaughterhouse and a rendering plant?
Uh, remind me not to lend you any dead cows or horses.
Wow.
You know what, man? I deserve this job.
I scored Stone and Sun suit warehouse with you,
and God knows to get the Scranton White pages with Jan.
I went above and beyond.
And under.
You know what?
You're gonna get your interview, okay?
I know that you're going head to head against some real superstars,
but you've got a really good chance.
Clark has no chance.
I mean, he's up against my buddy Roll for God's sake.
Guy goes fishing with hand grenades.
And Trevor?
He'll make you laugh so hard you'll puke your pants.
This sucks.
You know, you put in 12 grueling weeks at a company, and what do they do?
They make you compete for a promotion, like an animal.
You know, I thought this was an office, not the Thunderdome.
Big changes coming to the old desk clump.
No longer a Pam-Jim alliance against Dwight.
Now it is Dwight and a friend Axis against Pam.
You could have just called that an alliance too, right?
I chose my words very carefully.
Things are a little delicate with me and Pam right now.
And if my working in Philly is gonna end up doubling the Dwight in her life,
that's only gonna make things worse.
Whew.
You interviewing for the sales job too?
No. You're interviewing for it.
I'm getting it.
Well, I wouldn't be so sure about that.
I mean, I've been working here 12 weeks.
That's a full season of Homeland.
A ton of things can happen in that amount of time, as we've seen.
I'm Rolf. Rolf-all.
Rolf-all.
Sounds kind of like Rol-dol.
Go to hell.
There he is.
Hey.
Come on, buddy.
Let's do this.
Sorry, Rolf goes first. You don't compare.
When you're with the R-O-L-F, you're literally rolling on the laughing floor.
Come on.
Nice.
Rolf is my best friend, and he is the man.
Cool, calm, and collected 24-7.
Just try and rattle Rolf, I dare you.
Such a sweet guy.
When are you talking to David Wallace?
I'm talking to him this afternoon, but don't get your hopes up.