Uh, what else? I've seen Dirty Dancing like 10 times.
Breaks my heart every time, you know?
Whoa! Andy!
Huh.
That's way easy. Sure can dance dirty.
Don't you have any sunblock?
No, Walter J. has been hoarding it.
You want to worry about a part of my body?
Worry about my eyes.
They're like two flaming meatballs in my skull.
Last week, Andy set sail for the Bahamas to sell his family's boat.
And he took his brother, but not me.
I was kind of sad at first, but then I remembered that Bob Marley song.
No woman, no cry.
Check this out.
It keeps my hair out of my stare.
Also helps me combat the glare bear. That's what I call the sun now.
Andy, it's Darryl. Take your drawers off your head.
Ah!
That happens about five times a day.
Look at this. Old man in the sea. Finally going to finish it.
You know, I've started it like a thousand times.
What else can I show you?
Uh, over here is my trusty console.
Check out my trusty comp.
Andy, why is it pointed north?
At no time should you be traveling north.
Relax, Pam. That thing's been broken for days.
Because I was using it as a bongo.
Charmin' with the glare bear, mon. Charmin'. Charmin' with the glare bear.
Oh, damn it!
Oh, Andy, was that your drinking water?
Yeah, it was. That's okay, though. I got this cool desalinator device.
It sucks up sea water through this hose and pumps out fresh water.
See, check it out.
Ow!
Oh!
Ah!
That's not good.
I better sign off. I hate to get going.
I mean, these Skype sessions are like the only thing to keep me sane out here, you know?
Ha ha ha ha!
Ha ha ha!
He's been sailing for two days.
I'll leave you with this. The image of a man and his boat.
Burn this into your brains.
Yeah.
No, no.
Oh! Oh!
Oh!
Andy? Andy? Andy? Andy?
Oh.
Dwight Schrute.
Well, hi there, David Wallace.
Why would you ever call me when the manager's out of town?
Well, I have some very exciting news.
And you didn't call Jim. That seems significant.
Hey, David.
Jim, good. You should hear this, too.
No, he shouldn't.
Go ahead, David.
Nothing.
Okay, David, I want to take you off speaker, but I don't know where I'd put you.
I'm sorry.
Guys, listen, this is big news.
The Scranton White Pages just got in contact with my office.
They have apparently dropped their supplier for the last ten years.
The White Pages.
The White Pages. Do you want it? No.
Do you use it? No.
Does it inexplicably show up on your doorstep three times a year?
Yes, yes, and yes.
There's a reason we in the paper industry call this thing the White Whale.
Look at all that sweet blubber.
Look, we need our top salesman running point on this, and Dwight, that is you.