The documentary series finished airing ages ago.
Why is PBS sending another crew?
We're getting bonus footage for the DVD.
Nobody buys DVDs anymore.
It'll be a pledge gift.
PBS, the propaganda wing of Bill and Melinda Gates
and viewers like you.
In the past year, I have consolidated
the entire Scranton paper market.
We regained the white pages, the school district,
Lackawanna County, we supply them all.
I'm getting married tomorrow afternoon.
And in the morning, there's a mini reunion,
a kind of a Where Are They Now panel at a local theater.
It'll be nice to see everyone again.
I haven't seen Kevin since we let him go.
Buh-buh-buh-buh-buh-buh-buh-buh-buh-buh-buh-buh.
Today marks several important milestones.
Stanley, as you know, is retiring.
Applause.
I've been looking forward to this day
since I was 18 years old.
Speech! No.
And our next and most thickly frosted cake
is for Kevin.
Yes!
Wait, why?
Go ahead and just read the frosting.
Get out?
What does that mean?
It's a colloquial way of saying you're fired,
Kevin, which you are.
What?
Dwight, you can't do that.
Sorry.
Well, if anyone here can make a case for Kevin staying...
Dwight, come on.
Based on his merit...
Uh...
Um...
I'm good.
Well, Toby will stop it.
Any time anyone's ever been fired, Toby's blocked it, so...
Yeah, yeah, I don't think...
Wait, wait, hold that thought.
Here's your cake.
Bye-bye, Toby.
At least I got chocolate.
I bike to work now.
Saves on gas, cheaper than a vasectomy,
and, uh... oh, yeah, it's good for the environment, too.
Pam and I are great.
She just recently finished her mural
for the Irish Cultural Centre.
I'm going to go to the museum.
Pam finished her mural for the Irish Cultural Centre.
Whoo!
Good job, Pam.
And Dwight is imitating Japanese business practices
for reasons he explained to us in Japanese.
Angela, are you ready for the wedding?
Yes. My heart is so open.
I'm so at peace.
Ugh, look at Meredith.
She's disgusting.
Those feet, they're like the paws of an orangutan.
I think she looks good.
Now that she's wearing sports bras,
we don't see her boobs as much.
I was at a dog fight this summer,
and I thought, we should not be eating these things.
Animals. So I went vegan.