Daryl?
Sounds good.
You're a movie star.
Oh, hey guys, it's 522.
We can go home.
Sounds good.
Stone and Sons Suit Warehouse recently lost their paper provider.
They're a family owned business.
Jim and I used to clean up at those.
We'd go in pretending to be family.
Brothers.
We did it at a family owned law firm,
at a family owned construction company,
and a family owned motorcycle store.
Jim and Dwight Schrupert.
I was the dynamic likable winner that was doted upon by Mom.
And Jim was the closeted foot fetishist pretending to belong.
The client never knew any of that.
But I knew.
I hope you've been paying your wig storage bills, Jimbo,
because it's time for another episode of Handsome and Stinky Paper Brothers for Hire.
Sorry Stinky, can't do it. Too busy.
Oh God, this again? You're stinky.
Okay, there's no possible way I can get there,
so just ask Phyllis. She can be your older sister.
Phyllis, my sister, more like my dead great great grandmother who died of stupidity.
I have ears, Dwight.
Oh, do you really have ears, Phyllis?
Like all human beings, we all have ears.
See what you leave me with here, Jim?
Hey, I'm in Philadelphia right now.
How is that my problem? Get in your car and drive down here.
You can make it in 30 minutes if you drive 240 miles per hour.
Huh. How long would it take me if I drove 300 miles an hour?
Hmm. That's a good question. 300 times...