To me, the Sixers are a five seat tops.
I think they're going to the conference finals.
No.
Bynum.
Obvious monster.
I have three point shooting.
Don't you...
I bit my lip at lunch today.
Sucks.
Anyway, I just don't see it.
The nicks are tough.
The nets are tough.
Oh, the nets are super tough.
Now I have this big bump in my lip that hurts.
I hate it.
The hooks are terrible.
They're always terrible.
Okay, you need to think about it before you come with the...
...
Whatever.
It's not a big deal.
You know, I always tell my three year old,
if this is the worst thing that's going to happen,
you got to be kidding me.
Okay.
Pam, that's it.
I'm going home.
Maybe that's a shopping list.
He's buying a ham, skeleton, and a rainbow?
It's Creed.
We found this weird drawing under Creed's desk.
So bizarre.
Oh my God.
It's a map.
Of course.
Okay, so the waves, water.
The water cooler.
And a hammes, food, the kitchen.
The bucket is the bathroom.
It's a map of the office.
Bingo.
Who's the skeleton?
Angela.
You're the cheeseburger.
Hey.
What am I?
I don't know.
The toilet.
He used the bucket to signify the bathroom,
the toilet to signify me.
I'm sorry.
Hello.
Hey Creed.
Are you lost?
What?
No.
Lost in the office?
Nope.
Anybody going back to the little pinch soon?
I am.
Want some company?
Okay.
Morning Meredith.
What?
Oh, sorry.
Pam.
Yikes.
Jim's been spending a few days a week in Philly,
and I'm not going to lie, it's been challenging.
Yesterday things took a turn for the worse.
I found out Cece has lice.
So I was up all night disinfecting every sheet,
towel, toy, item of clothing in the entire house.
I'm exhausted.
But don't tell Jim.
He has a huge meeting today, under a lot of pressure.
And he's doing it all for the family.
Hey.
There he is.
You cool for today?
Cool?
Curse if I'm so cool, I'm frozen.
Sorry.
I will not talk like that.
I'll be cool.
I am meeting Dr. J today, otherwise known
as Julius Irving, Fame 76er, and my own personal hero.
But I have to be careful not to rub in Pam's face,
because let's be honest, how would I
feel if I was at home stuck with the kids
while she was go-karting with John Stamos?
You sound tired.
Everything OK?
Great.
Everything's great.
Hey, are you nervous about your big meeting?
A little bit.
It's a lot of pressure, you know.
But that's what I signed up for, right?
Jim, Flimmel's here.
You know what, I got to hop off because my taxi is here
to take me to the meeting.
Oh, call me later.
OK.
Talk.
Thanks.
I love you.
Love you, too.
Bye.
How you doing?
OK.
I mean, it's what you want, so.
It's how it has to be.
I know.
It's just hard.
Me and Val were going nowhere.
And if I'm going to be working in Philly,
I'm going to need my freedom.
So I convinced Val to break out with me.
Here's how you do it.
You say, what are you going to do, break out with me?
Like, as a joke.
And then you gain a lot of weight.
I'll never be sorry, not for a moment of it.
Me neither.
Hey, Meredith.
I need your supply requests today.
She was eight in the morning.
Will you stop your nagging already?
No wonder Jim left you.
He didn't leave me.
He just went part time.
Can you just fill out the form, please?
Yes.
I'm sure she's just confused.
People scratch their heads when they're confused.
Not always like an ape, the way Meredith just did.
But it happens.