Gotta clear out this cabinet, people.
A lot of these are dead accounts.
What? Scranton Mimeograph Corp.
I don't think we're doing business with them anytime soon.
That's odd.
A letter from Robert Dunder.
A valuable artifact has come into my possession.
I have hidden it until such time as a person of strong intellect
may safely recover it.
This golden chalice is of immeasurable historical and religious significance.
The Holy Grail.
Did you send Dwight on a quest for the Holy Grail?
I think I'm a little too busy these days to send...
Oh my God.
I did send Dwight on a quest for the Holy Grail.
The Dunder Code!
I completely forgot about that prank.
That had to be like six or seven years ago.
Stayed late every night for a month.
Had a lot more free time back then.
I don't get it.
Aha! A light bulb.
A light bulb.
Okay. Okay.
Invisible ink.
Whoa.
Higher than numbers go.
The ceiling above the county!
Dwight! Down, Dwight! Dwight!
Man, I wish I was there to see his face when he gets to the end.
And finds the...pink grail.
No grail?
You don't remember?
I don't.
An X.
Annex.
It must open something in the annex.
Oh.
Sidus and Troiti.
Seat of entrance.
Hya!
What?
That's a flush.
The warehouse!
There's nothing down here.
Oh. I expected more from young Albert.
Just...forget it. Forget it.
So, how are we getting on with our grand...