THEME MUSIC
I'm taking some time off from work, well my other work, because we needed it.
It's great.
The phone's been ringing off the hook.
Guys in Philly are kind of going nuts.
That doesn't matter.
This does.
It's the only thing that matters.
We had some really nice days together.
Mm-hmm.
Nice morning too.
Beasley.
Oh my god.
Hey, which tie makes me look like a guy who likes sofas?
My agent's putting me up for a furniture commercial.
Ah, definitely blue.
Totally, right?
So big tuna, what's up?
Back in the small pond.
For now, yeah.
I was just spreading myself way too thin.
Thin sliced tuna, carpaccio, go on.
Well, it took me a while, but I finally realized that I can't give 100% to two things at once.
Yeah, tell me about it.
I've been trying to act and manage this branch.
Half the time I don't know if I'm wearing my stage makeup or my work makeup.
Huh.
Well, you know, you can't have everything, so you gotta ask yourself what makes you the
happiest.
Go all in for what's most important.
That's my new thing.
Is everything okay?
No, everything is not okay.
County took my cats.
Wait, all of them?
Two Saxworth.
Apparently, my apartment complex has rules about how many pets are too many for a studio.
And while I was out picking Philip up from daycare, they came.
They came into my house.
That's awful, Angela.
I'm so sorry.
It's the b**** that lives downstairs.
She's this uptight, judgmental shrew.
You know the type.
I've never met anyone like that.
You're my god.
And I have no one left.
Without my cats, I am utterly and completely alone.
Angela, you still have your son.
I guess.
Attention, everyone.
May I have your attention?
There are four new deadly weapons in this office.
Basher, thrasher, crasher, and...
Smasher.
Smasher?
No, where'd you get that?
Fireball.
Cat!
This morning, after hours of combat with some of the city's best teenagers, I earned my
black belt in...
Gojo crew.
...Marshal Arts.
I had to find a new dojo after Sensei Ira and I parted ways.
My new sensei, Sensei Billy, thought I had more than enough training to take the test.
Turns out, Sensei Ira was a bit of a shyster.
Sensei Billy says most students don't spend $150,000 over 20 years to get their black
belt.
I would like to invite you all to my black belt ceremony right here in the office at
lunch.
Lunch not provided.
Fireball!
Yeah!
That's how it's done.
That's pretty good.
I feel safe.
Aaron, is Andi in?
Oh, is Andi in?
Sorry, I thought you said is Indian.
And I was like, is Indian what?
Is Indian food good?
Is Indian jewelry pretty?
Is Indian hair an expensive kind of wig?
Yes, to all three, by the way.
Lately, I've been having a lot of trouble keeping track of Andi's calendar.
His student film audition schedule is crazy hectic.
Yes, there's Andi.
Andi is in.
I'm a good receptionist.
I know he's in.
David Walrus, in his native habitat.
Hey Andi, can we go in your office and talk?
Yeah.
This isn't going to be an easy conversation.
I told Andi that he was on very thin ice when he snuck away for three months to the Caribbean.
Then last week he used company money to buy...