Uh-oh. She's doing it again.
Phyllis has gotten into audiobooks,
and lately she's been listening to 50 Shades of Grey,
which, if you don't know what it is, it's a book about a, um...
It's porn. Yeah.
Seriously?
This is unacceptable. It's officially a hostile work environment.
Why?
Somebody just needs to get her attention, tell her it's not okay to do this in public.
Be careful. I pulled my mom's dog off a pillow once, and I got bit.
Just ignore her. Sooner or later she'll finish.
Oh, we heard it. Good lord.
What?
Phyllis is masturbating in the office right now as we speak.
Can we skip the color commentary and just have Andy go out there and fire her?
You can't do that.
Turns out she's allowed to have feelings of sexual arousal.
Doesn't become a violation until she physically acts on it.
No!
Tony, how do you propose that?
Okay, wait, wait, wait, wait. Why is Phyllis so aroused?
She's listening to 50 Shades of Grey.
Well, there you go. Es muy caliente.
Okay, you are useless. I'll take care of this.
What the hell?
It's okay, guys. She's no longer horny.
Excuse me, dirty birdie.
What?
You're gonna have this back at the end of the day.
Okay.
Ah!
Clark, I need your advice. I'm having some lady troubles.
What's her name?
Esther Brueger.
Sweet.
Lives on the neighboring farm, 85 acres.
Oh, yeah. Keep talking.
Well, we've been out three times. There has been physicality.
The thing is, we were hanging out with her father the other night looking at a farm catalog.
Next thing I know, he wants to lease a tractor with me.
Ugh!
What do you think?
The same thing that you think.
A long-term tractor lease can put pressure on a relationship.
God, a lot of my buddies are going through the same thing right now.
Something in the hair.
Here you go.
And good for you, Dwight. I'm so glad you found someone.
I bet she's got kind eyes.
Dwight is dating a Brussels sprout farmer named Esther.
She's coming here this afternoon with her father.
Who knows? Maybe she'll be pulling the horse cart.
Cece has been calling me Pamela, like, four times this week.
Oh, man.
I wonder if she'll start calling you Jim.
Oh, boy. Please don't.
I know.
Let's not let that happen.
Um...
Oh, what was I gonna say?
Well, you know, your assistant told me that you have a big pitch meeting today.
With Ryan Howard. How did that happen?
Not that Ryan Howard. Um, the Phillies' first baseman, actually.
Oh, okay.
Yeah, yeah. Exactly.
Oh.
Um, okay. Well?
Yeah. So I'll talk to you later.
Yeah, sounds good. Okay.
Okay, great. Bye.
Bye.
Hey, what's going on?
Ooh, did Gangnam Style put out a new song?
There's a promo for the documentary on the web.
Play it again.
The Boss.
Oh, hey!
That's Michael.
Oh, yeah.