MUSIC
Hey.
I feel so lucky we're in the same city for Valentine's Day.
It's like magic.
Or it's like me getting on my hands and knees and begging my partners to switch it Tuesday for Thursday.
Alakazam.
By the way, they do need an extra day next week.
Aunt Poof, he disappears.
Hey.
Wanna play hooky today?
Oh, maybe.
What do you got in mind?
We can do anything you want.
I really wanna have fun today because tomorrow is going to be a nightmare.
Andy's coming back from his stupid dumb boat trip.
He's been rude.
He's been selfish.
I think he's a big jerk.
And I'm breaking up with him.
Bam, Andy!
How do you like me now?
I hope as a friend.
Erin says she's gonna break up with Andy, but I'm not sure.
He's coming back tomorrow.
And surprise, today she wants to do whatever I'd like.
You know, when I was a kid we had a dog who got real sick and we had to send him to a farm.
And on his last day we did everything he loved.
And nobody looked at him and said, dog, we're gonna kill you.
Wanna play catch in the parking lot?
Sure.
Great.
Get my coat.
Perfect.
Oh, you're good.
Or lucky.
Well, me too.
Oh.
Alright, it's under the car.
You gotta go get a stick.
Come on, Pete.
Go get a stick.
His name was Darby.
He was a beagle mix.
And much of his last day was spent playing with a stick.
Oh!
Sorry.
It's alright.
I get it.
Oh.
Oh!
Some homeless guy stashed his stuff back here.
Oh, ew.
Oh, Pete, drop it.
Drop it.
That's dirty.
Pete, come on.
Oh!
Pete, drop it.
Drop it, Pete.
No, that's dirty.
You're not bringing that in the office.
Did you even get the frisbee?
No, stay.
Nellie, what's wrong with your face?
Andy's coming back tomorrow.
Oh.
Ugh.
I guess I'll be back to one lunch and one nap a day.