Can you guys come with me for a minute?
I know you saw me with the Senator.
I think I'm in love.
Possibly for the first time.
So yes, Senator Lipton and I are having an affair.
I hope that I can count on your sensitivity, maturity, and discretion.
Why?
Alright good, yeah.
Just sell it and get the best price you can.
Or we can hope for a holiday rally.
Mike, I'm not a day trader.
I'm just a first responder in a disaster.
Andy's family had a total meltdown.
His dad blew through all their money and took off to Argentina with a younger woman.
And his brother, Walt Jr., locked himself in the wine cellar.
The weirdest part is Andy.
The aftermath got dumped on him and the way he's been handling it is just so...
Competent.
Right?
Are the Nards hurting?
Yeah, you bet.
Got kicked pretty hard.
Family shattered.
Super sad.
But I'm kind of crushing it in the damage control department.
So that's cool.
I wish my dad could see me now.
Of course he caused this whole mess so...
F*** him.
Kevin, listen to me.
I'm in love with the senator and I need time to sort this out in a responsible manner.
So I need your help in keeping it a secret because this means the world to me.
Okay?
That's beautiful.
No, I totally get that.
Can you do this, Kevin?
I really want to.
Whatever happens, always remember that.
I don't know what that means.
Hey, hey.
Oh, great.
Yeah, um, I'll get right back to you.
Hey, guys, has anyone ever heard of Iris Black on the radio?
Yeah, she hosts the Dr. Laura show.
Nope, that's Dr. Laura.
Well, her show, Bizwiz, wants someone from Dunder Mifflin to come on the air today.
Does anybody feel particularly passionate about local business issues?
I do.
The media can make you famous.
And do you have any idea how easy it is to sell something when you're famous?
Uh, yeah, wow, ten reams of 40-pound bond at only 6.90 after discount?
Whatever you say, Brad Pitt.
It's that easy.
Hey, so that good-looking single brother of yours heard he was in a downward spiral with
booze?
Yeah, he's in rehab, actually.
Which place?
The one right near Philly?
That could be in an hour.
No, it's in New Mexico.
Wow.
So, how are you holding up?
We're done, Meredith.
Right.
Greta the Tittle Tattle prattled on about the little metal bottle.
She spat a bit of spittle on the moth of Brittle's cattle in a bitter battle.
Hey, hey, stop questioning my methods, okay?
I was chosen for this task for a very good reason.
No, you chose yourself.
Tricky Siskel spat a bit of wicked biscuit in Nikki Sixx's sticky whiskers.
When you talk to Iris, will you tell her Stanley Hudson's SLO?
No.
Iris Black has not responded to one of my fan letters, but I know that she reads them.
If you're watching this, Iris, I'm your number one fan.
All right, guys, there's a lot of assets here that my dad—