Andy's coming back today.
David Wallace sent him on an outward bound wilderness adventure for a whole month
to make him more decisive and confident.
He sent his own son too.
And the counselor said they both grew up big time.
How was my summer?
It was pretty mixed.
I invented a new power drink made out of beet runoff.
Mmm. Mmm.
So that's really good.
But I got some disappointing medical news.
Mr. Shrut, the results are in. You're not the father.
I told you.
Oh, God! Oh, my God!
Oh, what a summer.
An emotional roller coaster.
I ran over a turtle in the parking lot.
But then I saved him by gluing his shell back together.
But I'm not that good at puzzles.
Ah, that piece doesn't go there.
Shh.
So I patched him with stuff from around the office.
But I couldn't get the pieces to fit right.
Then, one day, while I was reaching for the glue,
I crushed his shell again.
But I rebuilt him even better that time.
But it turned out the turtle was already dead.
Probably when I ran over him the first time.
For us? Um...
Nothing new, really. The kids are great.
You are really good at modesty. She's a genius.
She painted this incredible mural in the kids' room.
There's a hippo leading a parade of 500 children.
Well, you have that interesting thing.
Oh.
Yes, Jim's friend is starting a new company
based on this idea that Jim had when they were back in college.
It's sports marketing, basically, but the athletes are partners.
And he wanted Jim to be a partner, too.
In Philly.