Oh, hey, champions.
Good morning.
Quarterfinal's in an hour.
Hope you got some sleep,
because I am gonna be haunting your nightmares tonight.
I did. I got some really good sleep.
Did you?
Zzzz.
Yesterday was the first round
of a branch-wide paper airplane contest.
It was being sponsored by Wirehammer Paper
in an effort to get us to sell more of their new product,
Airstream Deluxe 80.
The Cadillac of paper.
It's not so easy on the environment,
if you know what I mean.
It's practically made of plastic.
We started with 16 brave aviators.
Some used skill.
Others relied on showmanship.
Others seemed not to comprehend what a paper airplane is.
And, of course, there was the odd moment
of heartbreak and disaster.
I left my glasses down here somewhere.
I'm not sure what I'm doing.
Yeah, I left my glasses down here somewhere.
Cross them through. Beep, beep.
Ow! Ow!
I didn't see who you should have yelled crossing!
I'm sorry!
Okay, so is that my spot?
We are now down to an Elite Eight.
Well, Seven and Toby.
Be careful of that beaker. It contains dangerous acid.
It does not say dangerous, and there's no exclamation point.
Well, I'm just trying to bring some life to it.
Last week I got an agent, and this week I got a movie.
HRPDC Chemical Handling Protocols is going to be seen
by tons of workers in the industrial chemical community.
One of whom could have a cousin whose brother is Brad Pitt.
And then, boom, next thing you know, I'm in Moneyballs 2.
Andy?
Go away. We're running lines.
You wanted to see the gooey eye.
Oh, yeah. All right, get over here.
I am so freaked out by things going into eyes.
It just...wow.
Ugh! I can't even...
I'm so freaked out by that. Just go. Go, go, go, go, go.
All right, this can goolier, so we'll just do it later.
Okay.
All right. Where were we?
You stopped at Full of Acid.
And remember, do not attempt to extinguish a chemical fire with water.
It will only exacerbate the flame, the dangerous flame.
That was great, man. All right, I'm out of here.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Stop, stop, stop.
Don't go anywhere. I just need to find more colors.
Let's do it six more times.
Hey, I just wanted to say that you woke up early with the kids
and let me sleep, and I really appreciate that.
Thank you. I appreciate that you appreciate that.
So, we had couples therapy.
No shame in that. Get it all out in the open.
And we have homework.
Yes, we are supposed to look for every chance to acknowledge
and appreciate each other's sacrifices,
because I need to appreciate what Pam's been doing
to run the house while I'm in Philly.
And we're also supposed to speak our truths,
because if I had spoken my truth earlier about not wanting to move to Philly,
then maybe we wouldn't have had this opportunity for couples therapy.
Oh, we're supposed to call everything we don't want to do opportunities.
Heads up, everyone. If you really need something for me today,
let's get it done tomorrow. Carla Fern got me a gig.
Hey. Yeah.
Who's Carla Fern? Who is Carla Fern?
Well, wow. She's my agent and my drill sergeant
and one of my best friends.
Oh, and Oscar, I already figured out if I have to get emotional in the film,
I'm just going to think about you getting dumped by the senator.
Why don't you use your own life? I haven't just dumped you.
It's a little raw. Not cool, Oscar.
But you're just not cool.
Okay. Day two. Drama in the warehouse, guys.
This is Robert from Weigh a Hammer Paper,
who will be joining us to judge the final rounds.
Who's pumped for the quarterfinals, huh? I'm pumped.
Clark's a dead man.
All right. Sounds like somebody wants to walk away with this.
Oh, my God.
Nellie, you didn't tell us we could win money.