All right, everybody. Great season of softball.
I'm super proud of you guys.
And I think you're gonna like this little highlight reel
that I put together.
-"Summer Midflat!"
-"Andy Bernard Presents Summer Softball Epic Fails!"
Fail.
That's me. Fail.
Is this, like, a blooper reel?
A blooper reel? What is this, 2005?
It looked like Bob Saget?
Fail!
Who's this guy?
-♪ Meow, meow, meow, meow, meow, meow, meow, meow...
-♪ Look at him dance!
Fail! Fail!
I deserve that.
-♪ Do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do...
That was ошибle.
Can't take the fail?
Get out of the fail video!
My pleasure.
Hey, I'm Pete.
Puberty is such a drag, man.
And I'm Clark.
I like to eat toilet paper.
We fail.
I'd like to take a solemn moment to remember Jerry
in the warehouse who passed away this year.
Pfft.
Well, that's all, folks.
Ski you later, everybody.
Thanks for a great season.
What was that?
That was just normal video with you making vulgar noises.
Well, I worked with what I had.
Oscar, next time, do more failure stuff, okay?
What happened in that video I sent you?
Oh, that wasn't...
That didn't work.
That was not the right one.
I think I got it right.
Yeah.
Whoo!
Oh!
My bottles.
Wow.
That was not a fail.
That was actually a serious accident
that could have resulted into your bodily harm.
You're all failing right now.
Congratulations on your epic fail
of the use of the word fail!
Oh, God.
What's going on?
Nothing. Nothing is going on.
Keep moving, please.
What's he measuring?
Okay, excuse me.
I am the landlord.
This is between me and the management.
No one else, please.
It's an EMF hotspot.
Oh, my God.
It stands for electromagnetic field,
generally caused by a concentration of wiring
in one area, especially in the lower part of the body.
Oh, my God.
It's a very strong electric field.
I'm not sure if there's a problem with wiring in one area,
especially if poorly insulated.
Dwight?
Um, okay, I'm just walking into this.
You might understand there's a beehive in the wall.
You think I have a machine for measuring beehives?
I was just asking a question, Toby.
How are you not murdered every hour?
Well, I'm not getting paid to work in a microwave oven.
Okay, listen.
Everything here is up to code.
Oh, the wires need insulation.
It's a wire, people.
I'm not buying it for a coat.
Thank you.
You got it.
Last week, I finally told Pam
about the other job I took in Philly, the side job,
and she was so incredibly cool about it.
And now I just want to do something huge for her.
Like, if we were in some biker bar
and she mouthed off to some bikers
and they came lumbering over, and I was like,
gotta go through me first.
Andy, could I have a word, please?
It won't take a moment.
It's extremely important, and it really has to happen now.
Fine, I will give you one minute.
Oh, please don't use the hourglass.
You have one minute, and your minute has begun,
and no time will be added at the end,
even to accommodate this sentence
with all of its baroque dependent clauses
and cascading turns of phrase.
I'm trying to adopt a baby.
A baby what? A human?
And the agency require a character reference
to my employer.
Oh.
You wouldn't have to do anything.
I would write the letter myself.
You'd just simply sign it, so...
Okay, and fall right into your plagiarism entrapment scheme?
I don't think so.
And I happen to notice you're down to about 30 seconds here,
and those sand grains are tumbling with fury
down the sides of the hourglass.
It's not entrapment if I'm writing...
Time's up.
Fine.
Sure, I'll read her letter,
and if she tells the truth about how evil
and unfit to be a mother she is,
then yeah, I'll sign that.
Statistical correlations exist between EMF radiation
and various health hazards,
but mainstream studies are inconclusive.
That means you can't make me do squat.
You better fix this.
I already ditched my uterus
and I ain't losing any more good parts.
You people don't realize what you're asking.
I'd have to rip open the walls.
We'd have to shut this place down for a week.
Week off. That'd be great.
Hey, if you don't want to teach me the PowerPoint,
just say so.
I don't want to teach you PowerPoint.
Come on. Just show me the PowerPoint.
Just do the tutorial.
You're the tutorial.
No, dude, I'm not.
I'm not the tutorial.
You could be.
Mm-mm.
Listen, I know Quicken, After Effects,
Photoshop, and AutoCAD,
which is like the equivalent of owning a pickup truck.
Hey, you free this weekend?
Yeah, man, let's hang out.
Oh, I bet instead of hanging...