The building's custodian is on vacation for the month and Dwight is too cheap to hire a replacement.
So instead we're living in filth, but not for long because I have created the chore wheel.
Oh yeah, can I spin first?
Well it doesn't spin, we'll just move the wheel one notch each morning and you see what chore you get that day.
A wheel is supposed to spin.
Yeah, you know like guh guh guh no I'm familiar with spinning, it's just that wouldn't work with a chore wheel because people might get the same chore.
Bah, boring. All she talks about is chores.
A wheel wants to spin Pam.
Spinning would be more fun.
Okay.
Okay, that's what I'm talking about!
Big money, big money!
Yeah!
Mug duty.
Yes, you clean all the mugs in the sink.
This sucks.
Yeah, seriously it's like everything on there is work.
I don't think you guys understand why we're doing this.
Yeah, and I don't think that you understand wheels.
I've been through several rounds of development with the team and here's where we stand with the chore wheel.
We've got prizes. Ten bucks, candy bar, manager for an hour, but there are also penalties like no internet, Stanley gets your lunch.
The one thing that is not on the chore wheel is chores, but they were right, it's more fun this way.
Tiny wheel! Tiny wheel! Tiny wheel!
The tiny wheel actually does have chores. It's so cute no one seems to mind.
Toilets!
Pam, we gotta go.
Cece, go back inside. Grandma's got breakfast, okay?
We are going to Roy's wedding.
Yep, Roy. I think the only weird thing about going to your wife's ex-fiance's wedding on a weekday at 8am is that it's your wife's ex-fiance.
Thanks, Mom!
A banana?
Yeah, I'm afraid he's only gonna have hot talks.
Oh, come on, not even Roy will have hot talks.
I planned a wedding with him. He wanted hot dogs.
It's all weird.
Oh, Pete, you've got mail.
Really? I got something?
Well, it's addressed to customer service, so it's your mail.
Well, you know, I'm also customer service.
Yeah, I'm alternating.
Yay, another person yelling at me.
Well, it could be a nice letter. I write nice letters to companies all the time.
That's really nice.
Wow, Newsweek, huh? This election thing is crazy, right?
It's open.
Oh, yeah, I accidentally read it. It's not a nice letter.
Get excited. The special projects fairy has arrived.
I know you don't really exist.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
The fairy has arrived.
I know you don't really exist.
Today I launched my big charity initiative, Operation Giveback.
Andy has shot down all of my special projects thus far, but this one is about charity,
so I'd like to see him piss on that one.
Daryl!
Oh, what's happening?
Congratulations, baby.
Oh, thank you.
Coconut shrimp.
I told you I'd have it.
Yes, you did.
Oh, you have arrived, sir. Well done.
Roy and I used to work together downstairs in a warehouse.
He used to be engaged to Pam, but then she tossed him aside like a cold-hearted bitch.