I do want to thank you all for donating to this year's Thanksgiving Canned Food Drive.
It's tough to be hungry during the holidays. That's why it's so great to see you all step up so generously to bring in this wonderful feast.
For instance, Phyllis, it must have been very difficult for you to part with this dented can of water chestnuts.
Well, they're good in stir-fries.
Is botulism good in stir-fries?
Creed, you brought in this can of garbanzo beans from 1990.
Beans don't age, they're beans.
It's a can of racquetballs.
I don't even know what this is.
Oh, Darryl, it's brown.
Okay, what is it?
What do you mean? It's brown.
I eat some brown every week.
Hot brown, ice brown, cream of brown, pasta with brown sauce, apple brown, scramble brown, fried brown.
It's brain food.
Poor people are not dumpsters for your garbage, guys.
Well, they should be grateful. This is good food.
All right, which is why we are not going home early today and can hang out and have a little Thanksgiving feast of our own.
Yes!
With this canned food.
You son of a bitch!
Don't, Darryl.
Kevin, you're getting it everywhere.
Not even beans.
No.
I think the point was made and now we're just wasting food.
But when Toby gets going, it's just no stopping him.
Happy Thanksgiving. And remember, you did this to yourselves.
I think everybody learned a valuable lesson.
And if I had a Thanksgiving meal with other people for the first time in years, good for me.
You know?
Yesterday, Angela may or may not have figured out that I'm having an affair with her husband.
So I just have to wait and see.
When she comes in, if she's cold and awkward and cruel to me, then great.
It's business as usual.
Good morning.
Oscar.
Can I ask you a question?
Of course. Ask me what? Questions.
Is it cool in here to you?
Yes, a little bit.
Yes.
I think the thermostat is acting up again.
It's a stupid thermostat.
Nothing's a catastrophe.
So I'm going to, on your suggestion, get someone to fix it. I'll just go downstairs.
Thank you.
No. Thank you, Angela.
She doesn't know. I shouldn't be surprised.
This is a woman who married a man who's obviously a homosexual.
Basically, she has her head in the sand.
In a way, I feel sorry for her.
I guess the universe rewards true love.
Well, well, well. It's finally happened.
Pam has ceased caring.
These are my painting clothes.
I think I'm going to do it. I am really going to start painting the warehouse mural today.
Sure you don't want to put another coat of primer on that, Pam?
Queen of the primer, that one.
You got this, Beasley.
Actually, do you want me to come down and help you get started?
Are you avoiding your phone call?
What? Yeah, right. As if.
Today I will be asking David Wallace if I can start working part-time
because the sports marketing company that I started really needs me to be there.
Last week, Jim wasn't there, and they named the company Athlead.
I could have prevented that. So I have to talk to Wallace.
Tell them your opening line.
Hey, David, how did you like a guy who's not here as much, gets paid the same amount of salary,
and has bigger fish to fry in Philadelphia?
I think it's good. He likes fishing.
This is going to be awful.
One of my jobs is to input customer complaints into the computer.
And when they're in, I fill out one of these complaints.