Oh, I have second thoughts about one of the shirts I packed.
The blue one with the stripes.
I'm sure it's fine. It's a blue shirt.
Oh, yeah, but I'm wondering if it's too blue.
Like, am I making a statement with the blueness?
I am leaving early today for Philly.
Because tomorrow is the first day of my new job.
So I figure I'd get in at five, check in at a hotel about six,
so I can get a real good night of restless sleep, nervous puking.
Excuse me, trying to get work done?
Some people don't care about Jim's new sports job and philla-whatever?
So you know my job has something to do with sports,
but you don't know the end of the word Philadelphia.
Philadelphia, from the Greek, philia meaning love,
and Adolf meaning Adolf, the city that loves Adolf.
Good luck with your new enterprise.
And don't wear the blue striped shirt.
It makes your neck look like an old mop handle.
Oh, hey guys, the Christmas party is today.
Merry Christmas, everyone!
No, is it?
I mean, it says Xmas party, but I think we all know what that's code for.
So we're not going to have a Christmas party this year?
Angela, how could you do this to us?
Oh, right, like I'm responsible because I'm in charge of the party planning committee.
Well, you are the one in charge of it.
Don't blame me for something we all forgot.
Let's not blame her for something we all forgot.
I didn't realize how many of Angela's opinions I agreed with
until she tried to have my kneecap shattered for sleeping with her husband.
She makes a lot of very sound points.
I knew the party was today, but nobody asked me to plan it, so I didn't.
Funny how that works.
We're out there sweating our balls off every day, busting our balls.
We deserve a Christmas party.
Well, then why don't we just get some liquor and those mini cupcakes?
Mini cupcakes?
As in the mini version of regular cupcakes, which is already a mini version of cake?
Honestly, where does it end with you people?
What about an authentic Pennsylvania Dutch Christmas?
Drink some Glühwein, enjoy some Hasenfeffer,
enjoy Christmas with St. Nicholas's rural German companion, Bouschnickel.
Yes, that, that, that.
Definitely doing that. Are we all in agreement?
No.
Done, right?
No, I want tropical Christmas.
Topless Christmas.
Topless Swissmiss.
Spanish topless and Swissmiss hot cocoa.
What's so hard to understand?
Or, who was it that suggested the authentic Pennsylvania Dutch Christmas?
I think it was someone really popular.
We already said no.
No, no, no.
This is me and my family celebrating Pennsylvania Dutch Christmas in 1982 on the farm.
There's me and my brother Jeb breaking the ceremonial pig rib.
He doesn't come back for Christmas anymore.
The sepia tint is from an app on my phone.
This is the same photo Matrix style.
I'm not understanding the confusion.
Am I the only one who wants to try Hufflepuffs and Schnauzerhosen and meet this Glenn Pickle guy?
Party planning committee, emergency meeting, now.
I'm on it.
Great. I'm just hoping German terrorists don't take over this Christmas party.
They can go all John McLean on their asses.
Wait, German terrorists? That's oddly specific.
And I think, I think you mean John McCain.
Die Hard reference?
I haven't seen it.
You haven't seen Die Hard?
Why haven't you seen Die Hard?
I don't know, I just haven't.
Come on, you had to have at least seen some of it.
Nope.
Now, I have a machine gun.
Ho, ho, ho.
Come out to the coast, we'll get together, have a few laughs.
None of this makes any sense to me.
Oh yeah, and when he takes the gun off his back and he's like, yippee-ki-yay, motherfuckers.
Actually, he doesn't say that there.
He says it earlier when he's on the radio with Hans.
Yes, you are right. Forgive me.
Well, that's okay, bud.
Nope.
Common mistake.
No, it's not.
Nerd! Do you know every line of the movie?
My brother dared me to memorize it, and I did.