No, you lied to me, Andy.
You pretended to be in this office for three months
and you were sailing on your boat.
I resent that.
I never lied to you.
Really? Hey, David?
All is good in Scranton, P.A.
And all was good in Scranton, P.A. that day.
By the way, Oscar says hi.
Oscar says hi all the time.
He says all kinds of greetings.
Hi, hello, hola.
You tell me you've never heard Oscar say hi.
Andy.
You're calling me a liar.
Andy. By the way, that reminds me.
I want to ask you about some of the lies you've been telling me lately.
Watch it, Andy. Oh, here we go. January 7th, 2013.
Hey, Andy, all's well.
Been meaning to make it down there, but my wife's sick.
Well, which is it?
Is all well or is your wife sick?
Busted! My wife?
This has been a really tough time.
Yeah, yeah. Has it? Aaron just dumped me
and I can't remember any of the aha moments
I had on the boat.
That sounds weird to say, but I really miss my beard.
It was like a security blanket.
Andy.
I'm not gonna fire you.
You're not?
No. That's awesome.
I wouldn't own the company if it wasn't for you.
So, I owe you that.
David, I'll be there for you.
These five words I swear to you.
When you breathe, I want to be here for you.
I'll be there for you.
That's a poem by J.B. Jovi.
I want you to have it.
We are even.
Now, understand?
Got it? Crystal.
And you are on very, hey,
very thin ice.
Vanilla.
Vanilla ice.
He was a band.
Good morning.
Good morning. And how are you on this find?
That's fine.
Okay.
Are we ready?
Yeah.
Last week, Aaron told me
that our relationship will be proceeding
without me.
Now I have to see her
every day at work.
Which is brutal.
When people say office relationships
are a good idea, they never talk about what might happen
if you break up.
He sounds like a wounded animal.
Should have put him out of his misery
and just fired him.
I can't be around sad people. It makes me sad.
I'm the same way with horny people.
Okay.
Yes, Pete and I have started
seeing each other and Andy still doesn't
know. We thought that keeping it secret
was more considerate to him.
And hot for us.
I mean, I saw Pete's butt.
It's sick.
Oh, that's mine.
I'll just get it out of the way for you.
Jim set up a job interview for me today
in Philly. It's with
a real estate company, which
is a great fit for me because
I live in a house
and I know what a bathroom is.
I'm sorry.
I am just very nervous because
honestly, this is all moving a lot
faster than I expected
and because my resume
can fit on a Post-It note.
Don't just let her eat the grass. She'll puke it right up.
Okay, just put out two bowls
and see what happens.