This year I decided to really get into the spirit of Halloween.
Ah!
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha!
It may have been the costliest decision I've ever made.
My greased up head went into the pumpkin no problem, but...
It won't budge.
I can't get it out.
Try again.
I mean, I could try destroying the pumpkin.
No, no, no, no!
But as Jim and I discovered...
No!
Any blow to the pumpkin itself could prove fatal to me.
At first I drove myself crazy thinking about the things I should have done differently.
I never should have played that joke on Aaron.
I never should have hollowed out this damn pumpkin in the first place.
But then I realized I was being silly.
I mean, the pumpkin should rot off of my head in a month or two.
Right?
Ah!
Yeah!
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Woo!
Yeah!
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Hey guys.
Hey.
Pam, what are you?
I'm Cinderella.
Cece's really into princesses now, so we decided to turn them into positive female role models.
I'm an oncologist.
And you are a dog.
I'm a puppy.
Dang it.
I was worried that would happen.
It's okay.
Um, Jim.
You're not dressed up at all.
Sure am.
I am...
One of the men in black eyes.
Can I have your sunglasses?
Jim, come on.
I thought we were past this.
So, the sports marketing business that Jim told everyone about except for me...
There's a big investment lunch today, so I decided to skip the costume.
Unless he has a secret costume that he told everyone about except for me.
Getting a lot of mileage out of this, aren't you?
Yeah, we'll get used to it, bud.
A cheetah bug.
Ha ha ha ha!
You guys look great!
Just a reminder, the party is right after lunch, so make sure you get all your work done before that or throw it out.
Any questions?
The senator will be joining us later.
Not a question.
No, it wasn't.
Excellent.
That reminds me, has anyone seen Treble?
Anyone?
Could have sworn I saw some Treble somewhere.
Oh, ladies and gentlemen, here comes Treble!
I'm a man, a man without conviction.
You come and go, you come and go.
Come a, come a, come a, come a chameleon.
Loving would be easy if your colors were like my dreams.
Red, gold, and green. Red, gold, and green.
Come a, come on!
Ah! So good!
What lab did these little clones escape from?
My Cornell acapella group.
You were in an acapella group?
You went to Cornell?
Yeah, okay, ha ha ha ha.
But you have no idea how lucky you are
because HCT is doing a set at our Halloween party.
Ugh, I don't want to sit through a whole concert of that.
I do. I love the boss's interest.
That a boy, Clark.
Where are your boys staying?
How does it work in the room?
Should you get a privacy partition?
No, no, no, no, no, no, stay away.
They're staying with me. Us, actually.
Aaron's got all the tenors and I got all the basses and B-tones.
Jealous.
You know what I just realized?
They might actually call me up to solo on George Michael's Faith.
That was one of my signature songs.
Oh man, that would be insane.
I'm so not prepared.
Hosting the guys in my studio apartment has been no problem.
They took the bed.