Have you seen Darryl?
He's around here somewhere.
Hmm.
Yeah, Darryl's here.
So is Santa Claus.
It's just a regular Thursday.
Neither guy is here, and it's Friday.
Welcome to me and Darryl's world of lies.
Nobody knows it yet, but Darryl already started working in Philly.
So now he has to sneak out of here
like the sneakiest little sneaky sneak you ever saw.
And I'm his helper. It's so fun.
Hi, Darryl.
Here are your full-color printouts for this business.
Hey, Erin, I'm going to the bathroom.
Take your time.
Normally I don't do shady stuff,
but seeing as Andy's been gone three months
and Clark took some sort of sexification,
I figure I can cut loose a little.
I'm good at it, too.
Darryl, meet Bear-l.
How much did you pay for that?
Nothing. Won him at the carnival.
Spent a ton on tickets, though.
Drive safe.
Everybody knows I go to Philly.
I've just been using sick days I saved up,
but Erin was so excited about being sneaky sneaks,
I went along with it.
Ha ha ha! Darryl, you are too much!
That guy's hilarious. He's here today.
You're kidding. You have to work Saturday and Sunday?
Yeah, maybe you could come up here.
I could get us into the Sixers practice facility.
You could see Cece working on her dunks.
Maybe see you guys for dinner.
Yeah, well, I was kind of hoping to work on my mural this weekend.
I mean, I want to get it finished so I can start working on the other one.
Blow it off. I haven't seen you guys in days.
You blow it off.
Ma'am, I'm not saying murals aren't important.
But?
Nothing. I'm just not saying they're not important.
Okay, good, because it kind of sounded like you were going to say
that murals are important but not as important as something else.
Well, I certainly did not say that. Only a fool would say that.
Yes, only a fool would. Good save, helper.
I've really been putting in the hours on this mural.
And my boss is totally okay with it because he's in the Bahamas
and has no clue what anybody's doing.
I'm usually very self-critical. I hate what I paint,
but I don't know. This time I feel like it's really coming together.
Oh, my God!
Well, you've got to be kidding me.
What? Are those butts?
Huh?
No way.
No way!
Excuse me, everyone.
Is it okay if I leave early from work today?
It's Philip's first birthday, and the senator and I are hosting a party at our house.
Oh, cute.