Morning, Dwight.
Who are you?
Who am I?
I'm Jim.
We've been working together for 12 years.
Weird job, Dwight.
You're not Jim.
Jim's not Asian.
You seriously never noticed?
Hey, hats off to you for not seeing race.
Alright then, Jim.
Why don't you tell me about that sale that you made yesterday?
Wellington Systems sold them 10 cases of 24 pound letter stock.
Or were you talking about Krieger Murphy because I didn't close that one yet.
But I'm hoping I've got a voicemail from Paul Krieger waiting for me.
Please enter your password.
You have one new message.
How did you know?
No, no, no.
That is sensitive information only for employees, not outsiders.
Dwight, cut it out.
I'm trying to work.
You don't work here.
You're not Jim.
Jim, I got us that dinner reservation.
Grieco 730.
Oh great, can't wait.
Jim's at the dentist this morning and Steve is an actor friend of ours.
I don't know who you are, but you are not Jim.
This is Jim.
Oh, how did...
Hey, study buddies.
Oh, okay.
Getting things done.
Awesome.
It's all about finding ways to make yourself more efficient.
Life hacking, baby.
This morning, I brushed my teeth in the shower, saved myself 90 seconds, which I just used
to explain this to you.
Damn it.
Since Andy promoted me to assistant regional manager, I've been trying to step up my game,
be more productive.
In fact, you know what?
Let's knock out a few more of these soundbites while we're here.
Whoa.
That person has found him or herself in quite a predicament.
Woo hoo, that Toby.
When will he ever learn?
Andy, Andy, Andy.
I can't believe Kevin swallowed a pen.
I can't believe Kevin swallowed another pen.
Oscar, Oscar, Oscar.
Thanks.
Totally my fault.
What are you doing?
What?
French.
It's a great language.
If you're a chain-smoking acrobat.
I'm just trying to fit in better with Andy's family.
They all speak more than one language, usually when I'm there.
You want to learn a really impressive second language?
Try Dothraki.
Win over any man in my guild.
Dothraki is the native tongue of the nomadic, warmongering horse lords of Essos, as featured
in the superb home box office series Game of Thrones.
It has a lot of nudity, which I fast-forward through to get to the chopped-off heads.
I could teach you if you want.
It's a lot easier than French.
Yeah, let's do it.
Athavrosar!
It means excellent.
And we have begun.
Is everything okay?
Oh, oh yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Fine, fine, fine, fine.
I mean, I just don't want to burden you with my massive stress freak-outs.
Great.
It's just that I am taking my driver's license test in two days, and I need to practice with
an experienced driver in the car.
But I've had no time to do that, thanks to Demandee.
I just want to hit the open road and drive, man, but in whose car?
Nellie!
Get your wrinkly old balls in here.
Nellie, I could practice with you in my car at lunchtime.
Oh, Pan, thank you.
You are my savior.
I'm sorry.